<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Childrens Books that talk about &#39;Resilient&#39; on Monsty The Monster Truck</title>
    <link>https://www.monsty.co/tags/childrens-books-that-talk-about-resilient/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Childrens Books that talk about &#39;Resilient&#39; on Monsty The Monster Truck</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.monsty.co/tags/childrens-books-that-talk-about-resilient/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Slightly True Story of Cedar B Hartley</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_slightly_true_story_of_cedar_b_hartley_by_martine_murray_isbn_043948622x/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_slightly_true_story_of_cedar_b_hartley_by_martine_murray_isbn_043948622x/</guid>
      <description>The Slightly True Story of Cedar B Hartley by Martine Murray Title: The Slightly True Story of Cedar B. Hartley Author: Martine Murray Review: The Slightly True Story of Cedar B. Hartley is a charming and whimsical children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the tale of a young girl named Cedar, who lives in a small town with her loving family. The story follows Cedar as she navigates through the ups and downs of life, making new friends, and learning valuable life lessons along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Jump Into the Other World</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/a_jump_into_the_other_world_by_bruno_tognolini_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/a_jump_into_the_other_world_by_bruno_tognolini_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>A Jump Into the Other World by Bruno Tognolini Title: A Jump Into the Other World Author: Bruno Tognolini Review: A Jump Into the Other World is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that transports young readers on an exciting adventure filled with fantasy and valuable life lessons. Author Bruno Tognolini has crafted a story that captivates the imagination while teaching important morals. The book is suitable for children between the ages of 7 and 12.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Parcel of Patterns</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/a_parcel_of_patterns_by_jill_paton_walsh_isbn_722658982/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/a_parcel_of_patterns_by_jill_paton_walsh_isbn_722658982/</guid>
      <description>A Parcel of Patterns by Jill Paton Walsh Title: A Parcel of Patterns Author: Jill Paton Walsh A Parcel of Patterns is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book by Jill Paton Walsh, set in the 17th century during the time of the Great Plague. The story revolves around a young girl named Matilda, who lives in the village of Eyam. When the plague strikes, Matilda&amp;rsquo;s life takes a dramatic turn, and she must learn to cope with the challenges that come her way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The October Child</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_october_child_by_eleanor_spence_isbn_340605480/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_october_child_by_eleanor_spence_isbn_340605480/</guid>
      <description>The October Child by Eleanor Spence Title: The October Child Author: Eleanor Spence Review: The October Child is a beautifully written and illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book that captures the essence of the changing seasons and the magic of childhood. The story follows a young girl named October, who is born on the first day of October and experiences the world around her through the lens of the changing seasons. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jolanda, Daughter of the Black Corsair</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/jolanda_daughter_of_the_black_corsair_by_emilio_salgari_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/jolanda_daughter_of_the_black_corsair_by_emilio_salgari_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Jolanda, Daughter of the Black Corsair by Emilio Salgari Title: Jolanda, Daughter of the Black Corsair Author: Emilio Salgari Review: Jolanda, Daughter of the Black Corsair is a thrilling adventure story that follows the life of a young girl named Jolanda, who is the daughter of the infamous Black Corsair. This book is a perfect fit for children between the ages of 8 and 12, as it is filled with exciting pirate adventures, mysterious islands, and valuable life lessons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Missing From Saint-Agil</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/missing_from_saint-agil_by_pierre_very_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/missing_from_saint-agil_by_pierre_very_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Missing From Saint-Agil by Pierre Very Title: Missing from Saint-Agil Author: Pierre Very Target Age Group: 8-12 years old Review: &amp;ldquo;Missing from Saint-Agil&amp;rdquo; is a captivating mystery novel that will keep young readers on the edge of their seats. Written by Pierre Very, the story is set in the small town of Saint-Agil and follows the adventures of a group of children who come together to solve a perplexing mystery. The book is recommended for children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Dolphin Crossing</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_dolphin_crossing_by_jill_paton_walsh_isbn_140366245/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_dolphin_crossing_by_jill_paton_walsh_isbn_140366245/</guid>
      <description>The Dolphin Crossing by Jill Paton Walsh Title: The Dolphin Crossing Author: Jill Paton Walsh The Dolphin Crossing is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Jill Paton Walsh, which takes the readers on an exciting adventure through the eyes of a young boy named Martin. This book is suitable for children between the ages of 8 to 12 years old, as it contains a perfect blend of adventure, friendship, and moral lessons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To Kill a Mockingbird</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/to_kill_a_mockingbird_by_harper_lee_isbn_434012602/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/to_kill_a_mockingbird_by_harper_lee_isbn_434012602/</guid>
      <description>To Kill a Mockingbird by Harper Lee Title: To Kill a Mockingbird Author: Harper Lee Review: To Kill a Mockingbird, written by Harper Lee, is a captivating novel that tells the story of a young girl named Scout Finch and her brother Jem, growing up in the fictional town of Maycomb, Alabama during the 1930s. Through the eyes of these innocent children, the reader is exposed to the harsh realities of racism, prejudice, and injustice that were prevalent in the American South during that time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fire, Bed and Bone</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/fire_bed_and_bone_by_henrietta_branford_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/fire_bed_and_bone_by_henrietta_branford_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Fire, Bed and Bone by Henrietta Branford Title: Fire, Bed and Bone Author: Henrietta Branford Review: Fire, Bed and Bone is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book by Henrietta Branford that tells the story of a young boy named Robin who, after a series of unfortunate events, finds himself living on the streets of London. The book is a perfect blend of adventure, mystery, and historical fiction, making it an engaging read for children aged 8-12 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kensuke&#39;s Kingdom</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/kensukes_kingdom_by_michael_morpurgo_isbn_1405267372/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/kensukes_kingdom_by_michael_morpurgo_isbn_1405267372/</guid>
      <description>Kensuke&amp;rsquo;s Kingdom by Michael Morpurgo Title: Kensuke&amp;rsquo;s Kingdom Author: Michael Morpurgo Review: Kensuke&amp;rsquo;s Kingdom is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Michael Morpurgo. The story revolves around a young boy named Michael who embarks on a thrilling adventure with his family. The book is targeted towards children aged 8-12 years old and is a perfect blend of adventure, friendship, and self-discovery. The story begins with Michael and his family setting sail on a yacht to fulfill their dream of exploring the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rupert the Rapper and Aunt Deep Freeze</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/rupert_the_rapper_and_aunt_deep_freeze_by_sinikka_and_tiina_nopola_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/rupert_the_rapper_and_aunt_deep_freeze_by_sinikka_and_tiina_nopola_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Rupert the Rapper and Aunt Deep Freeze by Sinikka and Tiina Nopola Title: Rupert the Rapper and Aunt Deep Freeze Author: Sinikka and Tiina Nopola Review: Rupert the Rapper and Aunt Deep Freeze is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young boy named Rupert who discovers his passion for rapping. The book is filled with engaging illustrations and an entertaining storyline that captures the attention of young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Graveyard Book</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_graveyard_book_isbn_9780747598626/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_graveyard_book_isbn_9780747598626/</guid>
      <description>The Graveyard Book Title: The Graveyard Book Author: Neil Gaiman Review: The Graveyard Book is a captivating and enchanting novel written by the renowned author Neil Gaiman. This book is a perfect blend of mystery, adventure, and fantasy, making it an ideal read for children aged 8 to 12 years old. The story revolves around the life of a young boy named Nobody Owens, or Bod for short, who is adopted by the ghostly residents of a graveyard after his family is tragically murdered.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Naming of Tishkin Silk</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_naming_of_tishkin_silk_by_glenda_millard_isbn_9780374354817/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_naming_of_tishkin_silk_by_glenda_millard_isbn_9780374354817/</guid>
      <description>The Naming of Tishkin Silk by Glenda Millard Title: The Naming of Tishkin Silk Author: Glenda Millard The Naming of Tishkin Silk is a beautifully written children&amp;rsquo;s book by Glenda Millard that captures the essence of love, friendship, and self-discovery. This enchanting story is perfect for children between the ages of 8 to 12 years old, as it delves into themes that are both relatable and important for this age group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halinka</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/halinka_by_mirjam_pressler_isbn_9780440228578/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/halinka_by_mirjam_pressler_isbn_9780440228578/</guid>
      <description>Halinka by Mirjam Pressler Title: Halinka Author: Mirjam Pressler Review: Halinka is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young girl named Halinka, who lives in a small village with her family. The book is suitable for children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old, as it contains relatable themes and engaging illustrations. The story is set in a time of war, and Halinka&amp;rsquo;s family is forced to flee their home in search of safety.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bridge to Terabithia</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/bridge_to_terabithia_isbn_9786051732077/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/bridge_to_terabithia_isbn_9786051732077/</guid>
      <description>Bridge to Terabithia Title: Bridge to Terabithia Author: Katherine Paterson Review: Bridge to Terabithia is a captivating and heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s novel written by Katherine Paterson. The story follows the lives of two young protagonists, Jess Aarons and Leslie Burke, as they embark on a journey of friendship, imagination, and self-discovery. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old. The themes and life lessons presented in the story are relatable and relevant to this age group, making it an excellent choice for young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Granny</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/granny_by_peter_hartling_isbn_905478118/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/granny_by_peter_hartling_isbn_905478118/</guid>
      <description>Granny by Peter Hartling Title: Granny Author: Peter Hartling Review: Granny, written by Peter Hartling, is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that captures the heart of its young readers with its simple yet profound message. The story revolves around a young boy named Tommy, who lives with his grandmother, Granny, in a small village. Granny is the heart and soul of the village, always ready to help anyone in need with her kindness and wisdom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stig of the Dump</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/stig_of_the_dump_isbn_754065766/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/stig_of_the_dump_isbn_754065766/</guid>
      <description>Stig of the Dump Title: Stig of the Dump Author: Clive King Target Age Group: 7-12 years old Stig of the Dump is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Clive King, which tells the story of a young boy named Barney who discovers a caveman named Stig living in a nearby dump. The book takes readers on a delightful adventure as Barney and Stig form a unique friendship, teaching valuable life lessons along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Adventures of Rupert the Toad</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_adventures_of_rupert_the_toad_by_roy_berocay_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_adventures_of_rupert_the_toad_by_roy_berocay_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Adventures of Rupert the Toad by Roy Berocay Title: The Adventures of Rupert the Toad Author: Roy Berocay Review: The Adventures of Rupert the Toad is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the journey of a young toad named Rupert. Author Roy Berocay has skillfully crafted a story that is not only entertaining but also teaches valuable life lessons to young readers. The book is suitable for children aged 4-8 years old, as it features simple language and engaging illustrations that capture the imagination of young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lucky Luke-Arizona 1880</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/lucky_luke-arizona_1880_by_morris_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/lucky_luke-arizona_1880_by_morris_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Lucky Luke-Arizona 1880 by Morris Title: Lucky Luke: Arizona 1880 Author: Morris Review: Lucky Luke: Arizona 1880 is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Morris, which tells the story of a cowboy named Lucky Luke who embarks on a thrilling adventure in the Wild West. The book is filled with colorful illustrations and engaging dialogue that captures the attention of young readers. The story takes place in Arizona in the year 1880, where Lucky Luke, known for his quick wit and sharpshooting skills, finds himself in the middle of a conflict between a group of bandits and the local townspeople.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Princess Who Had Magic Fingers</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_princess_who_had_magic_fingers_by_maria_luisa_gefaell_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_princess_who_had_magic_fingers_by_maria_luisa_gefaell_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Princess Who Had Magic Fingers by Maria Luisa Gefaell Title: The Princess Who Had Magic Fingers Author: Maria Luisa Gefaell The Princess Who Had Magic Fingers is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Maria Luisa Gefaell. This enchanting story is perfect for children aged 4-8 years old, as it features captivating illustrations and a simple yet engaging narrative. The story follows a young princess who discovers that she has magical fingers that can create beautiful art.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nobody&#39;s Boy</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/nobodys_boy_by_hector_malot_isbn_161104409x/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/nobodys_boy_by_hector_malot_isbn_161104409x/</guid>
      <description>Nobody&amp;rsquo;s Boy by Hector Malot Title: Nobody&amp;rsquo;s Boy Author: Hector Malot Review: Nobody&amp;rsquo;s Boy, written by Hector Malot, is a heartwarming and engaging children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of Remi, an orphan boy who embarks on a journey of self-discovery and resilience. The book is suitable for children between the ages of 8 and 12, and is a perfect read for both independent readers and as a bedtime story. The story follows Remi, who is taken in by a kind-hearted farmer named Capi after being abandoned by his birth mother.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snip Snap</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/snip_snap_by_mara_bergman_isbn_9780060777548/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/snip_snap_by_mara_bergman_isbn_9780060777548/</guid>
      <description>Snip Snap by Mara Bergman Title: Snip Snap Author: Mara Bergman Snip Snap is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Mara Bergman, which takes young readers on a magical adventure through the world of whimsical creatures. The book is filled with vibrant illustrations by the talented Nick Maland, which adds to the overall charm of the story. Target Age Group: Snip Snap is best suited for children between the ages of 4 to 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Horrid Henry Series</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/horrid_henry_series_by_francesca_simon_isbn_9781484001868/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/horrid_henry_series_by_francesca_simon_isbn_9781484001868/</guid>
      <description>Horrid Henry Series by Francesca Simon Title: Horrid Henry Series Author: Francesca Simon Review: The Horrid Henry Series, written by Francesca Simon, is a delightful collection of children&amp;rsquo;s books that follow the mischievous adventures of the titular character, Horrid Henry. The series is a perfect fit for young readers between the ages of 5 and 10 years old, as it captures their attention with its engaging storytelling and colorful illustrations. The books in the series are filled with funny, relatable, and sometimes outrageous situations that Horrid Henry finds himself in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Polar Express</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_polar_express_isbn_9781783446827/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_polar_express_isbn_9781783446827/</guid>
      <description>The Polar Express Title: The Polar Express Author: Chris Van Allsburg Review: The Polar Express is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Chris Van Allsburg, which tells the story of a young boy who embarks on a magical journey to the North Pole on Christmas Eve. The story is beautifully illustrated with captivating images that bring the enchanting world of the Polar Express to life. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Real Thief</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_real_thief_by_william_steig_isbn_1782691456/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_real_thief_by_william_steig_isbn_1782691456/</guid>
      <description>The Real Thief by William Steig Title: The Real Thief Author: William Steig Target Age Group: 5-10 years old The Real Thief is a beautifully illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book by William Steig, which tells the story of a young mouse named Pearl who is accused of stealing a cherished diamond ring. The book explores themes of friendship, trust, and honesty, making it a perfect read for children between the ages of 5 and 10 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sleep Well, Little Bear</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/sleep_well_little_bear_by_quint_buckholz_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/sleep_well_little_bear_by_quint_buckholz_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Sleep Well, Little Bear by Quint Buckholz Title: Sleep Well, Little Bear Author: Quint Buckholz Sleep Well, Little Bear is a beautifully illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young bear named Little Bear who is having trouble sleeping. The book is written by Quint Buckholz and is perfect for children between the ages of 3 to 8 years old. The story begins with Little Bear feeling restless and unable to sleep.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winnie the Witch</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/winnie_the_witch_by_valerie_thomas_isbn_192790846/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/winnie_the_witch_by_valerie_thomas_isbn_192790846/</guid>
      <description>Winnie the Witch by Valerie Thomas Title: Winnie the Witch Author: Valerie Thomas Winnie the Witch is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Valerie Thomas and illustrated by Korky Paul. This book is perfect for children aged 4-8 years old and tells the story of a friendly witch named Winnie and her cat Wilbur. The story follows Winnie as she tries to find a way to control her messy house. With the help of her magical powers, she creates a spell to clean up her house.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peter in Blueberry Land</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/peter_in_blueberry_land_by_elsa_beskow_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/peter_in_blueberry_land_by_elsa_beskow_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Peter in Blueberry Land by Elsa Beskow Title: Peter in Blueberry Land Author: Elsa Beskow Review: &amp;ldquo;Peter in Blueberry Land&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book by the renowned Swedish author and illustrator, Elsa Beskow. The story follows Peter, a young boy who embarks on a magical adventure in a land filled with talking blueberries and other enchanting creatures. This charming book is perfect for children aged 4 to 8 years old, as it captivates their imaginations and teaches them valuable life lessons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Quangle Wangle&#39;s Hat</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_quangle_wangles_hat_by_edward_lear_isbn_9780749713362/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_quangle_wangles_hat_by_edward_lear_isbn_9780749713362/</guid>
      <description>The Quangle Wangle&amp;rsquo;s Hat by Edward Lear Title: The Quangle Wangle&amp;rsquo;s Hat Author: Edward Lear &amp;ldquo;The Quangle Wangle&amp;rsquo;s Hat&amp;rdquo; is a whimsical and imaginative children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Edward Lear, an English artist, illustrator, and writer. This book is a delightful read for children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old. The story follows the adventures of the Quangle Wangle, a curious and friendly creature, who wears a tall, elaborate hat.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
