<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Childrens Books that talk about &#39;Smile&#39; on Monsty The Monster Truck</title>
    <link>https://www.monsty.co/tags/childrens-books-that-talk-about-smile/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Childrens Books that talk about &#39;Smile&#39; on Monsty The Monster Truck</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.monsty.co/tags/childrens-books-that-talk-about-smile/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Flambards</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/flambards_by_km_peyton_isbn_192739328/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/flambards_by_km_peyton_isbn_192739328/</guid>
      <description>Flambards by KM Peyton Title: Flambards Author: KM Peyton Review: Flambards is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by KM Peyton, which tells the story of a young girl named Christina, who goes to live with her cousins in a large country house called Flambards. The book is a perfect blend of adventure, friendship, and self-discovery, making it an ideal read for children aged 8-12 years. The story follows Christina as she navigates the complex relationships within her family, learns to ride horses, and ultimately finds her place in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Canterville Ghost</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_canterville_ghost_isbn_9783842451155/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_canterville_ghost_isbn_9783842451155/</guid>
      <description>The Canterville Ghost Title: The Canterville Ghost Author: Oscar Wilde Review: The Canterville Ghost is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the renowned author Oscar Wilde. The story revolves around a family who moves into an old castle haunted by a ghost, Sir Simon. The ghost tries to scare the family away but to his surprise, they are not afraid of him. Instead, they try to help him and understand his story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lost and Found</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/lost_and_found_by_oliver_jeffers_isbn_7240376/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/lost_and_found_by_oliver_jeffers_isbn_7240376/</guid>
      <description>Lost and Found by Oliver Jeffers Title: Lost and Found Author: Oliver Jeffers Review: Lost and Found, written and illustrated by Oliver Jeffers, is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young boy who finds a lost penguin at his doorstep. The boy embarks on a journey to return the penguin to its home in the South Pole. This beautifully illustrated book is suitable for children aged 4-8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
