<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Childrens Books that talk about &#39;Growing Up&#39; on Monsty The Monster Truck</title>
    <link>https://www.monsty.co/tags/childrens-books-that-talk-about-growing-up/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Childrens Books that talk about &#39;Growing Up&#39; on Monsty The Monster Truck</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.monsty.co/tags/childrens-books-that-talk-about-growing-up/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>By the River</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/by_the_river_by_steven_herrick_isbn_9781741143577/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/by_the_river_by_steven_herrick_isbn_9781741143577/</guid>
      <description>By the River by Steven Herrick Title: By the River Author: Steven Herrick Review: By the River is a beautifully written children&amp;rsquo;s book by Steven Herrick that captures the essence of childhood innocence and the importance of friendship. The book is perfect for children aged 8-12, as it is both engaging and thought-provoking. The story follows the life of Ben, a young boy who spends his days by the river, observing the world around him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deadly, Unna?</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/deadly_unna_by_phillip_gwynne_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/deadly_unna_by_phillip_gwynne_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Deadly, Unna? by Phillip Gwynne Title: Deadly, Unna? Author: Phillip Gwynne Review: Deadly, Unna? is a captivating and thought-provoking children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Phillip Gwynne. The story follows the life of a young boy named Gary Black, who is a member of the Australian football team. Gary&amp;rsquo;s life takes an unexpected turn when he befriends a young indigenous girl named Nunga, who teaches him about her culture and the struggles her community faces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finding Violet Park</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/finding_violet_park_by_jenny_valentine_isbn_7291248/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/finding_violet_park_by_jenny_valentine_isbn_7291248/</guid>
      <description>Finding Violet Park by Jenny Valentine Title: Finding Violet Park Author: Jenny Valentine Review: Finding Violet Park is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Jenny Valentine, which tells the story of a young boy named Lucas who embarks on a journey to find the mysterious Violet Park. The book is suitable for children aged 8-12 years old, as it contains elements of adventure, mystery, and self-discovery. The story follows Lucas as he navigates through various challenges and obstacles in his quest to find Violet Park.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Four Sisters</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/four_sisters_by_malika_ferdjoukh_isbn_1684051967/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/four_sisters_by_malika_ferdjoukh_isbn_1684051967/</guid>
      <description>Four Sisters by Malika Ferdjoukh Title: Four Sisters Author: Malika Ferdjoukh Review: Four Sisters is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Malika Ferdjoukh, which beautifully captures the essence of sisterhood, friendship, and the importance of embracing one&amp;rsquo;s unique qualities. The story revolves around four sisters, each with their own distinct personality and talent, who learn to support and celebrate each other&amp;rsquo;s differences. The book is targeted towards children aged 5 to 10 years old, as it features simple yet engaging illustrations and a heartwarming storyline that will resonate with young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Am Not Esther</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/i_am_not_esther_by_fleur_beale_isbn_9781864470598/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/i_am_not_esther_by_fleur_beale_isbn_9781864470598/</guid>
      <description>I Am Not Esther by Fleur Beale Title: I Am Not Esther Author: Fleur Beale Review: I Am Not Esther is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Fleur Beale, which tells the story of a young girl named Kirby who is forced to live with her estranged relatives after her mother&amp;rsquo;s sudden death. The book primarily targets children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old, as it explores themes of family, friendship, and self-discovery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keeper</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/keeper_by_mal_peet_isbn_9781406328066/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/keeper_by_mal_peet_isbn_9781406328066/</guid>
      <description>Keeper by Mal Peet Title: Keeper Author: Mal Peet Review: Keeper is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Mal Peet, which takes the reader on a thrilling journey through the world of soccer. The story follows the life of Elvis, a young boy who dreams of becoming a professional soccer player, and his encounter with the mysterious Keeper, who teaches him valuable life lessons. The book is targeted towards children aged 8-12 years old, as it explores themes such as perseverance, teamwork, and the importance of following one&amp;rsquo;s dreams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Noughts and Crosses</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/noughts_and_crosses_isbn_836932692/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/noughts_and_crosses_isbn_836932692/</guid>
      <description>Noughts and Crosses Title: Noughts and Crosses Author: Malorie Blackman Target Age Group: 10-14 years old Noughts and Crosses is a captivating novel by Malorie Blackman that takes readers on a thrilling journey through a world where racism and prejudice are reversed. The story follows the lives of two teenagers, Callum and Sephy, who come from different backgrounds and are faced with challenges in their friendship as they grow up in a society divided by race.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oh, Boy!</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/oh_boy_by_marie-aude_murail_isbn_811847624/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/oh_boy_by_marie-aude_murail_isbn_811847624/</guid>
      <description>Oh, Boy! by Marie-Aude Murail Title: Oh, Boy! Author: Marie-Aude Murail Review: Oh, Boy! is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that captures the essence of growing up and learning to navigate the complexities of life. The story follows the journey of a young boy named Nicolas as he navigates through the ups and downs of life, all while trying to find his place in the world. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Out of the Dust</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/out_of_the_dust_isbn_1845078357/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/out_of_the_dust_isbn_1845078357/</guid>
      <description>Out of the Dust Title: Out of the Dust Author: Karen Hesse Review: Out of the Dust is a poignant and powerful children&amp;rsquo;s novel that captures the heart and soul of its readers. Author Karen Hesse has skillfully crafted a story that is both touching and thought-provoking, making it a must-read for young readers. The book is set in the 1930s during the Great Depression and the Dust Bowl, and follows the life of a young girl named Billie Jo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parvana&#39;s Journey</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/parvanas_journey_by_deborah_ellis_isbn_9781459664760/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/parvanas_journey_by_deborah_ellis_isbn_9781459664760/</guid>
      <description>Parvana&amp;rsquo;s Journey by Deborah Ellis Title: Parvana&amp;rsquo;s Journey Author: Deborah Ellis Review: Parvana&amp;rsquo;s Journey is a compelling and thought-provoking children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Deborah Ellis. The story follows the life of a young girl named Parvana, who embarks on a journey to find her family amidst the turmoil of war-torn Afghanistan. The book is suitable for children aged 10 and above, as it tackles mature themes such as war, loss, and resilience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peeling the Onion</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/peeling_the_onion_by_wendy_orr_isbn_9781741149333/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/peeling_the_onion_by_wendy_orr_isbn_9781741149333/</guid>
      <description>Peeling the Onion by Wendy Orr Title: Peeling the Onion Author: Wendy Orr Review: Peeling the Onion is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Wendy Orr, which takes the reader on a journey of self-discovery and friendship. The story revolves around a young girl named Mia, who struggles with the challenges of growing up and finding her place in the world. Target Age Group: The book is suitable for children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Postcards From No Man&#39;s Land</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/postcards_from_no_mans_land_isbn_525468633/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/postcards_from_no_mans_land_isbn_525468633/</guid>
      <description>Postcards From No Man&amp;rsquo;s Land Title: Postcards From No Man&amp;rsquo;s Land Author: Aidan Chambers Target Age Group: 10-14 years old Review: Postcards From No Man&amp;rsquo;s Land is a captivating and thought-provoking book that delves into the complexities of life, relationships, and personal growth. Aidan Chambers has masterfully crafted a story that resonates with readers of all ages, but particularly with the 10-14 age group. The book follows the journey of Jacob, a young boy who embarks on a trip to Amsterdam with his mother and her new partner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Private Peaceful</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/private_peaceful_isbn_786289465/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/private_peaceful_isbn_786289465/</guid>
      <description>Private Peaceful Title: Private Peaceful Author: Michael Morpurgo Age Group: 9-12 years old Private Peaceful is a heart-warming and poignant children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Michael Morpurgo. The story follows the life of a young boy named Thomas &amp;ldquo;Tommo&amp;rdquo; Peaceful, who grows up in a loving family in a small village during the early 1900s. As the narrative unfolds, we witness the challenges and experiences that shape Tommo&amp;rsquo;s life, including the tragic events of World War I.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Curious Incident of the Dog in the Night-Time – Mark Haddon</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_curious_incident_of_the_dog_in_the_night-time__mark_haddon_isbn_521613795/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_curious_incident_of_the_dog_in_the_night-time__mark_haddon_isbn_521613795/</guid>
      <description>The Curious Incident of the Dog in the Night-Time – Mark Haddon Title: The Curious Incident of the Dog in the Night-Time Author: Mark Haddon Age Group: 12 years and above &amp;ldquo;The Curious Incident of the Dog in the Night-Time&amp;rdquo; is a captivating and thought-provoking novel that tells the story of Christopher Boone, a 15-year-old boy with Asperger&amp;rsquo;s Syndrome. The book takes the reader on a journey through Christopher&amp;rsquo;s unique perspective as he navigates the complexities of everyday life and solves the mystery of a murdered dog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Illustrated Mum</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_illustrated_mum_isbn_9780385902632/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_illustrated_mum_isbn_9780385902632/</guid>
      <description>The Illustrated Mum Title: The Illustrated Mum Author: Jacqueline Wilson Review: The Illustrated Mum is a heartwarming and poignant children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of two sisters, Dolphin and Star, who navigate the challenges of growing up with a mother suffering from mental illness. The book is beautifully illustrated and the artwork complements the emotional depth of the story. The target age group for this book is children between the ages of 8 and 12.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thursday&#39;s Child</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/thursdays_child_by_sonya_hartnett_isbn_1536206431/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/thursdays_child_by_sonya_hartnett_isbn_1536206431/</guid>
      <description>Thursday&amp;rsquo;s Child by Sonya Hartnett Title: Thursday&amp;rsquo;s Child Author: Sonya Hartnett Review: Thursday&amp;rsquo;s Child is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the talented Sonya Hartnett. This beautifully crafted story follows the life of a young boy named Harper Flute, who lives in a small, close-knit community during the Great Depression. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 8 and 12, making it an excellent choice for elementary school students.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Walking Naked</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/walking_naked_by_alyssa_brugman_isbn_385901410/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/walking_naked_by_alyssa_brugman_isbn_385901410/</guid>
      <description>Walking Naked by Alyssa Brugman Title: Walking Naked Author: Alyssa Brugman Review: Walking Naked is a beautifully written children&amp;rsquo;s book by Alyssa Brugman, which is suitable for children between the ages of 8 and 12. The story follows the life of a young girl named Nina, who is trying to find her place in the world and navigate the challenges of growing up. The book tackles various life lessons, such as the importance of self-acceptance, empathy, and resilience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alex</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/alex_by_tessa_duder_isbn_9780195581690/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/alex_by_tessa_duder_isbn_9780195581690/</guid>
      <description>Alex by Tessa Duder Title: Alex Author: Tessa Duder Review: &amp;ldquo;Alex&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Tessa Duder, which follows the adventures of a young girl named Alex as she navigates the challenges of growing up. The book is a perfect fit for children between the ages of 8 and 12, as it addresses themes that are relatable to this age group, such as friendship, self-discovery, and overcoming obstacles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Caperucita En Manhattan</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/caperucita_en_manhattan_by_carmen_mart%C3%ADn_gaite_isbn_9788478442010/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/caperucita_en_manhattan_by_carmen_mart%C3%ADn_gaite_isbn_9788478442010/</guid>
      <description>Caperucita En Manhattan by Carmen Martín Gaite Title: Caperucita en Manhattan Author: Carmen Martín Gaite &amp;ldquo;Caperucita en Manhattan&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes the classic fairy tale of Little Red Riding Hood and gives it a modern twist. The story follows Caperucita, a young girl who lives in New York City, as she navigates the bustling streets of Manhattan. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 5 and 10 years old and teaches valuable life lessons along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dear Nobody</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/dear_nobody_isbn_531086119/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/dear_nobody_isbn_531086119/</guid>
      <description>Dear Nobody Title: Dear Nobody Author: Berlie Doherty Recommended Age Group: 8-12 years old Dear Nobody is a heartwarming and thought-provoking children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Berlie Doherty. The story revolves around two main characters, Helen and Chris, who are both dealing with the challenges of growing up and navigating their emotions. The book is written in a diary format, with Helen and Chris taking turns to share their thoughts and feelings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heart&#39;s Delight</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/hearts_delight_by_per_nilsson_isbn_9781886910928/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/hearts_delight_by_per_nilsson_isbn_9781886910928/</guid>
      <description>Heart&amp;rsquo;s Delight by Per Nilsson Title: Heart&amp;rsquo;s Delight Author: Per Nilsson Review: Heart&amp;rsquo;s Delight is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that captures the hearts of young readers with its charming story and beautiful illustrations. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 4 and 8, and it teaches valuable life lessons through its engaging narrative. The story revolves around a young girl named Elsa, who is given a special heart-shaped box by her grandmother.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Johnny, My Friend</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/johnny_my_friend_by_peter_pohl_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/johnny_my_friend_by_peter_pohl_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Johnny, My Friend by Peter Pohl Title: Johnny, My Friend Author: Peter Pohl Review: &amp;ldquo;Johnny, My Friend&amp;rdquo; is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Peter Pohl. The story follows the adventures of a young boy named Johnny and his best friend, a magical talking dog named Rover. Together, they embark on a series of exciting and imaginative adventures that teach valuable life lessons along the way. The book is beautifully illustrated, with vibrant and engaging pictures that capture the essence of each scene.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Looking for Alibrandi</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/looking_for_alibrandi_isbn_375936947/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/looking_for_alibrandi_isbn_375936947/</guid>
      <description>Looking for Alibrandi Title: Looking for Alibrandi Author: Melina Marchetta Target Age Group: 12-15 years old Looking for Alibrandi is a heartwarming and relatable coming-of-age story that captures the struggles and experiences of a young girl named Josephine Alibrandi. The book is written by Melina Marchetta and is a perfect read for children between the ages of 12 and 15 years old. The story follows Josephine, a teenage girl trying to find her place in the world as she navigates through the challenges of high school, family, and her Italian heritage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Memoirs of a Basque Cow</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/memoirs_of_a_basque_cow_by_bernardo_atxaga_isbn_9781912868018/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/memoirs_of_a_basque_cow_by_bernardo_atxaga_isbn_9781912868018/</guid>
      <description>Memoirs of a Basque Cow by Bernardo Atxaga Title: Memoirs of a Basque Cow Author: Bernardo Atxaga Genre: Children&amp;rsquo;s Literature, Fiction Recommended Age Group: 8-12 years old Review: Memoirs of a Basque Cow by Bernardo Atxaga is a charming and heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a cow named Koki, who lives in the Basque Country. Through Koki&amp;rsquo;s eyes, the reader is introduced to a world of farm animals, human characters, and the ups and downs of life on a farm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pagan&#39;s Crusade</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/pagans_crusade_by_catherine_jinks_isbn_9780763625849/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/pagans_crusade_by_catherine_jinks_isbn_9780763625849/</guid>
      <description>Pagan&amp;rsquo;s Crusade by Catherine Jinks Title: Pagan&amp;rsquo;s Crusade Author: Catherine Jinks Pagan&amp;rsquo;s Crusade is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the talented author, Catherine Jinks. The story follows the adventures of a young boy named Pagan as he embarks on a thrilling crusade to rescue his kidnapped sister. The book is primarily targeted towards children aged 8-12 years old, as it contains elements of adventure, history, and fantasy that are likely to captivate young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Redwork</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/redwork_by_michael_bedard_isbn_886192765/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/redwork_by_michael_bedard_isbn_886192765/</guid>
      <description>Redwork by Michael Bedard Title: Redwork Author: Michael Bedard Redwork is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Michael Bedard, which takes readers on a journey through a young girl&amp;rsquo;s life, filled with mystery, intrigue, and valuable life lessons. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 8 and 12, making it a perfect addition to any elementary school library or classroom. The story revolves around a young girl named Clara, who is on a quest to uncover the truth about her mother&amp;rsquo;s mysterious past.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>See Ya, Simon</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/see_ya_simon_by_david_hill_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/see_ya_simon_by_david_hill_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>See Ya, Simon by David Hill Title: See Ya, Simon Author: David Hill Target Age Group: 8-12 years old &amp;ldquo;See Ya, Simon&amp;rdquo; is a heartwarming and engaging children&amp;rsquo;s book by David Hill that captures the attention of young readers with its relatable characters and themes. The story revolves around a young boy named Simon, who struggles with the challenges of growing up and navigating the complexities of friendships and relationships. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 8 and 12, as it addresses issues that are relevant to this age group, such as bullying, self-esteem, and the importance of communication.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stone Cold</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/stone_cold_by_robert_swindells_isbn_9780745173993/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/stone_cold_by_robert_swindells_isbn_9780745173993/</guid>
      <description>Stone Cold by Robert Swindells Title: Stone Cold Author: Robert Swindells Review: Stone Cold by Robert Swindells is a captivating and thought-provoking children&amp;rsquo;s book that explores the complex themes of homelessness, family dynamics, and the power of friendship. The story follows the life of a young boy named Link, who finds himself homeless after his father&amp;rsquo;s death and his mother&amp;rsquo;s inability to cope. The book is well-written and engaging, making it an excellent choice for children aged 10-14.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tomorrow, When the War Began</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/tomorrow_when_the_war_began_by_john_marsden_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/tomorrow_when_the_war_began_by_john_marsden_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Tomorrow, When the War Began by John Marsden Title: Tomorrow, When the War Began Author: John Marsden Review: Tomorrow, When the War Began is a gripping novel written by John Marsden, which takes the readers on an adventurous journey through the eyes of a group of teenagers. The book is a perfect blend of action, suspense, and emotional depth, making it an ideal read for young adults. The story revolves around a group of seven friends who embark on a camping trip to a remote area, only to return and find their hometown occupied by a foreign military force.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Walk Two Moons</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/walk_two_moons_isbn_9780590649438/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/walk_two_moons_isbn_9780590649438/</guid>
      <description>Walk Two Moons Title: Walk Two Moons Author: Sharon Creech Review: Walk Two Moons is a beautifully written children&amp;rsquo;s novel by Sharon Creech, which tells the story of a young girl named Salamanca Tree Hiddle, who embarks on a journey to find her missing mother. The book is an engaging and thought-provoking read that explores themes of family, friendship, and the power of storytelling. Target Age Group: The book is suitable for children aged 9-12 years old, as it contains relatable themes and characters that resonate well with this age group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When the World Was Still Young</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/when_the_world_was_still_young_by_jurg_schubiger_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/when_the_world_was_still_young_by_jurg_schubiger_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>When the World Was Still Young by Jurg Schubiger Title: When the World Was Still Young Author: Jurg Schubiger Review: When the World Was Still Young is a beautifully illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young boy named Jonas who embarks on a magical adventure. The book is suitable for children between the ages of 6 and 10 years old. The story follows Jonas as he discovers a hidden door in his grandfather&amp;rsquo;s attic, which leads him to a world where time has stopped.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Kestrel for a Knave</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/a_kestrel_for_a_knave_isbn_1858481465/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/a_kestrel_for_a_knave_isbn_1858481465/</guid>
      <description>A Kestrel for a Knave Title: A Kestrel for a Knave Author: Barry Hines Recommended Age Group: 10-14 years old A Kestrel for a Knave is a captivating and thought-provoking novel by Barry Hines, which tells the story of Billy Casper, a young boy from a working-class family in a small English town. The book is a perfect blend of emotions, struggles, and triumphs, making it an excellent read for children between the ages of 10 and 14.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Long Way From Verona</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/a_long_way_from_verona_by_jane_gardam_isbn_349114056/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/a_long_way_from_verona_by_jane_gardam_isbn_349114056/</guid>
      <description>A Long Way From Verona by Jane Gardam Title: A Long Way From Verona Author: Jane Gardam Review: A Long Way From Verona is a delightful and thought-provoking children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Jane Gardam. The story follows the life of a young girl named Betty Carpenter, who is growing up in a small village during World War II. The book is an engaging read for children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old, as it covers themes such as friendship, family, and resilience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Across the Barricades</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/across_the_barricades_by_joan_lindgard_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/across_the_barricades_by_joan_lindgard_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Across the Barricades by Joan Lindgard Title: Across the Barricades Author: Joan Lindgard Review: Across the Barricades is a heartwarming and thought-provoking children&amp;rsquo;s book that explores the themes of friendship, overcoming differences, and the power of understanding. The story follows two young characters, Sadie and Kevin, who live on opposite sides of a barricade that divides their town. Sadie&amp;rsquo;s family is part of the wealthy and privileged community, while Kevin&amp;rsquo;s family struggles to make ends meet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bilgewater</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/bilgewater_by_jane_gardam_isbn_688801080/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/bilgewater_by_jane_gardam_isbn_688801080/</guid>
      <description>Bilgewater by Jane Gardam Title: Bilgewater Author: Jane Gardam Review: Bilgewater is a charming and engaging children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes readers on a journey through the life of Marigold Green, a young girl growing up in a small English seaside town. Author Jane Gardam has crafted a beautifully written story that is both heartwarming and thought-provoking. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 8 and 12, and it covers a range of important life lessons, such as the importance of family, friendship, and perseverance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hey, Dollface</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/hey_dollface_by_deborah_hautzig_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/hey_dollface_by_deborah_hautzig_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Hey, Dollface by Deborah Hautzig Title: Hey, Dollface Author: Deborah Hautzig Review: Hey, Dollface is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Deborah Hautzig. The story revolves around a young girl named Dollface, who is struggling to find her identity and place in the world. Throughout the book, Dollface encounters various challenges and experiences that help her grow and learn valuable life lessons. Target Age Group: Hey, Dollface is primarily targeted towards children between the ages of 8 and 12.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Homecoming</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/homecoming_isbn_9780413413307/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/homecoming_isbn_9780413413307/</guid>
      <description>Homecoming Title: Homecoming Author: K.A. Applegate Review: Homecoming is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the journey of a young girl named Lily, who discovers the importance of family, friendship, and finding one&amp;rsquo;s true home. The story is filled with beautiful illustrations and captivating characters that will keep young readers engaged from start to finish. Target Age Group: Homecoming is suitable for children between the ages of 7 and 10. The book&amp;rsquo;s themes and language are appropriate for this age range, and the story provides valuable life lessons that children can relate to and learn from.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;m the King of the Castle</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/im_the_king_of_the_castle_by_susan_hill_isbn_9780141041940/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/im_the_king_of_the_castle_by_susan_hill_isbn_9780141041940/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m the King of the Castle by Susan Hill Title: I&amp;rsquo;m the King of the Castle Author: Susan Hill Review: &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m the King of the Castle&amp;rdquo; is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Susan Hill, which takes readers on a thrilling journey through the lives of two young boys, Joseph Hooper and Edmund Hooper. The story is set in the 1950s and is centered around themes of friendship, power dynamics, and the complexities of human relationships.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MC Higgins</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/mc_higgins_by_virginia_hamilton_isbn_068971694x/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/mc_higgins_by_virginia_hamilton_isbn_068971694x/</guid>
      <description>MC Higgins by Virginia Hamilton Title: MC Higgins Author: Virginia Hamilton Review: MC Higgins is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Virginia Hamilton, which takes the readers on a journey through the life of a young boy named Mayo Cornelius Higgins. The story is set in the Appalachian Mountains and portrays the challenges faced by the protagonist as he grows up in a poverty-stricken community. The book is targeted towards children aged 8-12 years old, as it deals with themes of friendship, family, and resilience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nobody&#39;s Family Is Going to Change</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/nobodys_family_is_going_to_change_by_louise_fitzhugh_isbn_333294505/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/nobodys_family_is_going_to_change_by_louise_fitzhugh_isbn_333294505/</guid>
      <description>Nobody&amp;rsquo;s Family Is Going to Change by Louise Fitzhugh Title: Nobody&amp;rsquo;s Family Is Going to Change Author: Louise Fitzhugh Review: &amp;ldquo;Nobody&amp;rsquo;s Family Is Going to Change&amp;rdquo; is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Louise Fitzhugh, which tells the story of a young boy named Tommy who is trying to find his place in the world. The book is perfect for children aged 8-12 years old, as it deals with themes of self-discovery, family dynamics, and acceptance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roll of Thunder, Hear My Cry</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/roll_of_thunder_hear_my_cry_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/roll_of_thunder_hear_my_cry_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Roll of Thunder, Hear My Cry Title: Roll of Thunder, Hear My Cry Author: Mildred D. Taylor Age Group: 10-14 years old Roll of Thunder, Hear My Cry is a captivating novel by Mildred D. Taylor that tells the story of a young African American girl named Cassie Logan, who lives with her family in Mississippi during the 1930s. The book offers a unique perspective on the challenges faced by African Americans during the Great Depression and the Jim Crow era.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sounder</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/sounder_isbn_575006536/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/sounder_isbn_575006536/</guid>
      <description>Sounder Title: Sounder Author: William H. Armstrong Review: Sounder is a heartwarming and thought-provoking children&amp;rsquo;s book written by William H. Armstrong. The story is set in the rural South during the early 1900s and follows the life of a young African American boy named David and his loyal dog, Sounder. The book primarily targets children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old. It is a great read for this age group as it touches upon themes of family, friendship, and perseverance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Chocolate War</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_chocolate_war_by_robert_cormier_isbn_9781400089963/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_chocolate_war_by_robert_cormier_isbn_9781400089963/</guid>
      <description>The Chocolate War by Robert Cormier Title: The Chocolate War Author: Robert Cormier Genre: Young Adult Fiction, Coming-of-Age Novel Recommended Age Group: 12-18 years old The Chocolate War, written by Robert Cormier, is a gripping and thought-provoking coming-of-age novel that delves into the complexities of adolescent life. This book is a must-read for young adults aged 12-18, as it addresses themes of individuality, conformity, and the consequences of standing up for one&amp;rsquo;s beliefs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Friends</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_friends_by_rosa_guy_isbn_9780808554028/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_friends_by_rosa_guy_isbn_9780808554028/</guid>
      <description>The Friends by Rosa Guy Title: The Friends Author: Rosa Guy Review: The Friends is a heartwarming and thought-provoking children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Rosa Guy. This book is a perfect fit for children aged 8-12 years old, as it delves into themes of friendship, understanding, and acceptance. The story revolves around two young girls, Phyllisia and Celie, who come from different cultural backgrounds but develop a strong bond of friendship. Throughout the book, the author beautifully portrays the importance of embracing diversity and understanding the experiences of others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Island on Bird Street</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_island_on_bird_street_by_uri_orlev_isbn_9780091595807/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_island_on_bird_street_by_uri_orlev_isbn_9780091595807/</guid>
      <description>The Island on Bird Street by Uri Orlev Title: The Island on Bird Street Author: Uri Orlev Review: The Island on Bird Street is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Uri Orlev, which takes readers on a heartwarming journey through the eyes of a young boy named Alex. The story is set during World War II, where Alex and his family are forced to live in a ghetto due to their Jewish heritage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Peppermint Pig</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_peppermint_pig_by_nina_bawden_isbn_9780582186897/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_peppermint_pig_by_nina_bawden_isbn_9780582186897/</guid>
      <description>The Peppermint Pig by Nina Bawden Title: The Peppermint Pig Author: Nina Bawden Review: The Peppermint Pig is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Nina Bawden. The story follows the adventures of a family of mice, who live in a dollhouse, as they try to help their youngest member, Timothy, who is suffering from pneumonia. To save Timothy, the family decides to make a peppermint pig, a traditional English good luck charm, in the hopes that it will bring them good fortune and help Timothy recover.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Village by the Sea</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_village_isbn_1075176603/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_village_isbn_1075176603/</guid>
      <description>The Village Title: The Village Author: Jane Smith Review: The Village is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young boy named Timmy who lives in a small, close-knit village. The book is beautifully illustrated and written in a way that is easy for young readers to understand and enjoy. Target Age Group: The Village is suitable for children between the ages of 5 and 10. The story is engaging and relatable for this age group, as it teaches valuable life lessons while also being entertaining.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twopence a Tub</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/twopence_a_tub_by_susan_price_isbn_9780571106240/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/twopence_a_tub_by_susan_price_isbn_9780571106240/</guid>
      <description>Twopence a Tub by Susan Price Title: Twopence a Tub Author: Susan Price Review: Twopence a Tub is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Susan Price, which takes readers on a captivating journey through the life of a young boy named Joe. The story is set in the early 1900s and revolves around Joe&amp;rsquo;s family, who work as washerwomen, washing clothes for wealthy people. The book targets children between the ages of 8 to 12 years old, as it contains a perfect blend of adventure, emotion, and historical context.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where the Lilies Bloom</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/where_the_lilies_bloom_isbn_881032913/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/where_the_lilies_bloom_isbn_881032913/</guid>
      <description>Where the Lilies Bloom Title: Where the Lilies Bloom Author: Vera Cleaver and Bill Cleaver Review: &amp;ldquo;Where the Lilies Bloom&amp;rdquo; is a heartwarming and inspiring children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a family living in the Appalachian Mountains. The story follows the lives of Mary Call, her siblings, and their struggle to survive after their father&amp;rsquo;s death. The book is suitable for children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adventures of the Ingenious Alfanhui</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/adventures_of_the_ingenious_alfanhui_by_rafael_sanchez_ferlosio_isbn_1873982593/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/adventures_of_the_ingenious_alfanhui_by_rafael_sanchez_ferlosio_isbn_1873982593/</guid>
      <description>Adventures of the Ingenious Alfanhui by Rafael Sanchez Ferlosio Title: Adventures of the Ingenious Alfanhui Author: Rafael Sanchez Ferlosio Review: Adventures of the Ingenious Alfanhui is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes readers on a whimsical journey through the eyes of its young protagonist, Alfanhui. This book is a perfect choice for children between the ages of 8 and 12, as it is filled with engaging adventures, captivating illustrations, and valuable life lessons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Caddie Woodlawn</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/caddie_woodlawn_isbn_20418809/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/caddie_woodlawn_isbn_20418809/</guid>
      <description>Caddie Woodlawn Title: Caddie Woodlawn Author: Carol Ryrie Brink Genre: Children&amp;rsquo;s Historical Fiction Recommended Age Group: 8-12 years old Caddie Woodlawn is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s historical fiction novel that tells the story of an eleven-year-old girl named Caddie, who lives with her family in the Wisconsin frontier in the mid-1800s. The book is filled with adventure, humor, and valuable life lessons that make it a must-read for young readers. The story follows Caddie as she navigates the challenges of growing up, including learning to be independent, standing up for what is right, and understanding the importance of family and friendship.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emily Climbs</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/emily_climbs_isbn_1844089894/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/emily_climbs_isbn_1844089894/</guid>
      <description>Emily Climbs Title: Emily Climbs Author: L.M. Montgomery Emily Climbs is the second book in the Emily series by L.M. Montgomery, following the story of a young orphan girl named Emily Starr. The book is set in the early 20th century and takes place in the fictional town of New Moon, where Emily lives with her strict and traditional relatives. The story follows Emily&amp;rsquo;s journey as she navigates her way through adolescence, her passion for writing, and the challenges of growing up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Friedrich</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/friedrich_by_hans-peter_richter_isbn_9782010141591/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/friedrich_by_hans-peter_richter_isbn_9782010141591/</guid>
      <description>Friedrich by Hans-Peter Richter Title: Friedrich Author: Hans-Peter Richter Friedrich is a beautifully written children&amp;rsquo;s book by Hans-Peter Richter that tells the story of a young boy named Friedrich who is growing up in Germany during World War II. The book is suitable for children aged 9-12 years old and is an excellent choice for parents and educators looking to introduce historical events and important life lessons to their young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Capture the Castle</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/i_capture_the_castle_by_dodie_smith_isbn_8379430069/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/i_capture_the_castle_by_dodie_smith_isbn_8379430069/</guid>
      <description>I Capture the Castle by Dodie Smith Title: I Capture the Castle Author: Dodie Smith Review: I Capture the Castle is a charming and delightful novel that captures the essence of childhood and the complexities of growing up. The story follows the adventures of Cassandra Mortmain, a young girl living in a crumbling castle with her family. As Cassandra navigates the ups and downs of life, she learns valuable lessons about love, friendship, and the importance of staying true to oneself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pastures of the Blue Crane</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/pastures_of_the_blue_crane_by_hf_brinsmead_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/pastures_of_the_blue_crane_by_hf_brinsmead_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Pastures of the Blue Crane by HF Brinsmead Title: Pastures of the Blue Crane Author: HF Brinsmead Review: Pastures of the Blue Crane is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by HF Brinsmead. The story follows the life of a young boy named Jimmie who moves with his family to a new town in the Australian countryside. As Jimmie adjusts to his new surroundings, he befriends a local Aboriginal boy named Andy and learns about their culture, traditions, and the importance of preserving the environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Catcher in the Rye</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_catcher_in_the_rye_by_j.d._salinger_isbn_9504000681/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_catcher_in_the_rye_by_j.d._salinger_isbn_9504000681/</guid>
      <description>The Catcher in the Rye by J.D. Salinger Title: The Catcher in the Rye Author: J.D. Salinger Review: The Catcher in the Rye is a classic coming-of-age novel written by J.D. Salinger. The story follows the life of a young teenager, Holden Caulfield, who struggles with the complexities of growing up and finding his place in the world. The book is targeted towards young adults, particularly those in their teenage years, who can relate to the challenges faced by the protagonist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Lion</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_lion_by_joseph_kessel_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_lion_by_joseph_kessel_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Lion by Joseph Kessel Title: The Lion Author: Joseph Kessel Review: The Lion is a beautifully written children&amp;rsquo;s book by Joseph Kessel, which takes the readers on a captivating journey through the African wilderness. The story revolves around a young lion named Luk, who learns valuable life lessons as he navigates the challenges of growing up in the wild. Target Age Group: The Lion is a perfect read for children between the ages of 6 and 10 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Min-Min</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_min-min_by_mavis_thorpe_clark_isbn_20422806/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_min-min_by_mavis_thorpe_clark_isbn_20422806/</guid>
      <description>The Min-Min by Mavis Thorpe Clark Title: The Min-Min Author: Mavis Thorpe Clark Review: The Min-Min is a charming and engaging children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young boy named Tim who befriends a mysterious creature called the Min-Min. Through their adventures together, Tim learns valuable life lessons about friendship, courage, and the importance of standing up for what is right. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 8 and 12, as it contains themes and lessons that are appropriate and relatable for this age group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Outsiders</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_outsiders_isbn_9780739339015/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_outsiders_isbn_9780739339015/</guid>
      <description>The Outsiders Title: The Outsiders Author: S.E. Hinton Review: The Outsiders is a classic coming-of-age novel written by S.E. Hinton, first published in 1967. The story is set in the 1960s and revolves around the lives of two rival gangs, the Greasers and the Socs, in Oklahoma. The narrative follows the experiences of Ponyboy Curtis, a young Greaser, as he navigates the challenges of growing up, dealing with the loss of loved ones, and questioning the societal divisions that exist between the two groups.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Pigman</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_pigman_isbn_553125796/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_pigman_isbn_553125796/</guid>
      <description>The Pigman Title: The Pigman Author: Paul Zindel Review: The Pigman is a captivating and heartfelt novel written by Paul Zindel, which tells the story of two high school students, John and Lorraine, who develop a unique friendship with an elderly man, Mr. Pignati. The story is set in the 1960s and delves into themes of loneliness, friendship, and the consequences of one&amp;rsquo;s actions. The book is targeted towards readers between the ages of 10 and 14, as it explores relatable themes and situations that young readers can connect with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The War of the Buttons</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_war_of_the_buttons_by_louis_pergaud_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_war_of_the_buttons_by_louis_pergaud_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The War of the Buttons by Louis Pergaud Title: The War of the Buttons Author: Louis Pergaud Genre: Children&amp;rsquo;s Fiction, Coming-of-Age Recommended Age Group: 8-12 years old The War of the Buttons, written by Louis Pergaud, is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes readers on a journey through the lives of two rival groups of young boys. The story is set in a small French village, where the boys from one village constantly engage in playful battles with the boys from another village.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To Kill a Mockingbird</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/to_kill_a_mockingbird_by_harper_lee_isbn_434012602/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/to_kill_a_mockingbird_by_harper_lee_isbn_434012602/</guid>
      <description>To Kill a Mockingbird by Harper Lee Title: To Kill a Mockingbird Author: Harper Lee Review: To Kill a Mockingbird, written by Harper Lee, is a captivating novel that tells the story of a young girl named Scout Finch and her brother Jem, growing up in the fictional town of Maycomb, Alabama during the 1930s. Through the eyes of these innocent children, the reader is exposed to the harsh realities of racism, prejudice, and injustice that were prevalent in the American South during that time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zazie in the Metro</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/zazie_in_the_metro_isbn_9780714538723/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/zazie_in_the_metro_isbn_9780714538723/</guid>
      <description>Zazie in the Metro Title: Zazie in the Metro Author: Raymond Queneau Recommended Age Group: 7-10 years old Zazie in the Metro is a charming and whimsical children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the adventures of Zazie, a young girl who gets lost in the Paris Metro system. The story is filled with humor, vivid descriptions, and engaging characters that will capture the imagination of young readers. The book is suitable for children aged 7-10 years old, as it features simple language and relatable themes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Barrumbi Kids</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/barrumbi_kids_by_leonie_norrington_isbn_9781862914964/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/barrumbi_kids_by_leonie_norrington_isbn_9781862914964/</guid>
      <description>Barrumbi Kids by Leonie Norrington Title: Barrumbi Kids Author: Leonie Norrington Review: Barrumbi Kids is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes young readers on an adventure through the Australian outback. The story follows the lives of four Indigenous children, each with their unique personalities and talents. Leonie Norrington has beautifully crafted a tale that not only entertains but also teaches valuable life lessons. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 7 and 12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eric, or Little by Little</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/eric_or_little_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/eric_or_little_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Eric, or Little Title: Eric, or Little Author: Sarah Grand Review: &amp;ldquo;Eric, or Little&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the adventures of a young boy named Eric, who is trying to find his place in the world. The story is filled with valuable life lessons and is perfect for children aged 6-10 years old. The book is set in a small village, where Eric lives with his family. He is a curious and imaginative child who often finds himself in trouble due to his mischievous nature.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Girragundji</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/my_girragundji_by_meme_mcdonald_and_boon_pryor_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/my_girragundji_by_meme_mcdonald_and_boon_pryor_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>My Girragundji by Meme Mcdonald and Boon Pryor Title: My Girragundji Author: Meme McDonald and Boon Pryor Review: My Girragundji is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young boy named Jake and his special bond with a pet fish named Girragundji. The book is beautifully illustrated, and the text is simple and engaging, making it perfect for children aged 4 to 8 years old. The story explores themes of friendship, loss, and the importance of cherishing the memories we create with our loved ones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seven Little Australians</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/seven_little_australians_isbn_9798595793711/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/seven_little_australians_isbn_9798595793711/</guid>
      <description>Seven Little Australians Title: Seven Little Australians Author: Ethel Turner Review: Seven Little Australians is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the adventures of the seven Woolcot siblings living in the late 19th century in Australia. The story is filled with fun, mischief, and a touch of drama that will keep young readers engaged and entertained. The book is suitable for children aged 8-12 years old, as it is easy to read and understand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Children of the New Forest</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_children_of_the_new_forest_isbn_158287395x/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_children_of_the_new_forest_isbn_158287395x/</guid>
      <description>The Children of the New Forest Title: The Children of the New Forest Author: Frederick Marryat Review: The Children of the New Forest is a captivating novel written by Frederick Marryat, originally published in 1847. This historical fiction story is set in the New Forest region of southern England during the English Civil War, and follows the lives of four orphaned children who must learn to survive and coexist in the wilderness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Composition</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_composition_isbn_9781305633858/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_composition_isbn_9781305633858/</guid>
      <description>The Composition Title: The Composition Author: Antonia Banyard Genre: Children&amp;rsquo;s Picture Book Target Age Group: 4-8 years old Review: &amp;ldquo;The Composition&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s picture book that tells the story of a young boy named Sam who is tasked with creating a picture for his school&amp;rsquo;s art competition. The book takes readers on a journey as Sam struggles to find inspiration for his artwork, eventually discovering that the beauty of nature can be found in the most unexpected places.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Day I Learned to Tame Spiders</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_day_i_learned_to_tame_spiders_by_jutta_richter_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_day_i_learned_to_tame_spiders_by_jutta_richter_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Day I Learned to Tame Spiders by Jutta Richter Title: The Day I Learned to Tame Spiders Author: Jutta Richter Review: The Day I Learned to Tame Spiders is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young girl named Lina, who learns to overcome her fear of spiders. The book is written by Jutta Richter, who has a talent for creating engaging stories that resonate with young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Katy Did</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/what_katy_did_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/what_katy_did_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>What Katy Did Title: What Katy Did Author: Susan Coolidge Target Age Group: 8-12 years old &amp;ldquo;What Katy Did&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Susan Coolidge, originally published in 1872. The story revolves around the life of a young girl named Katy Carr and her family. The book has been cherished by generations of readers and continues to be a favorite among children today. The story is set in the 19th century and follows Katy, a lively and adventurous girl who loves to play with her siblings and friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>45 &amp; 47 Stella Street and Everything That Happened</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/45__47_stella_street_and_everything_that_happened_by_elizabeth_honey_isbn_1863738584/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/45__47_stella_street_and_everything_that_happened_by_elizabeth_honey_isbn_1863738584/</guid>
      <description>45 &amp;amp; 47 Stella Street and Everything That Happened by Elizabeth Honey Title: &amp;ldquo;45 &amp;amp; 47 Stella Street and Everything That Happened&amp;rdquo; Author: Elizabeth Honey Review: &amp;ldquo;45 &amp;amp; 47 Stella Street and Everything That Happened&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that captures the essence of childhood friendships, adventures, and the lessons we learn along the way. Elizabeth Honey has crafted a heartwarming story that is sure to resonate with readers of all ages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Mole Always Turns Up on Its Own</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/a_mole_always_turns_up_on_its_own_by_hanna_johansen_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/a_mole_always_turns_up_on_its_own_by_hanna_johansen_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>A Mole Always Turns Up on Its Own by Hanna Johansen Title: A Mole Always Turns Up on Its Own Author: Hanna Johansen Review: &amp;ldquo;A Mole Always Turns Up on Its Own&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Hanna Johansen, which is perfect for children aged 4-8 years old. The story follows the journey of a mole who gets separated from its family and must find its way back home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anastasia Krupnik</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/anastasia_krupnik_isbn_9788423927791/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/anastasia_krupnik_isbn_9788423927791/</guid>
      <description>Anastasia Krupnik Title: Anastasia Krupnik Author: Lois Lowry Review: Anastasia Krupnik is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Lois Lowry, which tells the story of a young girl named Anastasia who is trying to find her place in the world. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 8 and 12, and it is a perfect read for those who enjoy heartwarming stories with relatable characters. Anastasia Krupnik is a charming and witty protagonist who faces various challenges and experiences a wide range of emotions throughout the book.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Haroun and the Sea of Stories by Salman Rushdie</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/haroun_and_the_sea_of_stories_isbn_571196934/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/haroun_and_the_sea_of_stories_isbn_571196934/</guid>
      <description>Haroun and the Sea of Stories Title: Haroun and the Sea of Stories Author: Salman Rushdie Recommended Age Group: 8-12 years old Haroun and the Sea of Stories is a captivating and imaginative children&amp;rsquo;s book by Salman Rushdie. The story follows the adventures of a young boy named Haroun, who embarks on a magical journey to the fantastical world of Kahani. This enchanting world is filled with talking animals, wondrous creatures, and mysterious beings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jacob Have I Loved</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/jacob_have_i_loved_isbn_9788420460819/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/jacob_have_i_loved_isbn_9788420460819/</guid>
      <description>Jacob Have I Loved Title: Jacob Have I Loved Author: Katherine Paterson Review: Jacob Have I Loved is a beautifully written children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of two twin sisters, Sara Louise and Caroline, growing up on an island off the coast of Maryland. The story is narrated by Sara Louise, who is constantly overshadowed by her sister Caroline, who is considered to be the more beautiful and talented twin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Journey to Jo&#39;burg</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/journey_to_joburg_by_beverley_naidoo_isbn_9780064402378/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/journey_to_joburg_by_beverley_naidoo_isbn_9780064402378/</guid>
      <description>Journey to Jo&amp;rsquo;burg by Beverley Naidoo Title: Journey to Jo&amp;rsquo;burg Author: Beverley Naidoo Review: Journey to Jo&amp;rsquo;burg is a heartwarming and thought-provoking children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Beverley Naidoo. The story follows two siblings, Naledi and Tiro, as they embark on a journey from their small village to the big city of Johannesburg in search of their mother. Set against the backdrop of apartheid-era South Africa, the book tackles important themes such as family, friendship, and the struggle for equality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pit Pony</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/pit_pony_by_joyce_barkhouse_isbn_771570236/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/pit_pony_by_joyce_barkhouse_isbn_771570236/</guid>
      <description>Pit Pony by Joyce Barkhouse Title: Pit Pony Author: Joyce Barkhouse Review: &amp;ldquo;Pit Pony&amp;rdquo; by Joyce Barkhouse is a heartwarming and engaging children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young boy named Ben and his special bond with a pit pony named Gem. The book is set in a small coal-mining town in Nova Scotia, Canada, during the early 20th century. The target age group for this book is 8-12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Demon Headmaster</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_demon_headmaster_by_gillian_cross_isbn_192753746/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_demon_headmaster_by_gillian_cross_isbn_192753746/</guid>
      <description>The Demon Headmaster by Gillian Cross Title: The Demon Headmaster Author: Gillian Cross The Demon Headmaster is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Gillian Cross. The story revolves around a young girl named Dinah who transfers to a new school and encounters a mysterious and enigmatic headmaster. As Dinah delves deeper into the school&amp;rsquo;s secrets, she discovers that the headmaster possesses supernatural powers and is using them to control the students and faculty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Painted House</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_painted_house_by_montserrate_del_amo_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_painted_house_by_montserrate_del_amo_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Painted House by Montserrate Del Amo Title: The Painted House Author: Montserrate Del Amo Review: The Painted House is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that captures the imagination of young readers with its vibrant illustrations and heartwarming story. The book is perfect for children aged 4-8, as it is both engaging and educational. The story follows the adventures of a young girl named Lily, who loves to paint and dreams of creating a colorful world around her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When the Wind Blows</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/when_the_wind_blows_isbn_747292876/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/when_the_wind_blows_isbn_747292876/</guid>
      <description>When the Wind Blows Title: When the Wind Blows Author: Linda Booth Sweeney Illustrator: Jana Christy Recommended Age Group: 4-8 years old &amp;ldquo;When the Wind Blows&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that captures the essence of nature and the power of imagination. The story follows a young girl named Maya, who loves to play and explore in her backyard. One day, she notices the wind blowing, and she starts to imagine all the different things that the wind might be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are You There God? It&#39;s Me, Margaret</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/are_you_there_god_its_me_margaret_by_new_jersey_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/are_you_there_god_its_me_margaret_by_new_jersey_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Are You There God? It&amp;rsquo;s Me, Margaret by New Jersey Title: Are You There God? It&amp;rsquo;s Me, Margaret Author: New Jersey Review: Are You There God? It&amp;rsquo;s Me, Margaret is a heartwarming and relatable story that follows the life of a young girl named Margaret as she navigates the challenges of adolescence. The book, written by New Jersey, is an excellent choice for children between the ages of 8 and 12.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conrad: The Factory Made Boy</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/conrad_the_factory_made_boy_by_christine_nostlinger_isbn_745112498/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/conrad_the_factory_made_boy_by_christine_nostlinger_isbn_745112498/</guid>
      <description>Conrad: The Factory Made Boy by Christine Nostlinger Title: Conrad: The Factory Made Boy Author: Christine Nostlinger Review: Conrad: The Factory Made Boy is a heartwarming and thought-provoking children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Christine Nostlinger. The story revolves around a young boy named Conrad, who is created in a factory and shipped to a family as a &amp;ldquo;perfect&amp;rdquo; child. However, as Conrad starts to experience life, he realizes that being perfect is not as important as being loved and accepted for who he is.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stradbroke Dreamtime</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/stradbroke_dreamtime_by_oodgeroo_noonucal_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/stradbroke_dreamtime_by_oodgeroo_noonucal_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Stradbroke Dreamtime by Oodgeroo Noonucal Title: Stradbroke Dreamtime Author: Oodgeroo Noonucal Review: Stradbroke Dreamtime is a beautifully written and illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes readers on a captivating journey through the rich cultural heritage of the Aboriginal people of Australia. Authored by the renowned Oodgeroo Noonucal, this book is a perfect blend of storytelling, art, and education. The book primarily targets children between the ages of 6 and 12, making it an ideal choice for elementary school students.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Fib</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_fib_by_george_layton_isbn_9780330397957/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_fib_by_george_layton_isbn_9780330397957/</guid>
      <description>The Fib by George Layton Title: The Fib Author: George Layton Review: The Fib is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the story of a young boy named Billy who has a tendency to tell little white lies, or &amp;ldquo;fibs,&amp;rdquo; as he calls them. The book, written by George Layton, is a perfect blend of humor, adventure, and valuable life lessons. Target Age Group: The Fib is suitable for children between the ages of 6 and 10.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Goalkeeper&#39;s Revenge</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_goalkeepers_revenge_by_bill_naughton_isbn_340149418/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_goalkeepers_revenge_by_bill_naughton_isbn_340149418/</guid>
      <description>The Goalkeeper&amp;rsquo;s Revenge by Bill Naughton Title: The Goalkeeper&amp;rsquo;s Revenge Author: Bill Naughton Age Group: 8-12 years old The Goalkeeper&amp;rsquo;s Revenge is a charming and engaging children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Bill Naughton. The story follows the adventures of a young boy named Tommy who dreams of becoming a great soccer player. As Tommy faces various challenges and learns valuable life lessons, the reader is taken on a journey filled with humor, excitement, and heartwarming moments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Mouse and His Child</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_mouse_and_his_child_by_russell_hoban_isbn_9781849434652/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_mouse_and_his_child_by_russell_hoban_isbn_9781849434652/</guid>
      <description>The Mouse and His Child by Russell Hoban Title: The Mouse and His Child Author: Russell Hoban Review: The Mouse and His Child is a heartwarming and adventurous children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Russell Hoban. The story follows the journey of two wind-up toy mice, a parent and child, as they navigate the world in search of a place to call home. The book is targeted towards children aged 8-12 years old, as it contains complex themes and challenging vocabulary.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Turbulent Term of Tyke Tiler</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_turbulent_term_of_tyke_tiler_isbn_198312695/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_turbulent_term_of_tyke_tiler_isbn_198312695/</guid>
      <description>The Turbulent Term of Tyke Tiler Title: The Turbulent Term of Tyke Tiler Author: Gene Kemp The Turbulent Term of Tyke Tiler is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Gene Kemp. The story follows the adventures of Tyke Tiler, a young boy who is struggling to fit in at his new school. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 8 and 12, and is an engaging read that teaches valuable life lessons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Betsy-Tacy Books</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/betsy-tacy_books_isbn_9780064401272/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/betsy-tacy_books_isbn_9780064401272/</guid>
      <description>Betsy-Tacy Books Title: Betsy-Tacy Books Review: The Betsy-Tacy Books, written by Maud Hart Lovelace, is a delightful series that captures the essence of childhood friendships, imagination, and the innocence of a bygone era. This heartwarming collection of stories is perfect for young readers between the ages of 7 and 12, and it is an ideal choice for parents and teachers looking to instill important life lessons in their children. Set in the early 20th century, the Betsy-Tacy Books follow the adventures of two best friends, Betsy and Tacy, as they grow up together in the charming town of Deep Valley.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marcelino, Bread and Wine</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/marcelino_bread_and_wine_by_jose_maria_sanchez_silva_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/marcelino_bread_and_wine_by_jose_maria_sanchez_silva_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Marcelino, Bread and Wine by Jose Maria Sanchez Silva Title: Marcelino, Bread and Wine Author: José María Sánchez-Silva Target Age Group: 8-12 years old Marcelino, Bread and Wine is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young boy named Marcelino who lives in a monastery. The book, written by José María Sánchez-Silva, is a beautiful tale of friendship, love, and the power of faith. The story follows Marcelino as he forms a deep bond with the monks in the monastery, who become his family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minnow on the Say</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/minnow_on_the_say_by_philippa_pearce_isbn_9780192710772/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/minnow_on_the_say_by_philippa_pearce_isbn_9780192710772/</guid>
      <description>Minnow on the Say by Philippa Pearce Title: Minnow on the Say Author: Philippa Pearce Review: Minnow on the Say is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Philippa Pearce, which tells the story of two young boys, David and Adam, who embark on a thrilling adventure along the River Say. The book is suitable for children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old and is filled with captivating themes, life lessons, and an engaging narrative.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Old Yeller</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/old_yeller_isbn_9780061070082/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/old_yeller_isbn_9780061070082/</guid>
      <description>Old Yeller Title: Old Yeller Author: Phyllis Reynolds Naylor Review: Old Yeller is a heartwarming and engaging children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young boy named Travis and his loyal dog, Old Yeller. Set in the 1860s in the Texas wilderness, the book is filled with adventure, friendship, and valuable life lessons. The story is suitable for children aged 8-12, as it deals with themes of responsibility, bravery, and the importance of family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Warden&#39;s Niece</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/wardens_niece_by_gillian_avery_isbn_6707947/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/wardens_niece_by_gillian_avery_isbn_6707947/</guid>
      <description>Warden&amp;rsquo;s Niece by Gillian Avery Title: The Warden&amp;rsquo;s Niece Author: Gillian Avery Review: The Warden&amp;rsquo;s Niece is a charming and delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Gillian Avery. This story follows the adventures of a young girl named Matilda, who is sent to live with her uncle, the warden of a castle, after her parents pass away. As Matilda navigates her new life, she learns valuable lessons about friendship, courage, and the importance of embracing one&amp;rsquo;s unique qualities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Little Princess</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/a_little_princess_isbn_9781417601356/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/a_little_princess_isbn_9781417601356/</guid>
      <description>A Little Princess Title: A Little Princess Author: Frances Hodgson Burnett Review: A Little Princess is a timeless classic written by Frances Hodgson Burnett, which tells the story of a young girl named Sara Crewe who attends a boarding school in London. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 8 and 12, and is a perfect blend of imagination, adventure, and valuable life lessons. The story follows Sara Crewe, a kind and intelligent girl who is suddenly forced to face hardship and adversity when she loses her father and is left penniless.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anne of Green Gables</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/anne_of_green_gables_isbn_9798632974271/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/anne_of_green_gables_isbn_9798632974271/</guid>
      <description>Anne of Green Gables Title: Anne of Green Gables Author: Lucy Maud Montgomery Age Group: 8-12 years old Anne of Green Gables is a timeless classic that has captured the hearts of readers for generations. Written by Lucy Maud Montgomery, this children&amp;rsquo;s novel tells the story of Anne Shirley, an orphan girl who is sent to live with Matthew and Marilla Cuthbert, an elderly brother and sister, on their farm called Green Gables.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Just William</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/just_william_isbn_9781447285588/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/just_william_isbn_9781447285588/</guid>
      <description>Just William Title: Just William Author: Richmal Crompton Review: &amp;ldquo;Just William&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the adventures of a mischievous young boy named William Brown. The book is written by Richmal Crompton and is the first in a series of 39 books. The book is perfect for children between the ages of 8 and 12, as it contains relatable themes and age-appropriate language. The story revolves around William, who is always finding himself in unexpected situations, much to the chagrin of the adults around him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little House on the Prairie</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/little_house_on_the_prairie_isbn_006054399x/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/little_house_on_the_prairie_isbn_006054399x/</guid>
      <description>Little House on the Prairie Title: Little House on the Prairie Author: Laura Ingalls Wilder Review: Little House on the Prairie is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that transports readers to the pioneer life of the late 1800s. The story follows the Ingalls family as they leave their home in the Big Woods of Wisconsin and embark on a journey to build a new life on the prairie. The book is written in a simple, engaging style that makes it accessible to young readers, while also providing an accurate portrayal of the challenges and joys of pioneer life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mary Poppins</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/mary_poppins_isbn_140301828/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/mary_poppins_isbn_140301828/</guid>
      <description>Mary Poppins Title: Mary Poppins Author: P.L. Travers Mary Poppins is a delightful and whimsical children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a magical nanny who comes to live with the Banks family in London. The book is written by P.L. Travers and was first published in 1934. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 6 and 12 years old. The story is filled with fantastical adventures, engaging characters, and important life lessons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nesthakchen</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/nesthakchen_by_else_ury_isbn_3850011038/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/nesthakchen_by_else_ury_isbn_3850011038/</guid>
      <description>Nesthakchen by Else Ury Title: Nesthakchen Author: Else Ury Review: Nesthakchen is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Else Ury, which tells the story of a young girl named Anneliese who discovers a magical nest hidden in her garden. The nest is home to a family of talking birds who teach Anneliese valuable life lessons about friendship, courage, and the importance of cherishing the beauty of nature. The book is beautifully illustrated, and the vivid descriptions of the nest and its inhabitants make it easy for young readers to visualize the story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rebecca of Sunnybrook Farm</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/rebecca_of_sunnybrook_farm_by_kate_douglas_wiggin_isbn_9798445751250/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/rebecca_of_sunnybrook_farm_by_kate_douglas_wiggin_isbn_9798445751250/</guid>
      <description>Rebecca of Sunnybrook Farm by Kate Douglas Wiggin Title: Rebecca of Sunnybrook Farm Author: Kate Douglas Wiggin Review: Rebecca of Sunnybrook Farm is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s novel written by Kate Douglas Wiggin, first published in 1903. The story follows the adventures of Rebecca Rowena Randall, a young girl who is sent to live with her spinster aunts in the small town of Riverboro. The book is targeted towards children aged 8-12 years old and is filled with valuable life lessons that are relevant even today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sussi and Biribissi</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/sussi_and_biribissi_by_collodi_nipote_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/sussi_and_biribissi_by_collodi_nipote_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Sussi and Biribissi by Collodi Nipote Title: Sussi and Biribissi Author: Collodi Nipote Review: Sussi and Biribissi is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the adventures of two lovable characters, Sussi and Biribissi, as they explore the wonders of the natural world. With its engaging storyline and vibrant illustrations, this book is sure to capture the hearts of young readers and spark their curiosity about the world around them. Target Age Group: Sussi and Biribissi is an ideal read for children between the ages of 4 and 8.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Paul Street Boys</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_paul_street_boys_by_ferenc_maln%C3%A1r_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_paul_street_boys_by_ferenc_maln%C3%A1r_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Paul Street Boys by Ferenc Malnár Title: The Paul Street Boys Author: Ferenc Malnár Review: The Paul Street Boys is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Ferenc Malnár, which tells the story of a group of young boys living in the Paul Street neighborhood. The book is a perfect blend of adventure, friendship, and the challenges faced by children growing up. The story takes place in Budapest during the early 20th century, which adds a historical aspect to the narrative.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The School at the Chalet</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_school_at_the_chalet_by_elinor_m._brent-dyer_isbn_6903347/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_school_at_the_chalet_by_elinor_m._brent-dyer_isbn_6903347/</guid>
      <description>The School at the Chalet by Elinor M. Brent-Dyer Title: The School at the Chalet Author: Elinor M. Brent-Dyer Review: The School at the Chalet is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Elinor M. Brent-Dyer. The story follows the adventures of Jo Bettany, a young girl who finds herself at a new boarding school in the Swiss Alps called the Chalet School. The book is filled with heartwarming friendships, exciting adventures, and valuable life lessons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Secret Garden</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_secret_garden_isbn_9780721406329/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_secret_garden_isbn_9780721406329/</guid>
      <description>The Secret Garden Title: The Secret Garden Author: Frances Hodgson Burnett Review: The Secret Garden is a timeless classic that has captured the hearts of young readers for generations. Written by Frances Hodgson Burnett, this enchanting story takes us on a journey of self-discovery, friendship, and the power of nature. The story revolves around a young girl named Mary Lennox, who is orphaned and sent to live with her uncle in a mysterious and secluded manor on the Yorkshire Moors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Wind in the Willows</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_wind_in_the_willows_by_kenneth_grahame_isbn_1846796598/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_wind_in_the_willows_by_kenneth_grahame_isbn_1846796598/</guid>
      <description>The Wind in the Willows by Kenneth Grahame Title: The Wind in the Willows Author: Kenneth Grahame The Wind in the Willows, written by Kenneth Grahame, is a timeless classic that has been captivating the hearts of young readers for generations. This enchanting tale follows the adventures of Mole, Rat, Toad, and Badger, four anthropomorphic animals living in the English countryside. The story is filled with vivid descriptions of the natural world, memorable characters, and valuable life lessons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Young Visiters</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_young_visiters_by_daisy_ashford_isbn_9781448104086/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_young_visiters_by_daisy_ashford_isbn_9781448104086/</guid>
      <description>The Young Visiters by Daisy Ashford Title: The Young Visiters Author: Daisy Ashford Review: The Young Visiters is a charming and whimsical children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the young and talented Daisy Ashford. The story follows the adventures of a group of young visitors as they navigate the complexities of life and love. The book is targeted towards children aged 8-12 years old, as it features relatable characters and situations that young readers can easily connect with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Celia Says</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/what_celia_says_by_elena_fortun_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/what_celia_says_by_elena_fortun_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>What Celia Says by Elena Fortun Title: What Celia Says Author: Elena Fortun &amp;ldquo;What Celia Says&amp;rdquo; is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Elena Fortun, which tells the story of a young girl named Celia who has a unique way of looking at the world. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 5 to 10 years old, and it is an excellent choice for parents and teachers looking for a book that teaches valuable life lessons in a fun and engaging manner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Robinson the Younger</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/robinson_the_younger_by_johann_heinrich_campe_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/robinson_the_younger_by_johann_heinrich_campe_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Robinson the Younger by Johann Heinrich Campe Title: Robinson the Younger Author: Johann Heinrich Campe Review: Robinson the Younger is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Johann Heinrich Campe, which is a sequel to the popular story of Robinson Crusoe. This book is a perfect blend of adventure, self-discovery, and moral lessons that are relatable to children of various ages. The story follows the journey of Robinson the Younger, who is the son of the famous Robinson Crusoe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sophie&#39;s Misfortunes</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/sophies_misfortunes_by_comtesse_de_segur_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/sophies_misfortunes_by_comtesse_de_segur_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Sophie&amp;rsquo;s Misfortunes by Comtesse De Segur Title: Sophie&amp;rsquo;s Misfortunes Author: Comtesse De Segur Review: Sophie&amp;rsquo;s Misfortunes is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Comtesse De Segur. The story follows the adventures of a young girl named Sophie, who often finds herself in trouble due to her mischievous nature. This charming book is perfect for children between the ages of 7 and 12 years old. The book is filled with valuable life lessons that are presented in a simple and engaging manner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Adventures of Huckleberry Finn</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_adventures_of_huckleberry_finn_by_mark_twain_isbn_8190732617/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_adventures_of_huckleberry_finn_by_mark_twain_isbn_8190732617/</guid>
      <description>The Adventures of Huckleberry Finn by Mark Twain Title: The Adventures of Huckleberry Finn Author: Mark Twain Review: The Adventures of Huckleberry Finn is a classic American novel written by Mark Twain, which has been cherished by readers for generations. The story follows the adventures of a young boy named Huckleberry Finn, who escapes his abusive father and sets sail on a raft down the Mississippi River with a runaway slave named Jim.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Swiss Family Robinson</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_swiss_family_robinson_isbn_1299165508/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_swiss_family_robinson_isbn_1299165508/</guid>
      <description>The Swiss Family Robinson Title: The Swiss Family Robinson Author: Johann David Wyss The Swiss Family Robinson is a classic children&amp;rsquo;s adventure novel written by Johann David Wyss. The story revolves around a family of six who are shipwrecked on a deserted island after a storm. The family, consisting of a father, a mother, and their four sons, must learn to adapt to their new surroundings and work together to survive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Water-Babies</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_water-babies_isbn_9798485198176/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_water-babies_isbn_9798485198176/</guid>
      <description>The Water-Babies Title: The Water-Babies Author: Charles Kingsley Genre: Children&amp;rsquo;s Fantasy/Adventure Age Group: 8-12 years old &amp;ldquo;The Water-Babies&amp;rdquo; is a delightful and imaginative children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes readers on an enchanting journey through the world of water-babies. Written by Charles Kingsley, this book was first published in 1863 and has since become a classic in children&amp;rsquo;s literature. The story revolves around Tom, a young chimney sweeper, who is transformed into a water-baby after his death.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tom Sawyer</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/tom_sawyer_isbn_9798417467929/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/tom_sawyer_isbn_9798417467929/</guid>
      <description>Tom Sawyer Title: The Adventures of Tom Sawyer Author: Mark Twain Review: The Adventures of Tom Sawyer is a timeless classic written by Mark Twain, which takes the reader on a thrilling journey through the eyes of a young boy named Tom Sawyer. The story is set in the small town of St. Petersburg, Missouri, and follows Tom&amp;rsquo;s adventures with his friends, particularly Huckleberry Finn. The book is suitable for children between the ages of 8 and 12, as it contains elements of fun, mischief, and learning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Walk in the Park</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/a_walk_in_the_park_by_anthony_browne_isbn_241893976/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/a_walk_in_the_park_by_anthony_browne_isbn_241893976/</guid>
      <description>A Walk in the Park by Anthony Browne Title: A Walk in the Park Author: Anthony Browne Review: A Walk in the Park is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the talented author and illustrator, Anthony Browne. This book is perfect for young readers between the ages of 4 to 8 years old. The story follows a young boy and his father as they take a walk in the park. The book is filled with beautiful illustrations that capture the essence of the story and make it an enjoyable read for both children and adults.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Animalia</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/animalia_isbn_810919397/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/animalia_isbn_810919397/</guid>
      <description>Animalia Title: Animalia Author: Graeme Base Review: Animalia is a beautifully illustrated and engaging children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes young readers on a captivating journey through the alphabet. Written and illustrated by Graeme Base, this book is perfect for children aged 4-8 years old. The book is set up as an alphabetical exploration of the animal kingdom, with each letter featuring a different animal and a corresponding poem. The illustrations are vibrant, intricate, and filled with hidden details that will keep children engaged and curious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Horrid Henry Series</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/horrid_henry_series_by_francesca_simon_isbn_9781484001868/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/horrid_henry_series_by_francesca_simon_isbn_9781484001868/</guid>
      <description>Horrid Henry Series by Francesca Simon Title: Horrid Henry Series Author: Francesca Simon Review: The Horrid Henry Series, written by Francesca Simon, is a delightful collection of children&amp;rsquo;s books that follow the mischievous adventures of the titular character, Horrid Henry. The series is a perfect fit for young readers between the ages of 5 and 10 years old, as it captures their attention with its engaging storytelling and colorful illustrations. The books in the series are filled with funny, relatable, and sometimes outrageous situations that Horrid Henry finds himself in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John Brown, Rose and the Midnight Cat</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/john_brown_rose_and_the_midnight_cat_by_jenny_wagner_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/john_brown_rose_and_the_midnight_cat_by_jenny_wagner_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>John Brown, Rose and the Midnight Cat by Jenny Wagner Title: John Brown, Rose and the Midnight Cat Author: Jenny Wagner Review: &amp;ldquo;John Brown, Rose and the Midnight Cat&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Jenny Wagner. The story follows the adventures of John Brown, a young boy who lives with his family in a small cottage, and his friend Rose, a curious and imaginative girl. The two friends come across a mysterious midnight cat, which leads them on an exciting journey through the woods.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joyful Noise: Poems for Two Voices by Paul Fleischman</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/joyful_noise_poems_for_two_voices_isbn_590981838/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/joyful_noise_poems_for_two_voices_isbn_590981838/</guid>
      <description>Joyful Noise: Poems for Two Voices Title: Joyful Noise: Poems for Two Voices Author: Paul Fleischman Age Group: 6-10 years old &amp;ldquo;Joyful Noise: Poems for Two Voices&amp;rdquo; is a delightful and engaging collection of poems written by Paul Fleischman, specifically designed for two people to read aloud together. This book is perfect for children aged 6-10 years old, as it encourages collaboration, creativity, and a love for poetry. The book features a variety of poems, each with its own unique theme and message.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tar Beach</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/tar_beach_isbn_590463810/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/tar_beach_isbn_590463810/</guid>
      <description>Tar Beach Title: Tar Beach Author: Faith Ringgold Target Age Group: 5-10 years old Tar Beach is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Faith Ringgold, which takes readers on a magical journey through the eyes of a young girl named Cassie. The story is set in the 1930s and is based on the author&amp;rsquo;s own experiences growing up in Harlem. The book is beautifully illustrated with Faith Ringgold&amp;rsquo;s quilt-like artwork, which adds to the charm and uniqueness of the story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Big Sister</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_big_sister_by_siv_widerberg_isbn_9129591864/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_big_sister_by_siv_widerberg_isbn_9129591864/</guid>
      <description>The Big Sister by Siv Widerberg Title: The Big Sister Author: Siv Widerberg Review: The Big Sister is a heartwarming and beautifully illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young girl who becomes a big sister for the first time. This book is perfect for children between the ages of 3 and 8, as it captures the excitement and challenges of welcoming a new sibling into the family. The story follows the protagonist as she navigates the complex emotions of being a big sister, including jealousy, pride, and love.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Companions</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_companions_by_lygia_bojunga_nunes_isbn_9780434954155/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_companions_by_lygia_bojunga_nunes_isbn_9780434954155/</guid>
      <description>The Companions by Lygia Bojunga Nunes Title: The Companions Author: Lygia Bojunga Nunes Review: The Companions is a heartwarming and engaging children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a group of animals who come together to help a little bird find her way home. Written by Lygia Bojunga Nunes, this book is a perfect choice for young readers between the ages of 4 and 8 years old. The story revolves around a little bird named Zizi who gets lost while exploring the forest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Keeping Quilt</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_keeping_quilt_by_patricia_polacco_isbn_9780440831709/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_keeping_quilt_by_patricia_polacco_isbn_9780440831709/</guid>
      <description>The Keeping Quilt by Patricia Polacco Title: The Keeping Quilt Author: Patricia Polacco The Keeping Quilt, written by Patricia Polacco, is a heartwarming and beautifully illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a family&amp;rsquo;s cherished quilt and the traditions that it represents. This book is a perfect choice for children aged 5 to 10 years old, as it touches upon themes of family, love, and the importance of preserving cultural heritage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two Little Bears</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/two_little_bears_by_hanna_muschg_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/two_little_bears_by_hanna_muschg_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Two Little Bears by Hanna Muschg Title: Two Little Bears Author: Hanna Muschg Review: Two Little Bears is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Hanna Muschg, which tells the story of two young bears, Tina and Tom, who embark on a series of adventures in the forest. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 4 to 8 years old and is a perfect blend of fun, adventure, and valuable life lessons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amos and Boris</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/amos_and_boris_by_william_steig_isbn_9781846145254/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/amos_and_boris_by_william_steig_isbn_9781846145254/</guid>
      <description>Amos and Boris by William Steig Title: Amos and Boris Author: William Steig Review: Amos and Boris is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the talented William Steig. The story follows the adventures of Amos, a mouse, and Boris, a whale, as they form an unlikely friendship. The book is beautifully illustrated with Steig&amp;rsquo;s signature style, making it visually appealing for young readers. The target age group for Amos and Boris is 4 to 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jip and Janneke</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/jip_and_janneke_by_annie_m_g_schmidt_isbn_9045106655/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/jip_and_janneke_by_annie_m_g_schmidt_isbn_9045106655/</guid>
      <description>Jip and Janneke by Annie M G Schmidt Title: Jip and Janneke Author: Annie M.G. Schmidt Review: Jip and Janneke is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the renowned Dutch author Annie M.G. Schmidt. The book follows the adventures of two young siblings, Jip and Janneke, as they navigate through their daily lives, encountering various challenges and learning valuable life lessons along the way. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mog the Forgetful Cat</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/mog_the_forgetful_cat_by_judith_kerr_isbn_9780819305442/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/mog_the_forgetful_cat_by_judith_kerr_isbn_9780819305442/</guid>
      <description>Mog the Forgetful Cat by Judith Kerr Title: Mog the Forgetful Cat Author: Judith Kerr Review: Mog the Forgetful Cat is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Judith Kerr. The story revolves around Mog, a charming and lovable cat who is known for her forgetfulness. This book is perfect for children between the ages of 4 to 8 years old. The book is filled with colorful illustrations and simple, easy-to-understand language, making it an ideal read for young children.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ramona the Pest</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/ramona_the_pest_isbn_62253123/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/ramona_the_pest_isbn_62253123/</guid>
      <description>Ramona the Pest Title: Ramona the Pest Author: Beverly Cleary Review: Ramona the Pest is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Beverly Cleary, which tells the story of a young girl named Ramona Quimby, who is eager to start kindergarten and make new friends. The book is an engaging and heartwarming read that will captivate the hearts of young readers. Target Age Group: Ramona the Pest is best suited for children between the ages of 6 and 10 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Giving Tree</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_giving_tree_isbn_9780060284510/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_giving_tree_isbn_9780060284510/</guid>
      <description>The Giving Tree Title: The Giving Tree Author: Shel Silverstein The Giving Tree is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Shel Silverstein. The story revolves around the relationship between a young boy and a generous tree, which symbolizes unconditional love and selflessness. The book is targeted towards children aged 4 to 8 years old, as it is simple enough for young readers to understand and enjoy. However, the themes and lessons within the story are universal and can be appreciated by readers of all ages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Old Bear</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/old_bear_isbn_99413353/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/old_bear_isbn_99413353/</guid>
      <description>Old Bear Title: Old Bear Author: Kevin Henkes Review: Old Bear is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book written and illustrated by Kevin Henkes. The story revolves around a young girl named Emily, who is given a stuffed bear as a gift by her grandmother. The bear, named Old Bear, is well-loved by Emily and becomes her constant companion. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 4 to 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perez the Mouse</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/perez_the_mouse_by_luis_coloma_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/perez_the_mouse_by_luis_coloma_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Perez the Mouse by Luis Coloma Title: Perez the Mouse Author: Luis Coloma &amp;ldquo;Perez the Mouse&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Luis Coloma, which tells the story of a curious and adventurous little mouse named Perez. The book is perfect for children aged 4 to 8 years old, as it is filled with beautiful illustrations and simple language that young readers can easily understand and enjoy. The story revolves around Perez, who embarks on a journey to find a new home for his family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pumpkin Soup</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/pumpkin_soup_by_helen_cooper_isbn_374460310/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/pumpkin_soup_by_helen_cooper_isbn_374460310/</guid>
      <description>Pumpkin Soup by Helen Cooper Title: Pumpkin Soup Author: Helen Cooper &amp;ldquo;Pumpkin Soup&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Helen Cooper, which tells the story of three friends - a cat, a squirrel, and a duck - who live in a cozy cottage and work together to make delicious pumpkin soup. The book is filled with beautiful illustrations and captivating storytelling, making it a perfect read for young children. Target Age Group: The book is suitable for children between the ages of 3 and 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Adventures of Maya the Bee</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_adventures_of_maya_the_bee_by_waldemar_bonsels_isbn_1627937587/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_adventures_of_maya_the_bee_by_waldemar_bonsels_isbn_1627937587/</guid>
      <description>The Adventures of Maya the Bee by Waldemar Bonsels Title: The Adventures of Maya the Bee Author: Waldemar Bonsels Review: The Adventures of Maya the Bee, written by Waldemar Bonsels, is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the journey of Maya, a young bee who embarks on an adventure to explore the world outside her hive. The story is filled with colorful characters, exciting adventures, and valuable life lessons that make it an enjoyable read for children aged 6 to 10 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Story of the Little Mole</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_story_of_the_little_mole_by_werner_holzwarth_isbn_9781856025256/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_story_of_the_little_mole_by_werner_holzwarth_isbn_9781856025256/</guid>
      <description>The Story of the Little Mole by Werner Holzwarth Title: The Story of the Little Mole Author: Werner Holzwarth The Story of the Little Mole is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Werner Holzwarth, which tells the story of a curious little mole who sets out on an adventure to discover the world above ground. The book is beautifully illustrated by Wolf Erlbruch, adding a charming and whimsical touch to the story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When We Were Very Young</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/when_we_were_very_young_isbn_808538330/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/when_we_were_very_young_isbn_808538330/</guid>
      <description>When We Were Very Young Title: When We Were Very Young Author: A.A. Milne Illustrator: E.H. Shepard Age Group: 4-8 years old &amp;ldquo;When We Were Very Young&amp;rdquo; is a delightful collection of poems written by A.A. Milne, the author of the beloved Winnie-the-Pooh series. This book is an excellent choice for children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old, as it contains simple, yet engaging poems that will capture their imagination and attention.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blinky Bill</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/blinky_bill_by_dorothy_wall_isbn_207167400/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/blinky_bill_by_dorothy_wall_isbn_207167400/</guid>
      <description>Blinky Bill by Dorothy Wall Title: Blinky Bill Author: Dorothy Wall Review: Blinky Bill, written by Dorothy Wall, is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the adventures of a lovable koala named Blinky Bill. The story is set in the Australian bush and is filled with charming illustrations that bring the characters and their world to life. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Martine</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/martine_by_gilbert_delahaye_isbn_2203101555/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/martine_by_gilbert_delahaye_isbn_2203101555/</guid>
      <description>Martine by Gilbert Delahaye Title: Martine Author: Gilbert Delahaye Review: Martine is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Gilbert Delahaye that follows the adventures of a young girl named Martine. The book is perfect for children between the ages of 5 and 8, as it contains simple yet engaging language and beautiful illustrations that capture the imagination of young readers. The story revolves around Martine, who embarks on various exciting journeys and encounters a range of interesting characters along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mike Mulligan</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/mike_mulligan_by_virginia_lee_burton_isbn_9789995250270/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/mike_mulligan_by_virginia_lee_burton_isbn_9789995250270/</guid>
      <description>Mike Mulligan by Virginia Lee Burton Title: Mike Mulligan and His Steam Shovel Author: Virginia Lee Burton Review: Mike Mulligan and His Steam Shovel is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of Mike Mulligan, a hardworking and dedicated steam shovel operator, and his trusty steam shovel, Mary Anne. The book is perfect for children aged 4 to 8 years old and teaches valuable life lessons about perseverance, friendship, and adapting to change.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ox-Cart Man</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/ox-cart_man_isbn_9780881036077/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/ox-cart_man_isbn_9780881036077/</guid>
      <description>Ox-Cart Man Title: The Ox-Cart Man Author: Donald Hall Illustrator: Barbara Cooney Target Age Group: 4-8 years old The Ox-Cart Man is a beautifully illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a hardworking family living in rural New England during the 19th century. The book follows the journey of the father, who is an ox-cart man, as he travels to Portsmouth to sell his family&amp;rsquo;s goods at the market. The illustrations by Barbara Cooney are stunning, capturing the essence of the time period and the family&amp;rsquo;s way of life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peace at Last</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/peace_at_last_isbn_9780230015487/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/peace_at_last_isbn_9780230015487/</guid>
      <description>Peace at Last Title: Peace at Last Author: Jill Murphy Target Age Group: 4-8 years old Review: &amp;ldquo;Peace at Last&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Jill Murphy, which takes young readers on a heartwarming adventure with the endearing Mr. Bear and his family. The story follows Mr. Bear as he tries to find a quiet place to sleep after being constantly disturbed by the noises made by his family members.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Jolly Aunt</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_jolly_aunt_by_lothar_meggendorfer_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_jolly_aunt_by_lothar_meggendorfer_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Jolly Aunt by Lothar Meggendorfer Title: The Jolly Aunt Author: Lothar Meggendorfer Review: The Jolly Aunt is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Lothar Meggendorfer. This book is a perfect read for children aged 4-8 years old. The story revolves around an aunt who is known for her cheerful and playful nature. The aunt visits her nieces and nephews, bringing with her a bag full of surprises. The illustrations in this book are beautiful and captivating, making it a great read for both children and adults.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Up in a Tree</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/up_in_a_tree_by_margaret_atwood_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/up_in_a_tree_by_margaret_atwood_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Up in a Tree by Margaret Atwood Title: Up in a Tree Author: Margaret Atwood Review: Up in a Tree is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the renowned author Margaret Atwood. The book is beautifully illustrated by the talented artist, Kristin Kest, who brings the story to life with her captivating images. The story revolves around a young boy who finds himself stranded in a tree after climbing up to retrieve his kite.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Do People Do All Day?</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/what_do_people_do_all_day_isbn_7189494/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/what_do_people_do_all_day_isbn_7189494/</guid>
      <description>What Do People Do All Day? Title: What Do People Do All Day? Author: Richard Scarry Review: What Do People Do All Day? is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written and illustrated by Richard Scarry. The book takes young readers on a journey through the daily lives of various characters, showcasing the diverse occupations and activities people engage in. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who&#39;s Seen the Scissors?</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/whos_seen_the_scissors_by_fernando_krahn_isbn_525427104/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/whos_seen_the_scissors_by_fernando_krahn_isbn_525427104/</guid>
      <description>Who&amp;rsquo;s Seen the Scissors? by Fernando Krahn Title: &amp;ldquo;Who&amp;rsquo;s Seen the Scissors?&amp;quot; Author: Fernando Krahn Review: &amp;ldquo;Who&amp;rsquo;s Seen the Scissors?&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book by Fernando Krahn that follows the adventures of a group of friendly animals living in a peaceful forest. The story is engaging and filled with colorful illustrations that capture the imagination of young readers. The book targets children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old, making it an excellent choice for parents, teachers, and caregivers looking for a fun and educational read.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Little Engine That Could</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_little_engine_that_could_by_watty_piper_isbn_448189631/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_little_engine_that_could_by_watty_piper_isbn_448189631/</guid>
      <description>The Little Engine That Could by Watty Piper Title: The Little Engine That Could Author: Watty Piper The Little Engine That Could is a classic children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Watty Piper. This heartwarming story has been a favorite among children and parents alike for generations. The book is beautifully illustrated and has a simple, yet powerful message that resonates with readers of all ages. The story revolves around a little blue engine that is faced with the daunting task of pulling a long train over a steep mountain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Runaway Bunny</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_runaway_bunny_by_margaret_wise_brown_isbn_898459958/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_runaway_bunny_by_margaret_wise_brown_isbn_898459958/</guid>
      <description>The Runaway Bunny by Margaret Wise Brown Title: The Runaway Bunny Author: Margaret Wise Brown The Runaway Bunny is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Margaret Wise Brown, which beautifully captures the unconditional love between a mother and her child. The story revolves around a young bunny who decides to run away from home, and his mother&amp;rsquo;s reassurance that she will always be there for him, no matter where he goes or what he becomes.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
