<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Childrens Books that talk about &#39;Adulthood&#39; on Monsty The Monster Truck</title>
    <link>https://www.monsty.co/tags/childrens-books-that-talk-about-adulthood/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Childrens Books that talk about &#39;Adulthood&#39; on Monsty The Monster Truck</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.monsty.co/tags/childrens-books-that-talk-about-adulthood/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Keeper</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/keeper_by_mal_peet_isbn_9781406328066/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/keeper_by_mal_peet_isbn_9781406328066/</guid>
      <description>Keeper by Mal Peet Title: Keeper Author: Mal Peet Review: Keeper is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Mal Peet, which takes the reader on a thrilling journey through the world of soccer. The story follows the life of Elvis, a young boy who dreams of becoming a professional soccer player, and his encounter with the mysterious Keeper, who teaches him valuable life lessons. The book is targeted towards children aged 8-12 years old, as it explores themes such as perseverance, teamwork, and the importance of following one&amp;rsquo;s dreams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Illustrated Mum</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_illustrated_mum_isbn_9780385902632/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_illustrated_mum_isbn_9780385902632/</guid>
      <description>The Illustrated Mum Title: The Illustrated Mum Author: Jacqueline Wilson Review: The Illustrated Mum is a heartwarming and poignant children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of two sisters, Dolphin and Star, who navigate the challenges of growing up with a mother suffering from mental illness. The book is beautifully illustrated and the artwork complements the emotional depth of the story. The target age group for this book is children between the ages of 8 and 12.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alex</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/alex_by_tessa_duder_isbn_9780195581690/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/alex_by_tessa_duder_isbn_9780195581690/</guid>
      <description>Alex by Tessa Duder Title: Alex Author: Tessa Duder Review: &amp;ldquo;Alex&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Tessa Duder, which follows the adventures of a young girl named Alex as she navigates the challenges of growing up. The book is a perfect fit for children between the ages of 8 and 12, as it addresses themes that are relatable to this age group, such as friendship, self-discovery, and overcoming obstacles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Homecoming</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/homecoming_isbn_9780413413307/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/homecoming_isbn_9780413413307/</guid>
      <description>Homecoming Title: Homecoming Author: K.A. Applegate Review: Homecoming is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the journey of a young girl named Lily, who discovers the importance of family, friendship, and finding one&amp;rsquo;s true home. The story is filled with beautiful illustrations and captivating characters that will keep young readers engaged from start to finish. Target Age Group: Homecoming is suitable for children between the ages of 7 and 10. The book&amp;rsquo;s themes and language are appropriate for this age range, and the story provides valuable life lessons that children can relate to and learn from.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Kestrel for a Knave</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/a_kestrel_for_a_knave_isbn_1858481465/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/a_kestrel_for_a_knave_isbn_1858481465/</guid>
      <description>A Kestrel for a Knave Title: A Kestrel for a Knave Author: Barry Hines Recommended Age Group: 10-14 years old A Kestrel for a Knave is a captivating and thought-provoking novel by Barry Hines, which tells the story of Billy Casper, a young boy from a working-class family in a small English town. The book is a perfect blend of emotions, struggles, and triumphs, making it an excellent read for children between the ages of 10 and 14.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Chocolate War</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_chocolate_war_by_robert_cormier_isbn_9781400089963/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_chocolate_war_by_robert_cormier_isbn_9781400089963/</guid>
      <description>The Chocolate War by Robert Cormier Title: The Chocolate War Author: Robert Cormier Genre: Young Adult Fiction, Coming-of-Age Novel Recommended Age Group: 12-18 years old The Chocolate War, written by Robert Cormier, is a gripping and thought-provoking coming-of-age novel that delves into the complexities of adolescent life. This book is a must-read for young adults aged 12-18, as it addresses themes of individuality, conformity, and the consequences of standing up for one&amp;rsquo;s beliefs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Outsiders</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_outsiders_isbn_9780739339015/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_outsiders_isbn_9780739339015/</guid>
      <description>The Outsiders Title: The Outsiders Author: S.E. Hinton Review: The Outsiders is a classic coming-of-age novel written by S.E. Hinton, first published in 1967. The story is set in the 1960s and revolves around the lives of two rival gangs, the Greasers and the Socs, in Oklahoma. The narrative follows the experiences of Ponyboy Curtis, a young Greaser, as he navigates the challenges of growing up, dealing with the loss of loved ones, and questioning the societal divisions that exist between the two groups.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Catcher in the Rye</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_catcher_in_the_rye_by_j.d._salinger_isbn_9504000681/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_catcher_in_the_rye_by_j.d._salinger_isbn_9504000681/</guid>
      <description>The Catcher in the Rye by J.D. Salinger Title: The Catcher in the Rye Author: J.D. Salinger Review: The Catcher in the Rye is a classic coming-of-age novel written by J.D. Salinger. The story follows the life of a young teenager, Holden Caulfield, who struggles with the complexities of growing up and finding his place in the world. The book is targeted towards young adults, particularly those in their teenage years, who can relate to the challenges faced by the protagonist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Children of the New Forest</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_children_of_the_new_forest_isbn_158287395x/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_children_of_the_new_forest_isbn_158287395x/</guid>
      <description>The Children of the New Forest Title: The Children of the New Forest Author: Frederick Marryat Review: The Children of the New Forest is a captivating novel written by Frederick Marryat, originally published in 1847. This historical fiction story is set in the New Forest region of southern England during the English Civil War, and follows the lives of four orphaned children who must learn to survive and coexist in the wilderness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Girragundji</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/my_girragundji_by_meme_mcdonald_and_boon_pryor_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/my_girragundji_by_meme_mcdonald_and_boon_pryor_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>My Girragundji by Meme Mcdonald and Boon Pryor Title: My Girragundji Author: Meme McDonald and Boon Pryor Review: My Girragundji is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young boy named Jake and his special bond with a pet fish named Girragundji. The book is beautifully illustrated, and the text is simple and engaging, making it perfect for children aged 4 to 8 years old. The story explores themes of friendship, loss, and the importance of cherishing the memories we create with our loved ones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nothing to Be Afraid of</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/nothing_to_be_afraid_of_by_jan_mark_isbn_9780722656778/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/nothing_to_be_afraid_of_by_jan_mark_isbn_9780722656778/</guid>
      <description>Nothing to Be Afraid of by Jan Mark Title: &amp;ldquo;Nothing to Be Afraid of&amp;rdquo; Author: Jan Mark Review: &amp;ldquo;Nothing to Be Afraid of&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the adventures of a young boy named Gareth, who is afraid of the dark. Throughout the story, Gareth learns valuable life lessons about facing his fears and finding the courage to overcome them. The book is beautifully illustrated, with vibrant colors and engaging images that will capture the attention of young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Pair of Jesus Boots</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/a_pair_of_jesus_boots_by_sylvia_sherry_isbn_224615769/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/a_pair_of_jesus_boots_by_sylvia_sherry_isbn_224615769/</guid>
      <description>A Pair of Jesus Boots by Sylvia Sherry Title: A Pair of Jesus Boots Author: Sylvia Sherry Review: A Pair of Jesus Boots is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Sylvia Sherry. The story follows a young boy named Timmy, who desperately wants a pair of Jesus Boots - boots that can walk on water just like Jesus did. The book is targeted towards children aged 4-8 years old and is a perfect blend of adventure, imagination, and heartwarming lessons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are You There God? It&#39;s Me, Margaret</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/are_you_there_god_its_me_margaret_by_new_jersey_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/are_you_there_god_its_me_margaret_by_new_jersey_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Are You There God? It&amp;rsquo;s Me, Margaret by New Jersey Title: Are You There God? It&amp;rsquo;s Me, Margaret Author: New Jersey Review: Are You There God? It&amp;rsquo;s Me, Margaret is a heartwarming and relatable story that follows the life of a young girl named Margaret as she navigates the challenges of adolescence. The book, written by New Jersey, is an excellent choice for children between the ages of 8 and 12.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Knight&#39;s Fee</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/knights_fee_by_rosemary_sutcliff_isbn_99776308/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/knights_fee_by_rosemary_sutcliff_isbn_99776308/</guid>
      <description>Knight&amp;rsquo;s Fee by Rosemary Sutcliff Title: Knight&amp;rsquo;s Fee Author: Rosemary Sutcliff Genre: Children&amp;rsquo;s Historical Fiction Recommended Age Group: 8-12 years old Knight&amp;rsquo;s Fee by Rosemary Sutcliff is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s historical fiction novel that transports young readers to the medieval era. The story follows the life of a young boy named Bevis, who dreams of becoming a knight and serving his lord. Throughout the book, Bevis encounters various challenges, friendships, and life lessons that help shape his character and prepare him for the responsibilities of knighthood.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Goalkeeper&#39;s Revenge</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_goalkeepers_revenge_by_bill_naughton_isbn_340149418/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_goalkeepers_revenge_by_bill_naughton_isbn_340149418/</guid>
      <description>The Goalkeeper&amp;rsquo;s Revenge by Bill Naughton Title: The Goalkeeper&amp;rsquo;s Revenge Author: Bill Naughton Age Group: 8-12 years old The Goalkeeper&amp;rsquo;s Revenge is a charming and engaging children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Bill Naughton. The story follows the adventures of a young boy named Tommy who dreams of becoming a great soccer player. As Tommy faces various challenges and learns valuable life lessons, the reader is taken on a journey filled with humor, excitement, and heartwarming moments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Adventures of Huckleberry Finn</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_adventures_of_huckleberry_finn_by_mark_twain_isbn_8190732617/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_adventures_of_huckleberry_finn_by_mark_twain_isbn_8190732617/</guid>
      <description>The Adventures of Huckleberry Finn by Mark Twain Title: The Adventures of Huckleberry Finn Author: Mark Twain Review: The Adventures of Huckleberry Finn is a classic American novel written by Mark Twain, which has been cherished by readers for generations. The story follows the adventures of a young boy named Huckleberry Finn, who escapes his abusive father and sets sail on a raft down the Mississippi River with a runaway slave named Jim.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Paul Street Boys</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_paul_street_boys_by_ferenc_maln%C3%A1r_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_paul_street_boys_by_ferenc_maln%C3%A1r_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Paul Street Boys by Ferenc Malnár Title: The Paul Street Boys Author: Ferenc Malnár Review: The Paul Street Boys is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Ferenc Malnár, which tells the story of a group of young boys living in the Paul Street neighborhood. The book is a perfect blend of adventure, friendship, and the challenges faced by children growing up. The story takes place in Budapest during the early 20th century, which adds a historical aspect to the narrative.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tom Sawyer</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/tom_sawyer_isbn_9798417467929/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/tom_sawyer_isbn_9798417467929/</guid>
      <description>Tom Sawyer Title: The Adventures of Tom Sawyer Author: Mark Twain Review: The Adventures of Tom Sawyer is a timeless classic written by Mark Twain, which takes the reader on a thrilling journey through the eyes of a young boy named Tom Sawyer. The story is set in the small town of St. Petersburg, Missouri, and follows Tom&amp;rsquo;s adventures with his friends, particularly Huckleberry Finn. The book is suitable for children between the ages of 8 and 12, as it contains elements of fun, mischief, and learning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Water-Babies</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_water-babies_isbn_9798485198176/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_water-babies_isbn_9798485198176/</guid>
      <description>The Water-Babies Title: The Water-Babies Author: Charles Kingsley Genre: Children&amp;rsquo;s Fantasy/Adventure Age Group: 8-12 years old &amp;ldquo;The Water-Babies&amp;rdquo; is a delightful and imaginative children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes readers on an enchanting journey through the world of water-babies. Written by Charles Kingsley, this book was first published in 1863 and has since become a classic in children&amp;rsquo;s literature. The story revolves around Tom, a young chimney sweeper, who is transformed into a water-baby after his death.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
