<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Childrens Books that talk about &#39;Prejudice&#39; on Monsty The Monster Truck</title>
    <link>https://www.monsty.co/tags/childrens-books-that-talk-about-prejudice/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Childrens Books that talk about &#39;Prejudice&#39; on Monsty The Monster Truck</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.monsty.co/tags/childrens-books-that-talk-about-prejudice/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bud, Not Buddy</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/bud_not_buddy_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/bud_not_buddy_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Bud, Not Buddy Title: Bud, Not Buddy Author: Christopher Paul Curtis Review: Bud, Not Buddy is a heartwarming and adventurous story about a 10-year-old boy named Bud Caldwell, who embarks on a journey to find his father. Set in the 1930s during the Great Depression, the book takes readers on a rollercoaster of emotions as Bud encounters various obstacles and makes new friends along the way. The target age group for this book is 8-12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>By the River</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/by_the_river_by_steven_herrick_isbn_9781741143577/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/by_the_river_by_steven_herrick_isbn_9781741143577/</guid>
      <description>By the River by Steven Herrick Title: By the River Author: Steven Herrick Review: By the River is a beautifully written children&amp;rsquo;s book by Steven Herrick that captures the essence of childhood innocence and the importance of friendship. The book is perfect for children aged 8-12, as it is both engaging and thought-provoking. The story follows the life of Ben, a young boy who spends his days by the river, observing the world around him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deadly, Unna?</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/deadly_unna_by_phillip_gwynne_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/deadly_unna_by_phillip_gwynne_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Deadly, Unna? by Phillip Gwynne Title: Deadly, Unna? Author: Phillip Gwynne Review: Deadly, Unna? is a captivating and thought-provoking children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Phillip Gwynne. The story follows the life of a young boy named Gary Black, who is a member of the Australian football team. Gary&amp;rsquo;s life takes an unexpected turn when he befriends a young indigenous girl named Nunga, who teaches him about her culture and the struggles her community faces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Am Not Esther</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/i_am_not_esther_by_fleur_beale_isbn_9781864470598/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/i_am_not_esther_by_fleur_beale_isbn_9781864470598/</guid>
      <description>I Am Not Esther by Fleur Beale Title: I Am Not Esther Author: Fleur Beale Review: I Am Not Esther is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Fleur Beale, which tells the story of a young girl named Kirby who is forced to live with her estranged relatives after her mother&amp;rsquo;s sudden death. The book primarily targets children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old, as it explores themes of family, friendship, and self-discovery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not Chicage, Not Here</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/not_chicage_not_here_by_kirsten_boie_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/not_chicage_not_here_by_kirsten_boie_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Not Chicage, Not Here by Kirsten Boie Title: Not Chicago, Not Here Author: Kirsten Boie &amp;ldquo;Not Chicago, Not Here&amp;rdquo; is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book by Kirsten Boie that tells the story of a young girl named Lena, who struggles with the idea of moving to a new city and leaving her friends behind. The book beautifully captures the emotions and challenges that children face when dealing with change and uncertainty. The target age group for this book is 8 to 12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Noughts and Crosses</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/noughts_and_crosses_isbn_836932692/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/noughts_and_crosses_isbn_836932692/</guid>
      <description>Noughts and Crosses Title: Noughts and Crosses Author: Malorie Blackman Target Age Group: 10-14 years old Noughts and Crosses is a captivating novel by Malorie Blackman that takes readers on a thrilling journey through a world where racism and prejudice are reversed. The story follows the lives of two teenagers, Callum and Sephy, who come from different backgrounds and are faced with challenges in their friendship as they grow up in a society divided by race.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oh, Boy!</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/oh_boy_by_marie-aude_murail_isbn_811847624/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/oh_boy_by_marie-aude_murail_isbn_811847624/</guid>
      <description>Oh, Boy! by Marie-Aude Murail Title: Oh, Boy! Author: Marie-Aude Murail Review: Oh, Boy! is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that captures the essence of growing up and learning to navigate the complexities of life. The story follows the journey of a young boy named Nicolas as he navigates through the ups and downs of life, all while trying to find his place in the world. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stone Cold</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/stone_cold_by_robert_swindells_isbn_9780745173993/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/stone_cold_by_robert_swindells_isbn_9780745173993/</guid>
      <description>Stone Cold by Robert Swindells Title: Stone Cold Author: Robert Swindells Review: Stone Cold by Robert Swindells is a captivating and thought-provoking children&amp;rsquo;s book that explores the complex themes of homelessness, family dynamics, and the power of friendship. The story follows the life of a young boy named Link, who finds himself homeless after his father&amp;rsquo;s death and his mother&amp;rsquo;s inability to cope. The book is well-written and engaging, making it an excellent choice for children aged 10-14.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Fire-Eaters</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_fire-eaters_by_david_almond_isbn_385902077/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_fire-eaters_by_david_almond_isbn_385902077/</guid>
      <description>The Fire-Eaters by David Almond Title: The Fire-Eaters Author: David Almond Genre: Children&amp;rsquo;s Fiction, Fantasy Recommended Age Group: 9-12 years old The Fire-Eaters by David Almond is a captivating and enchanting children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes readers on a thrilling adventure filled with magic, mystery, and a touch of humor. The story revolves around a young boy named Bobby Burns, who lives in a small village in the North of England. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 9 and 12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Witch Child</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_witch_child_isbn_722658389/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_witch_child_isbn_722658389/</guid>
      <description>The Witch Child Title: The Witch Child Author: Virginia Pilegard Review: The Witch Child is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young girl named Mary who lives in a small village. Mary is different from the other children because she has a special gift - she can talk to animals. The story follows Mary as she uses her gift to help the animals in her village and teaches valuable life lessons along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thursday&#39;s Child</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/thursdays_child_by_sonya_hartnett_isbn_1536206431/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/thursdays_child_by_sonya_hartnett_isbn_1536206431/</guid>
      <description>Thursday&amp;rsquo;s Child by Sonya Hartnett Title: Thursday&amp;rsquo;s Child Author: Sonya Hartnett Review: Thursday&amp;rsquo;s Child is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the talented Sonya Hartnett. This beautifully crafted story follows the life of a young boy named Harper Flute, who lives in a small, close-knit community during the Great Depression. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 8 and 12, making it an excellent choice for elementary school students.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When the World Was Still Young</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/when_the_world_was_still_young_by_jurg_schubiger_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/when_the_world_was_still_young_by_jurg_schubiger_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>When the World Was Still Young by Jurg Schubiger Title: When the World Was Still Young Author: Jurg Schubiger Review: When the World Was Still Young is a beautifully illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young boy named Jonas who embarks on a magical adventure. The book is suitable for children between the ages of 6 and 10 years old. The story follows Jonas as he discovers a hidden door in his grandfather&amp;rsquo;s attic, which leads him to a world where time has stopped.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Parcel of Patterns</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/a_parcel_of_patterns_by_jill_paton_walsh_isbn_722658982/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/a_parcel_of_patterns_by_jill_paton_walsh_isbn_722658982/</guid>
      <description>A Parcel of Patterns by Jill Paton Walsh Title: A Parcel of Patterns Author: Jill Paton Walsh A Parcel of Patterns is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book by Jill Paton Walsh, set in the 17th century during the time of the Great Plague. The story revolves around a young girl named Matilda, who lives in the village of Eyam. When the plague strikes, Matilda&amp;rsquo;s life takes a dramatic turn, and she must learn to cope with the challenges that come her way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alex</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/alex_by_tessa_duder_isbn_9780195581690/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/alex_by_tessa_duder_isbn_9780195581690/</guid>
      <description>Alex by Tessa Duder Title: Alex Author: Tessa Duder Review: &amp;ldquo;Alex&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Tessa Duder, which follows the adventures of a young girl named Alex as she navigates the challenges of growing up. The book is a perfect fit for children between the ages of 8 and 12, as it addresses themes that are relatable to this age group, such as friendship, self-discovery, and overcoming obstacles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brother in the Land</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/brother_in_the_land_by_robert_swindells_isbn_9780140317985/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/brother_in_the_land_by_robert_swindells_isbn_9780140317985/</guid>
      <description>Brother in the Land by Robert Swindells Title: Brother in the Land Author: Robert Swindells Target Age Group: 10-14 years old &amp;ldquo;Brother in the Land&amp;rdquo; is a poignant and thought-provoking novel by Robert Swindells that delves into the harsh realities of a post-apocalyptic world. The story is set in a small town in northern England, where the devastating effects of a nuclear war have left the landscape barren and the community struggling to survive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Handles</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/handles_isbn_9781708024031/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/handles_isbn_9781708024031/</guid>
      <description>Handles Title: Handles Author: Jane Doe Review: Handles is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that captures the hearts of young readers with its engaging story and beautiful illustrations. The book, written by Jane Doe, is a perfect fit for children aged 4 to 8 years old. The story revolves around a lovable character named Handles, who is a little boy with a big heart. Handles goes on an adventure in his small town, where he encounters various challenges and learns valuable life lessons along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hey, Dollface</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/hey_dollface_by_deborah_hautzig_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/hey_dollface_by_deborah_hautzig_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Hey, Dollface by Deborah Hautzig Title: Hey, Dollface Author: Deborah Hautzig Review: Hey, Dollface is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Deborah Hautzig. The story revolves around a young girl named Dollface, who is struggling to find her identity and place in the world. Throughout the book, Dollface encounters various challenges and experiences that help her grow and learn valuable life lessons. Target Age Group: Hey, Dollface is primarily targeted towards children between the ages of 8 and 12.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Homecoming</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/homecoming_isbn_9780413413307/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/homecoming_isbn_9780413413307/</guid>
      <description>Homecoming Title: Homecoming Author: K.A. Applegate Review: Homecoming is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the journey of a young girl named Lily, who discovers the importance of family, friendship, and finding one&amp;rsquo;s true home. The story is filled with beautiful illustrations and captivating characters that will keep young readers engaged from start to finish. Target Age Group: Homecoming is suitable for children between the ages of 7 and 10. The book&amp;rsquo;s themes and language are appropriate for this age range, and the story provides valuable life lessons that children can relate to and learn from.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Johnny, My Friend</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/johnny_my_friend_by_peter_pohl_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/johnny_my_friend_by_peter_pohl_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Johnny, My Friend by Peter Pohl Title: Johnny, My Friend Author: Peter Pohl Review: &amp;ldquo;Johnny, My Friend&amp;rdquo; is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Peter Pohl. The story follows the adventures of a young boy named Johnny and his best friend, a magical talking dog named Rover. Together, they embark on a series of exciting and imaginative adventures that teach valuable life lessons along the way. The book is beautifully illustrated, with vibrant and engaging pictures that capture the essence of each scene.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Looking for Alibrandi</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/looking_for_alibrandi_isbn_375936947/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/looking_for_alibrandi_isbn_375936947/</guid>
      <description>Looking for Alibrandi Title: Looking for Alibrandi Author: Melina Marchetta Target Age Group: 12-15 years old Looking for Alibrandi is a heartwarming and relatable coming-of-age story that captures the struggles and experiences of a young girl named Josephine Alibrandi. The book is written by Melina Marchetta and is a perfect read for children between the ages of 12 and 15 years old. The story follows Josephine, a teenage girl trying to find her place in the world as she navigates through the challenges of high school, family, and her Italian heritage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pagan&#39;s Crusade</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/pagans_crusade_by_catherine_jinks_isbn_9780763625849/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/pagans_crusade_by_catherine_jinks_isbn_9780763625849/</guid>
      <description>Pagan&amp;rsquo;s Crusade by Catherine Jinks Title: Pagan&amp;rsquo;s Crusade Author: Catherine Jinks Pagan&amp;rsquo;s Crusade is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the talented author, Catherine Jinks. The story follows the adventures of a young boy named Pagan as he embarks on a thrilling crusade to rescue his kidnapped sister. The book is primarily targeted towards children aged 8-12 years old, as it contains elements of adventure, history, and fantasy that are likely to captivate young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roll of Thunder, Hear My Cry</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/roll_of_thunder_hear_my_cry_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/roll_of_thunder_hear_my_cry_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Roll of Thunder, Hear My Cry Title: Roll of Thunder, Hear My Cry Author: Mildred D. Taylor Age Group: 10-14 years old Roll of Thunder, Hear My Cry is a captivating novel by Mildred D. Taylor that tells the story of a young African American girl named Cassie Logan, who lives with her family in Mississippi during the 1930s. The book offers a unique perspective on the challenges faced by African Americans during the Great Depression and the Jim Crow era.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>See Ya, Simon</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/see_ya_simon_by_david_hill_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/see_ya_simon_by_david_hill_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>See Ya, Simon by David Hill Title: See Ya, Simon Author: David Hill Target Age Group: 8-12 years old &amp;ldquo;See Ya, Simon&amp;rdquo; is a heartwarming and engaging children&amp;rsquo;s book by David Hill that captures the attention of young readers with its relatable characters and themes. The story revolves around a young boy named Simon, who struggles with the challenges of growing up and navigating the complexities of friendships and relationships. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 8 and 12, as it addresses issues that are relevant to this age group, such as bullying, self-esteem, and the importance of communication.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Changeover</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_changeover_isbn_9780816144402/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_changeover_isbn_9780816144402/</guid>
      <description>The Changeover Title: The Changeover Author: Margaret Mahy Review: The Changeover is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Margaret Mahy, which explores the story of a teenage girl named Laura Chant who discovers her supernatural powers. This book is a perfect blend of fantasy, adventure, and coming-of-age themes, making it an enjoyable read for young readers. Target Age Group: The Changeover is best suited for children aged 10 to 14 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Devil&#39;s Arithmetic</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_devils_arithmetic_by_jane_yolen_isbn_9781664495296/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_devils_arithmetic_by_jane_yolen_isbn_9781664495296/</guid>
      <description>The Devil&amp;rsquo;s Arithmetic by Jane Yolen Title: The Devil&amp;rsquo;s Arithmetic Author: Jane Yolen Review: The Devil&amp;rsquo;s Arithmetic, written by Jane Yolen, is a poignant and thought-provoking children&amp;rsquo;s book that delves into the harsh realities of the Holocaust. The story follows a young girl named Hannah, who is transported back in time to a concentration camp during the Holocaust. Through her experiences, she learns the importance of remembering and honoring the past, as well as the value of courage and resilience in the face of adversity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Kestrel for a Knave</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/a_kestrel_for_a_knave_isbn_1858481465/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/a_kestrel_for_a_knave_isbn_1858481465/</guid>
      <description>A Kestrel for a Knave Title: A Kestrel for a Knave Author: Barry Hines Recommended Age Group: 10-14 years old A Kestrel for a Knave is a captivating and thought-provoking novel by Barry Hines, which tells the story of Billy Casper, a young boy from a working-class family in a small English town. The book is a perfect blend of emotions, struggles, and triumphs, making it an excellent read for children between the ages of 10 and 14.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Across the Barricades</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/across_the_barricades_by_joan_lindgard_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/across_the_barricades_by_joan_lindgard_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Across the Barricades by Joan Lindgard Title: Across the Barricades Author: Joan Lindgard Review: Across the Barricades is a heartwarming and thought-provoking children&amp;rsquo;s book that explores the themes of friendship, overcoming differences, and the power of understanding. The story follows two young characters, Sadie and Kevin, who live on opposite sides of a barricade that divides their town. Sadie&amp;rsquo;s family is part of the wealthy and privileged community, while Kevin&amp;rsquo;s family struggles to make ends meet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Carrie&#39;s War</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/carries_war_isbn_9780575016316/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/carries_war_isbn_9780575016316/</guid>
      <description>Carrie&amp;rsquo;s War Title: Carrie&amp;rsquo;s War Author: Nina Bawden Review: Carrie&amp;rsquo;s War is a heartwarming and engaging children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Nina Bawden. The story is set during World War II and follows the adventures of two siblings, Carrie and Nick, who are evacuated from London to a small Welsh village. The book targets the age group of 8-12 years old and provides an excellent opportunity for young readers to learn about the historical context of World War II.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chocky</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/chocky_isbn_14_003121_9/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/chocky_isbn_14_003121_9/</guid>
      <description>Chocky Title: Chocky Author: John Wyndham Genre: Science Fiction, Children&amp;rsquo;s Literature Recommended Age Group: 8-12 years old Chocky is a captivating science fiction novel written by John Wyndham, which tells the story of a young boy named Matthew who starts having conversations with an invisible entity named Chocky. The book is a perfect blend of adventure, mystery, and a touch of humor, making it an enjoyable read for children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Friedrich</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/friedrich_by_hans-peter_richter_isbn_9782010141591/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/friedrich_by_hans-peter_richter_isbn_9782010141591/</guid>
      <description>Friedrich by Hans-Peter Richter Title: Friedrich Author: Hans-Peter Richter Friedrich is a beautifully written children&amp;rsquo;s book by Hans-Peter Richter that tells the story of a young boy named Friedrich who is growing up in Germany during World War II. The book is suitable for children aged 9-12 years old and is an excellent choice for parents and educators looking to introduce historical events and important life lessons to their young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sounder</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/sounder_isbn_575006536/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/sounder_isbn_575006536/</guid>
      <description>Sounder Title: Sounder Author: William H. Armstrong Review: Sounder is a heartwarming and thought-provoking children&amp;rsquo;s book written by William H. Armstrong. The story is set in the rural South during the early 1900s and follows the life of a young African American boy named David and his loyal dog, Sounder. The book primarily targets children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old. It is a great read for this age group as it touches upon themes of family, friendship, and perseverance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Cay</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_cay_by_theodore_taylor_isbn_9780385079068/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_cay_by_theodore_taylor_isbn_9780385079068/</guid>
      <description>The Cay by Theodore Taylor Title: The Cay Author: Theodore Taylor The Cay is a captivating and thought-provoking children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Theodore Taylor. The story is set during World War II and follows the journey of two unlikely friends, a young boy named Phillip and an old West Indian man named Timothy, who are stranded on a small island after their ship is torpedoed by a German U-boat. The target age group for this book is 8-12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Chocolate War</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_chocolate_war_by_robert_cormier_isbn_9781400089963/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_chocolate_war_by_robert_cormier_isbn_9781400089963/</guid>
      <description>The Chocolate War by Robert Cormier Title: The Chocolate War Author: Robert Cormier Genre: Young Adult Fiction, Coming-of-Age Novel Recommended Age Group: 12-18 years old The Chocolate War, written by Robert Cormier, is a gripping and thought-provoking coming-of-age novel that delves into the complexities of adolescent life. This book is a must-read for young adults aged 12-18, as it addresses themes of individuality, conformity, and the consequences of standing up for one&amp;rsquo;s beliefs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Machine Gunners</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_machine_gunners_isbn_033033428x/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_machine_gunners_isbn_033033428x/</guid>
      <description>The Machine Gunners Title: The Machine Gunners Author: Robert Westall Review: The Machine Gunners is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Robert Westall, which takes the reader on a thrilling journey through the lives of a group of young friends living in the midst of World War II. The story is set in the north of England and follows the adventures of a group of children who discover a German machine gun in the wreckage of a downed aircraft.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Outsiders</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_outsiders_isbn_9780739339015/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_outsiders_isbn_9780739339015/</guid>
      <description>The Outsiders Title: The Outsiders Author: S.E. Hinton Review: The Outsiders is a classic coming-of-age novel written by S.E. Hinton, first published in 1967. The story is set in the 1960s and revolves around the lives of two rival gangs, the Greasers and the Socs, in Oklahoma. The narrative follows the experiences of Ponyboy Curtis, a young Greaser, as he navigates the challenges of growing up, dealing with the loss of loved ones, and questioning the societal divisions that exist between the two groups.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Witch of Blackbird Pond</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_witch_of_blackbird_pond_isbn_9780395913673/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_witch_of_blackbird_pond_isbn_9780395913673/</guid>
      <description>The Witch of Blackbird Pond Title: The Witch of Blackbird Pond Author: Elizabeth George Speare Genre: Historical Fiction, Children&amp;rsquo;s Literature Age Group: 8-12 years old &amp;ldquo;The Witch of Blackbird Pond&amp;rdquo; is a captivating historical fiction novel written by Elizabeth George Speare, which tells the story of a young orphan girl named Kit Tyler who moves from the lush Caribbean island of Barbados to the small, strict town of Wethersfield, Connecticut in 1687.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To Kill a Mockingbird</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/to_kill_a_mockingbird_by_harper_lee_isbn_434012602/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/to_kill_a_mockingbird_by_harper_lee_isbn_434012602/</guid>
      <description>To Kill a Mockingbird by Harper Lee Title: To Kill a Mockingbird Author: Harper Lee Review: To Kill a Mockingbird, written by Harper Lee, is a captivating novel that tells the story of a young girl named Scout Finch and her brother Jem, growing up in the fictional town of Maycomb, Alabama during the 1930s. Through the eyes of these innocent children, the reader is exposed to the harsh realities of racism, prejudice, and injustice that were prevalent in the American South during that time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twopence a Tub</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/twopence_a_tub_by_susan_price_isbn_9780571106240/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/twopence_a_tub_by_susan_price_isbn_9780571106240/</guid>
      <description>Twopence a Tub by Susan Price Title: Twopence a Tub Author: Susan Price Review: Twopence a Tub is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Susan Price, which takes readers on a captivating journey through the life of a young boy named Joe. The story is set in the early 1900s and revolves around Joe&amp;rsquo;s family, who work as washerwomen, washing clothes for wealthy people. The book targets children between the ages of 8 to 12 years old, as it contains a perfect blend of adventure, emotion, and historical context.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zazie in the Metro</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/zazie_in_the_metro_isbn_9780714538723/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/zazie_in_the_metro_isbn_9780714538723/</guid>
      <description>Zazie in the Metro Title: Zazie in the Metro Author: Raymond Queneau Recommended Age Group: 7-10 years old Zazie in the Metro is a charming and whimsical children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the adventures of Zazie, a young girl who gets lost in the Paris Metro system. The story is filled with humor, vivid descriptions, and engaging characters that will capture the imagination of young readers. The book is suitable for children aged 7-10 years old, as it features simple language and relatable themes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cue for Treason</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/cue_for_treason_by_geoffrey_trease_isbn_014132726x/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/cue_for_treason_by_geoffrey_trease_isbn_014132726x/</guid>
      <description>Cue for Treason by Geoffrey Trease Title: Cue for Treason Author: Geoffrey Trease Review: Cue for Treason is a thrilling adventure story set in the 16th century, which follows the journey of two young boys, Peter and Tom, as they become entangled in a dangerous plot to overthrow Queen Elizabeth I. The book is an excellent choice for elementary school children, particularly those in the 8-12 age range, as it is filled with suspense, action, and historical intrigue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Johnny Tremain</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/johnny_tremain_isbn_9780137171743/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/johnny_tremain_isbn_9780137171743/</guid>
      <description>Johnny Tremain Title: Johnny Tremain Author: Esther Forbes Age Group: 9-12 years old Johnny Tremain is a historical fiction novel written by Esther Forbes, which takes place during the American Revolution. The story follows the life of a young silversmith apprentice named Johnny Tremain, who loses the use of his hand in an accident. The book showcases the challenges Johnny faces as he navigates his new life and learns to adapt to his disability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lord of the Flies</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/lord_of_the_flies_by_william_golding_isbn_7532766969/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/lord_of_the_flies_by_william_golding_isbn_7532766969/</guid>
      <description>Lord of the Flies by William Golding Title: Lord of the Flies Author: William Golding Target Age Group: 12-16 years old Review: Lord of the Flies is a classic novel by William Golding that tells the story of a group of young boys who find themselves stranded on a deserted island after a plane crash. The book explores themes of human nature, power, and the fragility of civilization. The story is both captivating and thought-provoking, as it delves into the darker aspects of human nature.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Catcher in the Rye</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_catcher_in_the_rye_by_j.d._salinger_isbn_9504000681/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_catcher_in_the_rye_by_j.d._salinger_isbn_9504000681/</guid>
      <description>The Catcher in the Rye by J.D. Salinger Title: The Catcher in the Rye Author: J.D. Salinger Review: The Catcher in the Rye is a classic coming-of-age novel written by J.D. Salinger. The story follows the life of a young teenager, Holden Caulfield, who struggles with the complexities of growing up and finding his place in the world. The book is targeted towards young adults, particularly those in their teenage years, who can relate to the challenges faced by the protagonist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The War of the Buttons</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_war_of_the_buttons_by_louis_pergaud_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_war_of_the_buttons_by_louis_pergaud_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The War of the Buttons by Louis Pergaud Title: The War of the Buttons Author: Louis Pergaud Genre: Children&amp;rsquo;s Fiction, Coming-of-Age Recommended Age Group: 8-12 years old The War of the Buttons, written by Louis Pergaud, is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes readers on a journey through the lives of two rival groups of young boys. The story is set in a small French village, where the boys from one village constantly engage in playful battles with the boys from another village.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Around the World in Eighty Days</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/around_the_world_in_eighty_days_isbn_9780756784652/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/around_the_world_in_eighty_days_isbn_9780756784652/</guid>
      <description>Around the World in Eighty Days Title: Around the World in Eighty Days Author: Jules Verne Age Group: 8-12 years old &amp;ldquo;Around the World in Eighty Days&amp;rdquo; is a thrilling adventure novel written by Jules Verne, which takes readers on a whirlwind journey around the globe. The story follows the determined and punctual Phileas Fogg, who accepts a wager to circumnavigate the world in just 80 days. Accompanied by his loyal French valet, Passepartout, Fogg encounters numerous obstacles and challenges throughout his journey, making for an exciting and engaging read.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Barrumbi Kids</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/barrumbi_kids_by_leonie_norrington_isbn_9781862914964/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/barrumbi_kids_by_leonie_norrington_isbn_9781862914964/</guid>
      <description>Barrumbi Kids by Leonie Norrington Title: Barrumbi Kids Author: Leonie Norrington Review: Barrumbi Kids is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes young readers on an adventure through the Australian outback. The story follows the lives of four Indigenous children, each with their unique personalities and talents. Leonie Norrington has beautifully crafted a tale that not only entertains but also teaches valuable life lessons. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 7 and 12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/harry_potter_and_the_goblet_of_fire_isbn_1413185096/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/harry_potter_and_the_goblet_of_fire_isbn_1413185096/</guid>
      <description>Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire Title: Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire Author: J.K. Rowling Target Age Group: 9-12 years old Review: Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire is the fourth book in the Harry Potter series by J.K. Rowling. This thrilling and magical adventure takes readers on a journey with Harry Potter and his friends, Ron Weasley and Hermione Granger, as they navigate the challenges of their fourth year at Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little Women</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/little_women_by_louisa_may_alcott_isbn_1974138135/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/little_women_by_louisa_may_alcott_isbn_1974138135/</guid>
      <description>Little Women by Louisa May Alcott Title: Little Women Author: Louisa May Alcott Little Women, written by Louisa May Alcott, is a timeless classic that has captured the hearts of readers for generations. This heartwarming novel tells the story of the March sisters - Meg, Jo, Beth, and Amy - as they navigate their lives during the American Civil War. The book is an excellent choice for children aged 8 to 12 years old, as it provides valuable life lessons and a glimpse into the lives of these remarkable young women.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Robinson Crusoe</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/robinson_crusoe_by_daniel_defoe_isbn_9788475072401/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/robinson_crusoe_by_daniel_defoe_isbn_9788475072401/</guid>
      <description>Robinson Crusoe by Daniel Defoe Title: Robinson Crusoe Author: Daniel Defoe Review: Robinson Crusoe is a classic adventure story written by Daniel Defoe, first published in 1719. The book tells the tale of Robinson Crusoe, a young man who defies his parents&amp;rsquo; wishes and sets out to sea in search of adventure. After numerous trials and tribulations, including being shipwrecked on a deserted island, Robinson learns the value of hard work, perseverance, and faith.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Something&#39;s Fishy, Hazel Green!</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/somethings_fishy_hazel_green_by_odo_hirsch_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/somethings_fishy_hazel_green_by_odo_hirsch_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Something&amp;rsquo;s Fishy, Hazel Green! by Odo Hirsch Title: Something&amp;rsquo;s Fishy, Hazel Green! Author: Odo Hirsch Review: &amp;ldquo;Something&amp;rsquo;s Fishy, Hazel Green!&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Odo Hirsch, which takes readers on a captivating journey through the eyes of its protagonist, Hazel Green. The story follows Hazel as she sets out to uncover the mystery behind a peculiar smell that has been plaguing her school. The book is primarily targeted towards children between the ages of 7 to 10 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Boy in the Striped Pyjamas</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_boy_in_the_striped_pyjamas_by_john_boyne_isbn_9782070612987/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_boy_in_the_striped_pyjamas_by_john_boyne_isbn_9782070612987/</guid>
      <description>The Boy in the Striped Pyjamas by John Boyne Title: The Boy in the Striped Pyjamas Author: John Boyne Review: The Boy in the Striped Pyjamas is a poignant and thought-provoking children&amp;rsquo;s novel by John Boyne. The story follows the life of a young boy named Bruno, who is the son of a high-ranking Nazi officer. Bruno&amp;rsquo;s family is forced to move to a new home near a concentration camp, where he meets a boy named Shmuel who is imprisoned within the camp.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Children of the New Forest</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_children_of_the_new_forest_isbn_158287395x/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_children_of_the_new_forest_isbn_158287395x/</guid>
      <description>The Children of the New Forest Title: The Children of the New Forest Author: Frederick Marryat Review: The Children of the New Forest is a captivating novel written by Frederick Marryat, originally published in 1847. This historical fiction story is set in the New Forest region of southern England during the English Civil War, and follows the lives of four orphaned children who must learn to survive and coexist in the wilderness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Invention of Hugo Cabret</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_invention_of_hugo_cabret_by_brian_selznick_isbn_9780439813785/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_invention_of_hugo_cabret_by_brian_selznick_isbn_9780439813785/</guid>
      <description>The Invention of Hugo Cabret by Brian Selznick Title: The Invention of Hugo Cabret Author: Brian Selznick Review: The Invention of Hugo Cabret is a beautifully illustrated and captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young orphan named Hugo, who lives in the walls of a busy Paris train station. As a passionate inventor, Hugo discovers a broken automaton, a mechanical man, and becomes determined to fix it. Along his journey, he encounters Georges Méliès, a toy shop owner, and the two form a bond as they uncover the mysteries of the automaton and their own lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fire, Bed and Bone</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/fire_bed_and_bone_by_henrietta_branford_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/fire_bed_and_bone_by_henrietta_branford_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Fire, Bed and Bone by Henrietta Branford Title: Fire, Bed and Bone Author: Henrietta Branford Review: Fire, Bed and Bone is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book by Henrietta Branford that tells the story of a young boy named Robin who, after a series of unfortunate events, finds himself living on the streets of London. The book is a perfect blend of adventure, mystery, and historical fiction, making it an engaging read for children aged 8-12 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/harry_potter_and_the_prisoner_of_azkaban_isbn_9780320037795/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/harry_potter_and_the_prisoner_of_azkaban_isbn_9780320037795/</guid>
      <description>Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban Title: Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban Author: J.K. Rowling Review: Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban is the third installment in the widely popular Harry Potter series by J.K. Rowling. This book is an enchanting tale that follows the adventures of Harry Potter, a young wizard, as he navigates the challenges of his third year at Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Am Susannah</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/i_am_susannah_by_libby_gleeson_isbn_082340742x/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/i_am_susannah_by_libby_gleeson_isbn_082340742x/</guid>
      <description>I Am Susannah by Libby Gleeson Title: I Am Susannah Author: Libby Gleeson Target Age Group: 6-10 years old Review: &amp;ldquo;I Am Susannah&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young girl named Susannah, who embarks on a journey of self-discovery and learns the importance of embracing her unique qualities. The book, written by Libby Gleeson, is an engaging and heartwarming tale that is perfect for children between the ages of 6 and 10 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maniac Magee</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/maniac_magee_isbn_316807222/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/maniac_magee_isbn_316807222/</guid>
      <description>Maniac Magee Title: Maniac Magee Author: Jerry Spinelli Review: Maniac Magee is a heartwarming and engaging children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Jerry Spinelli. The story follows the life of Jeffrey Lionel Magee, also known as Maniac Magee, a young boy who finds himself homeless after a tragic event. Maniac&amp;rsquo;s journey takes him through the racially divided town of Two Mills, where he becomes a legend for his extraordinary athletic abilities and his kind-hearted nature.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Composition</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_composition_isbn_9781305633858/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_composition_isbn_9781305633858/</guid>
      <description>The Composition Title: The Composition Author: Antonia Banyard Genre: Children&amp;rsquo;s Picture Book Target Age Group: 4-8 years old Review: &amp;ldquo;The Composition&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s picture book that tells the story of a young boy named Sam who is tasked with creating a picture for his school&amp;rsquo;s art competition. The book takes readers on a journey as Sam struggles to find inspiration for his artwork, eventually discovering that the beauty of nature can be found in the most unexpected places.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Whipping Boy</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_whipping_boy_isbn_416088120/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_whipping_boy_isbn_416088120/</guid>
      <description>The Whipping Boy Title: The Whipping Boy Author: Sid Fleischman The Whipping Boy is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young prince named Horace and his whipping boy, Jemmy. The whipping boy, Jemmy, is a commoner who receives the punishments for the prince&amp;rsquo;s misbehavior, as it was believed that it would help the prince learn from his mistakes. The book is set in a medieval kingdom and follows the adventures of Horace and Jemmy as they escape from the castle and embark on a thrilling journey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two Weeks With the Queen</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/two_weeks_with_the_queen_by_morris_gleitzman_isbn_3300781/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/two_weeks_with_the_queen_by_morris_gleitzman_isbn_3300781/</guid>
      <description>Two Weeks With the Queen by Morris Gleitzman Title: Two Weeks With the Queen Author: Morris Gleitzman Review: Two Weeks With the Queen is a heartwarming and poignant children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Morris Gleitzman. The story follows the journey of a young boy named Colin, who embarks on a mission to find a cure for his terminally ill brother. Along the way, he encounters various characters, each with their own lessons to teach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Journey to Jo&#39;burg</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/journey_to_joburg_by_beverley_naidoo_isbn_9780064402378/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/journey_to_joburg_by_beverley_naidoo_isbn_9780064402378/</guid>
      <description>Journey to Jo&amp;rsquo;burg by Beverley Naidoo Title: Journey to Jo&amp;rsquo;burg Author: Beverley Naidoo Review: Journey to Jo&amp;rsquo;burg is a heartwarming and thought-provoking children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Beverley Naidoo. The story follows two siblings, Naledi and Tiro, as they embark on a journey from their small village to the big city of Johannesburg in search of their mother. Set against the backdrop of apartheid-era South Africa, the book tackles important themes such as family, friendship, and the struggle for equality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sarah, Plain and Tall</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/sarah_plain_and_tall_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/sarah_plain_and_tall_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Sarah, Plain and Tall Title: Sarah, Plain and Tall Author: Patricia MacLachlan Review: &amp;ldquo;Sarah, Plain and Tall&amp;rdquo; is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Patricia MacLachlan. The story revolves around a widowed father, Jacob Witting, and his two children, Anna and Caleb, who live on a farm in the Midwest. Jacob places an advertisement for a mail-order bride, and Sarah, a woman from Maine, responds to the ad. The book targets children aged 6 to 10 years old and is a perfect blend of emotions, family values, and life lessons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schoolboy Jia Li</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/schoolboy_jia_li_by_qin_wenjun_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/schoolboy_jia_li_by_qin_wenjun_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Schoolboy Jia Li by Qin Wenjun Title: Schoolboy Jia Li Author: Qin Wenjun Schoolboy Jia Li is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Qin Wenjun, which follows the story of a young boy named Jia Li as he navigates through the ups and downs of school life. This heartwarming tale is perfect for children between the ages of 6 and 10, as it addresses various life lessons and challenges that young readers can relate to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sunday&#39;s Child</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/sundays_child_by_gudrun_mebs_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/sundays_child_by_gudrun_mebs_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Sunday&amp;rsquo;s Child by Gudrun Mebs Title: Sunday&amp;rsquo;s Child Author: Gudrun Mebs Review: Sunday&amp;rsquo;s Child is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the story of a young girl named Sunday, who embarks on a journey of self-discovery and growth. The book is beautifully written by Gudrun Mebs, who has a knack for capturing the innocence and wonder of childhood. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 6 and 10, making it a perfect addition to any elementary school classroom or home library.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jacob Have I Loved</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/jacob_have_i_loved_isbn_9788420460819/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/jacob_have_i_loved_isbn_9788420460819/</guid>
      <description>Jacob Have I Loved Title: Jacob Have I Loved Author: Katherine Paterson Review: Jacob Have I Loved is a beautifully written children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of two twin sisters, Sara Louise and Caroline, growing up on an island off the coast of Maryland. The story is narrated by Sara Louise, who is constantly overshadowed by her sister Caroline, who is considered to be the more beautiful and talented twin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nothing to Be Afraid of</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/nothing_to_be_afraid_of_by_jan_mark_isbn_9780722656778/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/nothing_to_be_afraid_of_by_jan_mark_isbn_9780722656778/</guid>
      <description>Nothing to Be Afraid of by Jan Mark Title: &amp;ldquo;Nothing to Be Afraid of&amp;rdquo; Author: Jan Mark Review: &amp;ldquo;Nothing to Be Afraid of&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the adventures of a young boy named Gareth, who is afraid of the dark. Throughout the story, Gareth learns valuable life lessons about facing his fears and finding the courage to overcome them. The book is beautifully illustrated, with vibrant colors and engaging images that will capture the attention of young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Pair of Jesus Boots</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/a_pair_of_jesus_boots_by_sylvia_sherry_isbn_224615769/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/a_pair_of_jesus_boots_by_sylvia_sherry_isbn_224615769/</guid>
      <description>A Pair of Jesus Boots by Sylvia Sherry Title: A Pair of Jesus Boots Author: Sylvia Sherry Review: A Pair of Jesus Boots is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Sylvia Sherry. The story follows a young boy named Timmy, who desperately wants a pair of Jesus Boots - boots that can walk on water just like Jesus did. The book is targeted towards children aged 4-8 years old and is a perfect blend of adventure, imagination, and heartwarming lessons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crusade in Jeans</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/crusade_in_jeans_isbn_9781935954071/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/crusade_in_jeans_isbn_9781935954071/</guid>
      <description>Crusade in Jeans Title: Crusade in Jeans Author: Thea Beckman Review: Crusade in Jeans is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young boy named Dolf, who is unexpectedly transported back in time to the Middle Ages. The book, written by Thea Beckman, is an engaging and thought-provoking adventure that is perfect for children aged 10-14. The story is filled with historical details, and it provides an exciting and immersive way for young readers to learn about the past.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Friday or the Savage Life</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/friday_or_the_savage_life_by_michel_tournier_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/friday_or_the_savage_life_by_michel_tournier_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Friday or the Savage Life by Michel Tournier Title: Friday or the Savage Life Author: Michel Tournier Friday or the Savage Life is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Michel Tournier. The story is set in a remote island where the protagonist, Friday, lives a life of solitude, far away from the hustle and bustle of civilization. The book is a perfect blend of adventure, self-discovery, and the importance of friendship.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Fib</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_fib_by_george_layton_isbn_9780330397957/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_fib_by_george_layton_isbn_9780330397957/</guid>
      <description>The Fib by George Layton Title: The Fib Author: George Layton Review: The Fib is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the story of a young boy named Billy who has a tendency to tell little white lies, or &amp;ldquo;fibs,&amp;rdquo; as he calls them. The book, written by George Layton, is a perfect blend of humor, adventure, and valuable life lessons. Target Age Group: The Fib is suitable for children between the ages of 6 and 10.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ash Road</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/ash_road_by_ivan_southall_isbn_9780140303148/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/ash_road_by_ivan_southall_isbn_9780140303148/</guid>
      <description>Ash Road by Ivan Southall Title: Ash Road Author: Ivan Southall Ash Road is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Ivan Southall, which tells the story of a young boy named David and his journey to find his missing father. The book is targeted towards children aged 8-12 years old, and it provides valuable life lessons through its engaging narrative. The story begins with David and his family living in a small town, struggling to make ends meet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How the Whale Became</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/how_the_whale_became_by_ted_hughes_isbn_9780571056156/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/how_the_whale_became_by_ted_hughes_isbn_9780571056156/</guid>
      <description>How the Whale Became by Ted Hughes Title: How the Whale Became Author: Ted Hughes Review: How the Whale Became is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the renowned poet and author, Ted Hughes. The story revolves around a whale who, in search of its true identity, embarks on a journey to discover its purpose in life. The book is beautifully illustrated by the talented artist, Andrew Davidson, whose vivid and captivating illustrations bring the story to life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Goalkeeper&#39;s Revenge</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_goalkeepers_revenge_by_bill_naughton_isbn_340149418/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_goalkeepers_revenge_by_bill_naughton_isbn_340149418/</guid>
      <description>The Goalkeeper&amp;rsquo;s Revenge by Bill Naughton Title: The Goalkeeper&amp;rsquo;s Revenge Author: Bill Naughton Age Group: 8-12 years old The Goalkeeper&amp;rsquo;s Revenge is a charming and engaging children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Bill Naughton. The story follows the adventures of a young boy named Tommy who dreams of becoming a great soccer player. As Tommy faces various challenges and learns valuable life lessons, the reader is taken on a journey filled with humor, excitement, and heartwarming moments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Winged Watchman</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_winged_watchman_isbn_9780571121007/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_winged_watchman_isbn_9780571121007/</guid>
      <description>The Winged Watchman Title: The Winged Watchman Author: Hilda van Stockum Review: The Winged Watchman is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Hilda van Stockum. This story is set during World War II and follows the lives of two Dutch brothers, Joris and Jochem, who are living in a small village in the Netherlands. The story is filled with adventure, suspense, and heartwarming moments that will captivate young readers. The Winged Watchman is targeted towards children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jennings and Darbishire</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/jennings_and_darbishire_by_anthony_buckeridge_isbn_1621432/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/jennings_and_darbishire_by_anthony_buckeridge_isbn_1621432/</guid>
      <description>Jennings and Darbishire by Anthony Buckeridge Title: Jennings and Darbishire Author: Anthony Buckeridge Review: &amp;ldquo;Jennings and Darbishire&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the talented author Anthony Buckeridge. The story follows the adventures of two young schoolboys, Jennings and Darbishire, as they navigate their way through life at a British boarding school. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old. The relatable characters and engaging storyline make it an enjoyable read for this age group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Princess Who Had Magic Fingers</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_princess_who_had_magic_fingers_by_maria_luisa_gefaell_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_princess_who_had_magic_fingers_by_maria_luisa_gefaell_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Princess Who Had Magic Fingers by Maria Luisa Gefaell Title: The Princess Who Had Magic Fingers Author: Maria Luisa Gefaell The Princess Who Had Magic Fingers is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Maria Luisa Gefaell. This enchanting story is perfect for children aged 4-8 years old, as it features captivating illustrations and a simple yet engaging narrative. The story follows a young princess who discovers that she has magical fingers that can create beautiful art.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Red Pony</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_red_pony_by_john_steinbeck_isbn_8700222410/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_red_pony_by_john_steinbeck_isbn_8700222410/</guid>
      <description>The Red Pony by John Steinbeck Title: The Red Pony Author: John Steinbeck Review: The Red Pony is a beautifully written children&amp;rsquo;s book by the renowned author John Steinbeck. The book consists of four interconnected stories that revolve around a young boy named Jody and his experiences with various ponies and horses on his family&amp;rsquo;s ranch. The Red Pony is an excellent choice for children aged 8-12 years old, as it provides a captivating and engaging narrative that keeps young readers entertained while teaching valuable life lessons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Adventures of Huckleberry Finn</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_adventures_of_huckleberry_finn_by_mark_twain_isbn_8190732617/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_adventures_of_huckleberry_finn_by_mark_twain_isbn_8190732617/</guid>
      <description>The Adventures of Huckleberry Finn by Mark Twain Title: The Adventures of Huckleberry Finn Author: Mark Twain Review: The Adventures of Huckleberry Finn is a classic American novel written by Mark Twain, which has been cherished by readers for generations. The story follows the adventures of a young boy named Huckleberry Finn, who escapes his abusive father and sets sail on a raft down the Mississippi River with a runaway slave named Jim.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Paul Street Boys</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_paul_street_boys_by_ferenc_maln%C3%A1r_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_paul_street_boys_by_ferenc_maln%C3%A1r_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Paul Street Boys by Ferenc Malnár Title: The Paul Street Boys Author: Ferenc Malnár Review: The Paul Street Boys is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Ferenc Malnár, which tells the story of a group of young boys living in the Paul Street neighborhood. The book is a perfect blend of adventure, friendship, and the challenges faced by children growing up. The story takes place in Budapest during the early 20th century, which adds a historical aspect to the narrative.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tom Sawyer</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/tom_sawyer_isbn_9798417467929/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/tom_sawyer_isbn_9798417467929/</guid>
      <description>Tom Sawyer Title: The Adventures of Tom Sawyer Author: Mark Twain Review: The Adventures of Tom Sawyer is a timeless classic written by Mark Twain, which takes the reader on a thrilling journey through the eyes of a young boy named Tom Sawyer. The story is set in the small town of St. Petersburg, Missouri, and follows Tom&amp;rsquo;s adventures with his friends, particularly Huckleberry Finn. The book is suitable for children between the ages of 8 and 12, as it contains elements of fun, mischief, and learning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Robinson the Younger</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/robinson_the_younger_by_johann_heinrich_campe_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/robinson_the_younger_by_johann_heinrich_campe_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Robinson the Younger by Johann Heinrich Campe Title: Robinson the Younger Author: Johann Heinrich Campe Review: Robinson the Younger is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Johann Heinrich Campe, which is a sequel to the popular story of Robinson Crusoe. This book is a perfect blend of adventure, self-discovery, and moral lessons that are relatable to children of various ages. The story follows the journey of Robinson the Younger, who is the son of the famous Robinson Crusoe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tales From Shakespeare</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/tales_from_shakespeare_isbn_9780786103997/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/tales_from_shakespeare_isbn_9780786103997/</guid>
      <description>Tales From Shakespeare Title: Tales From Shakespeare Author: Charles and Mary Lamb Recommended Age Group: 8-12 years old Tales From Shakespeare is a beautifully written and illustrated collection of stories adapted from the works of the famous playwright, William Shakespeare. The book is a perfect introduction to Shakespeare&amp;rsquo;s world for young readers, as it presents the tales in a simplified and easy-to-understand manner. The stories in Tales From Shakespeare cover a wide range of themes and life lessons, including love, friendship, betrayal, and the importance of honesty and integrity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Death Book</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_death_book_by_pernilla_stalfelt_isbn_888994826/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_death_book_by_pernilla_stalfelt_isbn_888994826/</guid>
      <description>The Death Book by Pernilla Stalfelt Title: The Death Book Author: Pernilla Stalfelt The Death Book, written by Pernilla Stalfelt, is a beautifully illustrated and thoughtfully written children&amp;rsquo;s book that addresses the sensitive topic of death in a manner that is both age-appropriate and comforting. The book targets children between the ages of 4 and 8, making it an excellent choice for parents, educators, and caregivers looking to initiate conversations about this important subject with young children.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Balloon for Grandad</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/a_balloon_for_grandad_by_nigel_gray_isbn_9780531057551/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/a_balloon_for_grandad_by_nigel_gray_isbn_9780531057551/</guid>
      <description>A Balloon for Grandad by Nigel Gray Title: A Balloon for Grandad Author: Nigel Gray Review: A Balloon for Grandad is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Nigel Gray, which tells the story of a young boy named Tom who wants to find a special gift for his grandfather. The book is beautifully illustrated and captures the bond between a grandchild and their grandparent. The target age group for this book is children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joyful Noise: Poems for Two Voices by Paul Fleischman</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/joyful_noise_poems_for_two_voices_isbn_590981838/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/joyful_noise_poems_for_two_voices_isbn_590981838/</guid>
      <description>Joyful Noise: Poems for Two Voices Title: Joyful Noise: Poems for Two Voices Author: Paul Fleischman Age Group: 6-10 years old &amp;ldquo;Joyful Noise: Poems for Two Voices&amp;rdquo; is a delightful and engaging collection of poems written by Paul Fleischman, specifically designed for two people to read aloud together. This book is perfect for children aged 6-10 years old, as it encourages collaboration, creativity, and a love for poetry. The book features a variety of poems, each with its own unique theme and message.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matilda</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/matilda_isbn_9780754065098/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/matilda_isbn_9780754065098/</guid>
      <description>Matilda Title: Matilda Author: Roald Dahl Matilda, written by the renowned children&amp;rsquo;s author Roald Dahl, is a captivating and heartwarming story that follows the life of a young girl named Matilda. This book is a perfect choice for children aged 7 to 12 years old, as it explores themes of courage, resilience, and the power of intelligence. The story revolves around Matilda, a precocious and brilliant young girl who has a passion for books and learning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Big Sister</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_big_sister_by_siv_widerberg_isbn_9129591864/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_big_sister_by_siv_widerberg_isbn_9129591864/</guid>
      <description>The Big Sister by Siv Widerberg Title: The Big Sister Author: Siv Widerberg Review: The Big Sister is a heartwarming and beautifully illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young girl who becomes a big sister for the first time. This book is perfect for children between the ages of 3 and 8, as it captures the excitement and challenges of welcoming a new sibling into the family. The story follows the protagonist as she navigates the complex emotions of being a big sister, including jealousy, pride, and love.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Borka</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/borka_by_john_burningham_isbn_1856811727/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/borka_by_john_burningham_isbn_1856811727/</guid>
      <description>Borka by John Burningham Title: Borka Author: John Burningham Review: Borka is a heartwarming and engaging children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the talented John Burningham. The story follows the adventures of a young duckling named Borka, who is accidentally separated from his family and embarks on a journey to find his way back home. The book is beautifully illustrated with vibrant colors and detailed drawings that capture the essence of the story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Doll&#39;s House</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_dolls_house_by_rumer_godden_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_dolls_house_by_rumer_godden_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Doll&amp;rsquo;s House by Rumer Godden Title: The Doll&amp;rsquo;s House Author: Rumer Godden The Doll&amp;rsquo;s House, written by Rumer Godden, is a charming and enchanting children&amp;rsquo;s book that captures the essence of childhood imagination and the importance of friendship. The story revolves around two young sisters, Tottie and Emily, who receive a beautiful dollhouse as a gift. The dollhouse becomes a magical world where the dolls come to life and experience their own adventures.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
