<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Childrens Books that talk about &#39;Grace&#39; on Monsty The Monster Truck</title>
    <link>https://www.monsty.co/tags/childrens-books-that-talk-about-grace/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Childrens Books that talk about &#39;Grace&#39; on Monsty The Monster Truck</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.monsty.co/tags/childrens-books-that-talk-about-grace/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Finding Violet Park</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/finding_violet_park_by_jenny_valentine_isbn_7291248/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/finding_violet_park_by_jenny_valentine_isbn_7291248/</guid>
      <description>Finding Violet Park by Jenny Valentine Title: Finding Violet Park Author: Jenny Valentine Review: Finding Violet Park is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Jenny Valentine, which tells the story of a young boy named Lucas who embarks on a journey to find the mysterious Violet Park. The book is suitable for children aged 8-12 years old, as it contains elements of adventure, mystery, and self-discovery. The story follows Lucas as he navigates through various challenges and obstacles in his quest to find Violet Park.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I Live Now</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/how_i_live_now_isbn_9783596811106/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/how_i_live_now_isbn_9783596811106/</guid>
      <description>How I Live Now Title: How I Live Now Author: Meg Rosoff Target Age Group: 12-18 years old Review: How I Live Now is a poignant and thought-provoking novel by Meg Rosoff, which explores the themes of love, war, and self-discovery through the eyes of a young teenage girl named Daisy. The story is set in a dystopian future where war has broken out, and Daisy is forced to navigate the challenges of her new life on her cousin&amp;rsquo;s farm in the English countryside.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Policeman</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/new_policeman_by_kate_thompson_isbn_61831271/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/new_policeman_by_kate_thompson_isbn_61831271/</guid>
      <description>New Policeman by Kate Thompson Title: The New Policeman Author: Kate Thompson Review: The New Policeman is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Kate Thompson, which takes the readers on a magical adventure filled with music, mystery, and time travel. The story follows the journey of a young boy named J.J. Liddy, who discovers a secret passage to the land of Faerie, where time is running out. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 8 to 12 years old, and it beautifully blends the elements of fantasy, adventure, and music.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alex</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/alex_by_tessa_duder_isbn_9780195581690/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/alex_by_tessa_duder_isbn_9780195581690/</guid>
      <description>Alex by Tessa Duder Title: Alex Author: Tessa Duder Review: &amp;ldquo;Alex&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Tessa Duder, which follows the adventures of a young girl named Alex as she navigates the challenges of growing up. The book is a perfect fit for children between the ages of 8 and 12, as it addresses themes that are relatable to this age group, such as friendship, self-discovery, and overcoming obstacles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dear Nobody</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/dear_nobody_isbn_531086119/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/dear_nobody_isbn_531086119/</guid>
      <description>Dear Nobody Title: Dear Nobody Author: Berlie Doherty Recommended Age Group: 8-12 years old Dear Nobody is a heartwarming and thought-provoking children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Berlie Doherty. The story revolves around two main characters, Helen and Chris, who are both dealing with the challenges of growing up and navigating their emotions. The book is written in a diary format, with Helen and Chris taking turns to share their thoughts and feelings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flour Babies</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/flour_babies_isbn_9780316283199/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/flour_babies_isbn_9780316283199/</guid>
      <description>Flour Babies Title: Flour Babies Author: Anne Fine Flour Babies is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Anne Fine, which was first published in 1992. The story revolves around a group of elementary school students who are given flour sacks as their &amp;lsquo;babies&amp;rsquo; to take care of, as part of a school project. The project aims to teach the students about the responsibilities and challenges of parenthood. The book is suitable for children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Switchers</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/switchers_by_kate_thompson_isbn_9781480424203/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/switchers_by_kate_thompson_isbn_9781480424203/</guid>
      <description>Switchers by Kate Thompson Title: Switchers Author: Kate Thompson Review: Switchers is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the adventures of two young teenagers, Tess and Kevin, who discover they have the ability to &amp;lsquo;switch&amp;rsquo; into the bodies of other creatures. The story is set in Ireland and beautifully captures the essence of Irish folklore and mythology. The target age group for this book is 8-12 years old. The language used is simple yet engaging, making it an enjoyable read for young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Visits</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_visits_by_silvia_schujer_isbn_9789707704459/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_visits_by_silvia_schujer_isbn_9789707704459/</guid>
      <description>The Visits by Silvia Schujer Title: The Visits Author: Silvia Schujer Genre: Children&amp;rsquo;s Fiction, Ages 8-12 The Visits is a heartwarming and enchanting children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Silvia Schujer. This beautifully crafted story takes readers on a journey through the eyes of a young girl named Luna, who embarks on a series of magical adventures with her grandmother. The book is geared towards children between the ages of 8 and 12, and it is a perfect read for both independent readers and as a bedtime story for younger children.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Girl of the Limberlost</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/a_girl_of_the_limberlost_by_gene_stratton-porter_isbn_9780517072356/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/a_girl_of_the_limberlost_by_gene_stratton-porter_isbn_9780517072356/</guid>
      <description>A Girl of the Limberlost by Gene Stratton-Porter Title: A Girl of the Limberlost Author: Gene Stratton-Porter A Girl of the Limberlost is a beautifully written classic children&amp;rsquo;s book by Gene Stratton-Porter. The story follows the life of a young girl named Elnora Comstock, who lives in the swamps of the Limberlost forest in Indiana. Elnora&amp;rsquo;s mother has passed away, and her father is cold and distant, leaving her to navigate the challenges of life on her own.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Picnic at Hanging Rock</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/picnic_at_hanging_rock_isbn_582081742/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/picnic_at_hanging_rock_isbn_582081742/</guid>
      <description>Picnic at Hanging Rock Title: Picnic at Hanging Rock Author: Joan Lindsay Genre: Mystery/Historical Fiction Recommended Age Group: 10-14 years old &amp;ldquo;Picnic at Hanging Rock&amp;rdquo; is a captivating mystery novel written by Joan Lindsay, which tells the story of a group of schoolgirls and their governess who venture on a picnic to the enigmatic Hanging Rock on Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day in 1900. The book, set in Australia, has been adapted into a successful film and a television series, and it continues to captivate readers of all ages with its haunting tale and unanswered questions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Outsiders</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_outsiders_isbn_9780739339015/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_outsiders_isbn_9780739339015/</guid>
      <description>The Outsiders Title: The Outsiders Author: S.E. Hinton Review: The Outsiders is a classic coming-of-age novel written by S.E. Hinton, first published in 1967. The story is set in the 1960s and revolves around the lives of two rival gangs, the Greasers and the Socs, in Oklahoma. The narrative follows the experiences of Ponyboy Curtis, a young Greaser, as he navigates the challenges of growing up, dealing with the loss of loved ones, and questioning the societal divisions that exist between the two groups.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Series of Unfortunate Events #1: The Bad Beginning: The Short-Lived</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/a_series_of_unfortunate_events_#1_the_bad_beginning_the_short-lived_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/a_series_of_unfortunate_events_#1_the_bad_beginning_the_short-lived_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>A Series of Unfortunate Events #1: The Bad Beginning: The Short-Lived Title: A Series of Unfortunate Events #1: The Bad Beginning: The Short-Lived Author: Lemony Snicket Review: A Series of Unfortunate Events #1: The Bad Beginning: The Short-Lived is a captivating and engaging children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the story of the Baudelaire siblings, Violet, Klaus, and Sunny, as they navigate through the unfortunate events that befall them after the tragic death of their parents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rabbit and Coyote</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/rabbit_and_coyote_by_beatriz_donnet_isbn_9789706438294/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/rabbit_and_coyote_by_beatriz_donnet_isbn_9789706438294/</guid>
      <description>Rabbit and Coyote by Beatriz Donnet Title: Rabbit and Coyote Author: Beatriz Donnet Review: &amp;ldquo;Rabbit and Coyote&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a mischievous rabbit who constantly outwits a hungry coyote. The story is set in a vibrant and colorful South American landscape, and the illustrations are both engaging and educational. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 4 to 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Field Guide</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_field_guide_by_tony_diterlizzi_and_holly_black_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_field_guide_by_tony_diterlizzi_and_holly_black_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Field Guide by Tony Diterlizzi and Holly Black Title: The Field Guide Author: Tony Diterlizzi and Holly Black The Field Guide is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Tony Diterlizzi and Holly Black. The story follows the adventures of two young siblings, Jared and Simon Grace, who discover a hidden world of fairies and other magical creatures in their backyard. The book is geared towards children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clockwork</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/clockwork_isbn_345354435/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/clockwork_isbn_345354435/</guid>
      <description>Clockwork Title: Clockwork Author: Philip Pullman Review: Clockwork, written by the talented Philip Pullman, is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes young readers on an enchanting journey through a world of intricate clockwork mechanisms and exciting adventures. The story follows the life of a young apprentice named Karl, who discovers a mysterious clockwork knight that sets off a chain of events that will change his life forever. Target Age Group: This book is best suited for children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mouth Open, Story Jump Out</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/mouth_open_story_jump_out_by_grace_hallworth_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/mouth_open_story_jump_out_by_grace_hallworth_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Mouth Open, Story Jump Out by Grace Hallworth Title: Mouth Open, Story Jump Out Author: Grace Hallworth &amp;ldquo;Mouth Open, Story Jump Out&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Grace Hallworth, which is perfect for young readers between the ages of 5 and 8. The book is filled with charming illustrations and engaging stories that capture the imagination of its young audience. The book is divided into several short stories, each one featuring a unique character and a valuable life lesson.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nothing to Be Afraid of</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/nothing_to_be_afraid_of_by_jan_mark_isbn_9780722656778/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/nothing_to_be_afraid_of_by_jan_mark_isbn_9780722656778/</guid>
      <description>Nothing to Be Afraid of by Jan Mark Title: &amp;ldquo;Nothing to Be Afraid of&amp;rdquo; Author: Jan Mark Review: &amp;ldquo;Nothing to Be Afraid of&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the adventures of a young boy named Gareth, who is afraid of the dark. Throughout the story, Gareth learns valuable life lessons about facing his fears and finding the courage to overcome them. The book is beautifully illustrated, with vibrant colors and engaging images that will capture the attention of young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Snow Spider Trilogy</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_snow_spider_trilogy_isbn_9780749707446/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_snow_spider_trilogy_isbn_9780749707446/</guid>
      <description>The Snow Spider Trilogy Title: The Snow Spider Trilogy Author: Jenny Nimmo Genre: Children&amp;rsquo;s Fiction, Fantasy Age Group: 8-12 years old The Snow Spider Trilogy is a captivating and magical children&amp;rsquo;s book series written by Jenny Nimmo. This enchanting trilogy follows the adventures of Gwyn Griffiths, a young boy who discovers he has inherited magical powers from his Welsh ancestors. The series is divided into three books: The Snow Spider, Emlyn&amp;rsquo;s Moon, and The Chestnut Soldier.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two Weeks With the Queen</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/two_weeks_with_the_queen_by_morris_gleitzman_isbn_3300781/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/two_weeks_with_the_queen_by_morris_gleitzman_isbn_3300781/</guid>
      <description>Two Weeks With the Queen by Morris Gleitzman Title: Two Weeks With the Queen Author: Morris Gleitzman Review: Two Weeks With the Queen is a heartwarming and poignant children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Morris Gleitzman. The story follows the journey of a young boy named Colin, who embarks on a mission to find a cure for his terminally ill brother. Along the way, he encounters various characters, each with their own lessons to teach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Garden</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_garden_by_jiri_trnka_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_garden_by_jiri_trnka_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Garden by Jiri Trnka Title: The Garden Author: Jiri Trnka The Garden is a beautifully illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book by Jiri Trnka, which tells the story of a young boy named John who embarks on a magical adventure in a mysterious garden. This book is a perfect read for children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old, as it is filled with vibrant pictures and simple yet engaging text.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Little Princess</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/a_little_princess_isbn_9781417601356/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/a_little_princess_isbn_9781417601356/</guid>
      <description>A Little Princess Title: A Little Princess Author: Frances Hodgson Burnett Review: A Little Princess is a timeless classic written by Frances Hodgson Burnett, which tells the story of a young girl named Sara Crewe who attends a boarding school in London. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 8 and 12, and is a perfect blend of imagination, adventure, and valuable life lessons. The story follows Sara Crewe, a kind and intelligent girl who is suddenly forced to face hardship and adversity when she loses her father and is left penniless.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ballet Shoes</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/ballet_shoes_by_noel_streatfeild_isbn_1400094976/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/ballet_shoes_by_noel_streatfeild_isbn_1400094976/</guid>
      <description>Ballet Shoes by Noel Streatfeild Title: Ballet Shoes Author: Noel Streatfeild &amp;ldquo;Ballet Shoes&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Noel Streatfeild. The story revolves around three orphaned sisters, Pauline, Petrova, and Posy, who are sent to live with their eccentric and absent-minded great-uncle, Matthew, and his no-nonsense housekeeper, Sylvia. As the sisters grow up, they each discover their own unique talents and passions, with Pauline excelling in acting, Petrova in aviation, and Posy in ballet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are We There Yet?</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/are_we_there_yet_by_alison_lester_isbn_670880671/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/are_we_there_yet_by_alison_lester_isbn_670880671/</guid>
      <description>Are We There Yet? by Alison Lester Title: Are We There Yet? Author: Alison Lester Review: Are We There Yet? is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Alison Lester, which takes young readers on an exciting journey across Australia. The story follows Grace and her family as they embark on a road trip from their home in Melbourne to visit relatives in far-off Western Australia. The book is filled with vibrant illustrations and engaging storytelling, making it a perfect choice for children between the ages of 4 and 8.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Boy Who Grew Flowers</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_boy_who_grew_flowers_by_jen_wojtowicz_isbn_1846867495/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_boy_who_grew_flowers_by_jen_wojtowicz_isbn_1846867495/</guid>
      <description>The Boy Who Grew Flowers by Jen Wojtowicz Title: The Boy Who Grew Flowers Author: Jen Wojtowicz Review: The Boy Who Grew Flowers is a heartwarming and imaginative children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Jen Wojtowicz. The story follows a young boy named Rink, who possesses a unique ability to grow flowers from his body. Initially, Rink feels embarrassed and isolated due to his extraordinary gift, but he eventually learns to embrace his differences and make friends with a kind and understanding girl named Angelina.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apoutsiak</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/apoutsiak_by_paul-emile_victor_isbn_9782081604452/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/apoutsiak_by_paul-emile_victor_isbn_9782081604452/</guid>
      <description>Apoutsiak by Paul-Emile Victor Title: Apoutsiak Author: Paul-Emile Victor Review: Apoutsiak is a beautifully illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young Inuit boy named Apoutsiak who goes on a thrilling adventure with his family. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 5 and 10, and it offers a wonderful blend of adventure, cultural exploration, and important life lessons. The story begins with Apoutsiak and his family embarking on a journey to find a new place to live.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Captain Pugwash</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/captain_pugwash_by_john_ryan_isbn_859680169/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/captain_pugwash_by_john_ryan_isbn_859680169/</guid>
      <description>Captain Pugwash by John Ryan Title: Captain Pugwash Author: John Ryan Review: Captain Pugwash is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes readers on a thrilling adventure with its lovable characters and engaging storyline. The book, written by John Ryan, is an ideal read for children between the ages of 5 and 10 years old. The story revolves around the charming Captain Pugwash, a pirate captain, and his trusty crew as they embark on a treasure hunt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazing Grace</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/amazing_grace_isbn_9781423320166/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/amazing_grace_isbn_9781423320166/</guid>
      <description>Amazing Grace Title: Amazing Grace Author: Mary Hoffman Illustrator: Caroline Binch Amazing Grace is a beautifully illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young girl named Grace who loves to act out stories and dreams of being in a play. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 4 to 8 years old, as it features simple language and engaging illustrations that will capture the attention of young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
