<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Childrens Books that talk about &#39;Renew&#39; on Monsty The Monster Truck</title>
    <link>https://www.monsty.co/tags/childrens-books-that-talk-about-renew/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Childrens Books that talk about &#39;Renew&#39; on Monsty The Monster Truck</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.monsty.co/tags/childrens-books-that-talk-about-renew/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The October Child</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_october_child_by_eleanor_spence_isbn_340605480/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_october_child_by_eleanor_spence_isbn_340605480/</guid>
      <description>The October Child by Eleanor Spence Title: The October Child Author: Eleanor Spence Review: The October Child is a beautifully written and illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book that captures the essence of the changing seasons and the magic of childhood. The story follows a young girl named October, who is born on the first day of October and experiences the world around her through the lens of the changing seasons. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maniac Magee</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/maniac_magee_isbn_316807222/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/maniac_magee_isbn_316807222/</guid>
      <description>Maniac Magee Title: Maniac Magee Author: Jerry Spinelli Review: Maniac Magee is a heartwarming and engaging children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Jerry Spinelli. The story follows the life of Jeffrey Lionel Magee, also known as Maniac Magee, a young boy who finds himself homeless after a tragic event. Maniac&amp;rsquo;s journey takes him through the racially divided town of Two Mills, where he becomes a legend for his extraordinary athletic abilities and his kind-hearted nature.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Story of Tracy Beaker</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_story_of_tracy_beaker_isbn_9781855497887/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_story_of_tracy_beaker_isbn_9781855497887/</guid>
      <description>The Story of Tracy Beaker Title: The Story of Tracy Beaker Author: Jacqueline Wilson The Story of Tracy Beaker is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the talented Jacqueline Wilson. The story revolves around a 10-year-old girl named Tracy, who lives in a children&amp;rsquo;s home and dreams of finding a loving family to adopt her. Tracy is a spunky, independent, and sometimes mischievous character who is easy to love and root for.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
