<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Childrens Books that talk about &#39;Self-Worth&#39; on Monsty The Monster Truck</title>
    <link>https://www.monsty.co/tags/childrens-books-that-talk-about-self-worth/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Childrens Books that talk about &#39;Self-Worth&#39; on Monsty The Monster Truck</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.monsty.co/tags/childrens-books-that-talk-about-self-worth/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A Parcel of Patterns</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/a_parcel_of_patterns_by_jill_paton_walsh_isbn_722658982/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/a_parcel_of_patterns_by_jill_paton_walsh_isbn_722658982/</guid>
      <description>A Parcel of Patterns by Jill Paton Walsh Title: A Parcel of Patterns Author: Jill Paton Walsh A Parcel of Patterns is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book by Jill Paton Walsh, set in the 17th century during the time of the Great Plague. The story revolves around a young girl named Matilda, who lives in the village of Eyam. When the plague strikes, Matilda&amp;rsquo;s life takes a dramatic turn, and she must learn to cope with the challenges that come her way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Cloud</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_cloud_by_gudrun_pausewang_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_cloud_by_gudrun_pausewang_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Cloud by Gudrun Pausewang Title: The Cloud Author: Gudrun Pausewang Review: The Cloud is a thought-provoking and captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book by Gudrun Pausewang that takes young readers on a journey through a post-apocalyptic world. This book is suitable for children between the ages of 8 and 12, and it effectively teaches important life lessons through its engaging storyline. The story follows a young girl named Sanna, who lives in a small village with her family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Kestrel for a Knave</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/a_kestrel_for_a_knave_isbn_1858481465/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/a_kestrel_for_a_knave_isbn_1858481465/</guid>
      <description>A Kestrel for a Knave Title: A Kestrel for a Knave Author: Barry Hines Recommended Age Group: 10-14 years old A Kestrel for a Knave is a captivating and thought-provoking novel by Barry Hines, which tells the story of Billy Casper, a young boy from a working-class family in a small English town. The book is a perfect blend of emotions, struggles, and triumphs, making it an excellent read for children between the ages of 10 and 14.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer of the Swans by Betsy Byars</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/summer_of_the_swans_isbn_9780613806947/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/summer_of_the_swans_isbn_9780613806947/</guid>
      <description>Summer of the Swans Title: Summer of the Swans Author: Betsy Byars Recommended Age Group: 8-12 years old Review: Summer of the Swans is a heartwarming and thought-provoking children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Betsy Byars. The story revolves around a young girl named Sara who embarks on a journey of self-discovery and personal growth during a memorable summer. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old, as it explores themes of family, friendship, and the importance of self-worth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Friends</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_friends_by_rosa_guy_isbn_9780808554028/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_friends_by_rosa_guy_isbn_9780808554028/</guid>
      <description>The Friends by Rosa Guy Title: The Friends Author: Rosa Guy Review: The Friends is a heartwarming and thought-provoking children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Rosa Guy. This book is a perfect fit for children aged 8-12 years old, as it delves into themes of friendship, understanding, and acceptance. The story revolves around two young girls, Phyllisia and Celie, who come from different cultural backgrounds but develop a strong bond of friendship. Throughout the book, the author beautifully portrays the importance of embracing diversity and understanding the experiences of others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where the Lilies Bloom</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/where_the_lilies_bloom_isbn_881032913/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/where_the_lilies_bloom_isbn_881032913/</guid>
      <description>Where the Lilies Bloom Title: Where the Lilies Bloom Author: Vera Cleaver and Bill Cleaver Review: &amp;ldquo;Where the Lilies Bloom&amp;rdquo; is a heartwarming and inspiring children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a family living in the Appalachian Mountains. The story follows the lives of Mary Call, her siblings, and their struggle to survive after their father&amp;rsquo;s death. The book is suitable for children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tom Brown&#39;s School Days</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/tom_browns_school_days_by_thomas_hughes_isbn_9781096966081/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/tom_browns_school_days_by_thomas_hughes_isbn_9781096966081/</guid>
      <description>Tom Brown&amp;rsquo;s School Days by Thomas Hughes Title: Tom Brown&amp;rsquo;s School Days Author: Thomas Hughes Review: Tom Brown&amp;rsquo;s School Days is a classic children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Thomas Hughes, first published in 1857. The story follows the life of Tom Brown, a young boy who attends Rugby School, a boarding school in England. The book is set in the early 19th century and provides an insightful look into the life of a schoolboy during that time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Painted House</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_painted_house_by_montserrate_del_amo_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_painted_house_by_montserrate_del_amo_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Painted House by Montserrate Del Amo Title: The Painted House Author: Montserrate Del Amo Review: The Painted House is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that captures the imagination of young readers with its vibrant illustrations and heartwarming story. The book is perfect for children aged 4-8, as it is both engaging and educational. The story follows the adventures of a young girl named Lily, who loves to paint and dreams of creating a colorful world around her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Me in the Middle</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/me_in_the_middle_by_ana_maria_machado_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/me_in_the_middle_by_ana_maria_machado_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Me in the Middle by Ana Maria Machado Title: Me in the Middle Author: Ana Maria Machado Review: Me in the Middle is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young girl who finds herself caught in the middle of her family&amp;rsquo;s dynamics. The book is written by Ana Maria Machado, who has beautifully captured the essence of family life and the challenges that come with being a middle child.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Valley of the Fireflies</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_valley_of_the_fireflies_by_gloria_cecilia_diaz_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_valley_of_the_fireflies_by_gloria_cecilia_diaz_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Valley of the Fireflies by Gloria Cecilia Diaz Title: The Valley of the Fireflies Author: Gloria Cecilia Diaz The Valley of the Fireflies is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Gloria Cecilia Diaz, which takes readers on a magical journey through a mystical land filled with enchanting creatures and valuable life lessons. The book is primarily targeted at children between the ages of 7 and 12, although it can be enjoyed by readers of all ages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kubula and Kuba Kubikula</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/kubula_and_kuba_kubikula_by_vladisla_vancura_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/kubula_and_kuba_kubikula_by_vladisla_vancura_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Kubula and Kuba Kubikula by Vladisla Vancura Title: Kubula and Kuba Kubikula Author: Vladislav Vancura Review: Kubula and Kuba Kubikula is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Vladislav Vancura. The story follows the adventures of two young friends, Kubula and Kuba Kubikula, as they explore their world and learn valuable life lessons along the way. The book is beautifully illustrated, with vibrant colors and engaging images that capture the imagination of young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Celia Says</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/what_celia_says_by_elena_fortun_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/what_celia_says_by_elena_fortun_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>What Celia Says by Elena Fortun Title: What Celia Says Author: Elena Fortun &amp;ldquo;What Celia Says&amp;rdquo; is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Elena Fortun, which tells the story of a young girl named Celia who has a unique way of looking at the world. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 5 to 10 years old, and it is an excellent choice for parents and teachers looking for a book that teaches valuable life lessons in a fun and engaging manner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snip Snap</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/snip_snap_by_mara_bergman_isbn_9780060777548/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/snip_snap_by_mara_bergman_isbn_9780060777548/</guid>
      <description>Snip Snap by Mara Bergman Title: Snip Snap Author: Mara Bergman Snip Snap is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Mara Bergman, which takes young readers on a magical adventure through the world of whimsical creatures. The book is filled with vibrant illustrations by the talented Nick Maland, which adds to the overall charm of the story. Target Age Group: Snip Snap is best suited for children between the ages of 4 to 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Love Book</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_love_book_by_pernilla_stalfelt_isbn_888994559/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_love_book_by_pernilla_stalfelt_isbn_888994559/</guid>
      <description>The Love Book by Pernilla Stalfelt Title: The Love Book Author: Pernilla Stalfelt Review: The Love Book by Pernilla Stalfelt is a heartwarming and visually stunning children&amp;rsquo;s book that beautifully captures the essence of love and kindness. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 4 to 8 years old and is a perfect addition to any child&amp;rsquo;s library. The Love Book is a vibrant and imaginative exploration of love, showcasing the many ways love can be expressed and experienced.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where the Sidewalk Ends</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/where_the_sidewalk_ends_by_shel_silverstein_isbn_9780590134699/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/where_the_sidewalk_ends_by_shel_silverstein_isbn_9780590134699/</guid>
      <description>Where the Sidewalk Ends by Shel Silverstein Title: Where the Sidewalk Ends Author: Shel Silverstein &amp;ldquo;Where the Sidewalk Ends&amp;rdquo; is a delightful collection of poems and illustrations by the renowned author and illustrator Shel Silverstein. This book is a treasure trove of whimsical, imaginative, and thought-provoking poems that cater to children between the ages of 6 to 12 years old. The poems in &amp;ldquo;Where the Sidewalk Ends&amp;rdquo; touch upon various themes such as friendship, imagination, self-expression, and the importance of embracing one&amp;rsquo;s individuality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harold and the Purple Crayon</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/harold_and_the_purple_crayon_isbn_9780439132534/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/harold_and_the_purple_crayon_isbn_9780439132534/</guid>
      <description>Harold and the Purple Crayon Title: Harold and the Purple Crayon Author: Crockett Johnson Recommended Age Group: 4-8 years old &amp;ldquo;Harold and the Purple Crayon&amp;rdquo; is a timeless classic that has been enjoyed by children for generations. The story follows the adventures of a young boy named Harold, who uses his purple crayon to create a world of his own. This imaginative tale teaches valuable life lessons and is perfect for children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little Tim and the Brave Sea Captain</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/little_tim_and_the_brave_sea_captain_by_edward_ardizzone_isbn_809810425/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/little_tim_and_the_brave_sea_captain_by_edward_ardizzone_isbn_809810425/</guid>
      <description>Little Tim and the Brave Sea Captain by Edward Ardizzone Title: Little Tim and the Brave Sea Captain Author: Edward Ardizzone Review: Little Tim and the Brave Sea Captain is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written and illustrated by Edward Ardizzone. The story follows the adventures of Little Tim, a young boy who dreams of becoming a sailor. Tim&amp;rsquo;s journey takes him on a thrilling sea voyage, where he encounters various challenges and learns valuable life lessons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Little Red Engine Gets a Name</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_little_red_engine_gets_a_name_by_diana_ross_isbn_571064396/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_little_red_engine_gets_a_name_by_diana_ross_isbn_571064396/</guid>
      <description>The Little Red Engine Gets a Name by Diana Ross Title: The Little Red Engine Gets a Name Author: Diana Ross Review: The Little Red Engine Gets a Name is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Diana Ross. This delightful story follows the adventures of a little red engine who doesn&amp;rsquo;t have a name. The little red engine embarks on a journey to find a name that truly represents who they are.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unknown or Forgotten Princesses</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/unknown_or_forgotten_princesses_by_philippe_lechermeier_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/unknown_or_forgotten_princesses_by_philippe_lechermeier_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Unknown or Forgotten Princesses by Philippe Lechermeier Title: Unknown or Forgotten Princesses Author: Philippe Lechermeier Review: Unknown or Forgotten Princesses is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes young readers on a magical journey through the lives of lesser-known princesses from around the world. Author Philippe Lechermeier has done an excellent job of bringing these fascinating stories to life, making the book both educational and entertaining. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 6 and 10, and it is a perfect blend of history, culture, and adventure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guess How Much I Love You</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/guess_how_much_i_love_you_isbn_9783794142170/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/guess_how_much_i_love_you_isbn_9783794142170/</guid>
      <description>Guess How Much I Love You Title: Guess How Much I Love You Author: Sam McBratney Illustrator: Anita Jeram Recommended Age Group: 3-7 years old &amp;ldquo;Guess How Much I Love You&amp;rdquo; is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of Big Nutbrown Hare and Little Nutbrown Hare, who try to express how much they love each other. The story is a beautiful depiction of the bond between parents and their children, as well as the unconditional love that exists between family members.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pumpkin Soup</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/pumpkin_soup_by_helen_cooper_isbn_374460310/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/pumpkin_soup_by_helen_cooper_isbn_374460310/</guid>
      <description>Pumpkin Soup by Helen Cooper Title: Pumpkin Soup Author: Helen Cooper &amp;ldquo;Pumpkin Soup&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Helen Cooper, which tells the story of three friends - a cat, a squirrel, and a duck - who live in a cozy cottage and work together to make delicious pumpkin soup. The book is filled with beautiful illustrations and captivating storytelling, making it a perfect read for young children. Target Age Group: The book is suitable for children between the ages of 3 and 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazing Grace</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/amazing_grace_isbn_9781423320166/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/amazing_grace_isbn_9781423320166/</guid>
      <description>Amazing Grace Title: Amazing Grace Author: Mary Hoffman Illustrator: Caroline Binch Amazing Grace is a beautifully illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young girl named Grace who loves to act out stories and dreams of being in a play. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 4 to 8 years old, as it features simple language and engaging illustrations that will capture the attention of young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little I Am I</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/little_i_am_i_by_mira_lobe_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/little_i_am_i_by_mira_lobe_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Little I Am I by Mira Lobe Title: Little I Am I Author: Mira Lobe Review: Little I Am I is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Mira Lobe, which is perfect for young readers between the ages of 4 and 8. The book follows the story of a little girl who is trying to find her place in the world and learn about the importance of self-worth. The illustrations in the book are vibrant and eye-catching, which helps to keep the young readers engaged.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Love You Forever</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/love_you_forever_isbn_9780307410382/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/love_you_forever_isbn_9780307410382/</guid>
      <description>Love You Forever Title: Love You Forever Author: Robert Munsch Illustrator: Sheila McGraw Age Group: 4-8 years old Love You Forever is a heartwarming and timeless children&amp;rsquo;s book that has been cherished by many generations. Written by Robert Munsch and illustrated by Sheila McGraw, this book tells a beautiful story about the unconditional love between a mother and her child. The story follows the journey of a mother and her son as they navigate through life&amp;rsquo;s ups and downs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Little Red Lighthouse</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_little_red_lighthouse_by_hildegarde_h_swift_isbn_152045716/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_little_red_lighthouse_by_hildegarde_h_swift_isbn_152045716/</guid>
      <description>The Little Red Lighthouse by Hildegarde H Swift Title: The Little Red Lighthouse and the Great Gray Bridge Author: Hildegarde H. Swift Illustrator: Lynd Ward The Little Red Lighthouse and the Great Gray Bridge is a timeless classic that has been cherished by children and adults alike since its publication in 1942. The story revolves around a small lighthouse, tucked away under the George Washington Bridge in New York City, which begins to feel insignificant and overshadowed by the large, imposing bridge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Runaway Bunny</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_runaway_bunny_by_margaret_wise_brown_isbn_898459958/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_runaway_bunny_by_margaret_wise_brown_isbn_898459958/</guid>
      <description>The Runaway Bunny by Margaret Wise Brown Title: The Runaway Bunny Author: Margaret Wise Brown The Runaway Bunny is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Margaret Wise Brown, which beautifully captures the unconditional love between a mother and her child. The story revolves around a young bunny who decides to run away from home, and his mother&amp;rsquo;s reassurance that she will always be there for him, no matter where he goes or what he becomes.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
