<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Childrens Books that talk about &#39;Bullies&#39; on Monsty The Monster Truck</title>
    <link>https://www.monsty.co/tags/childrens-books-that-talk-about-bullies/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Childrens Books that talk about &#39;Bullies&#39; on Monsty The Monster Truck</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.monsty.co/tags/childrens-books-that-talk-about-bullies/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Monster Blood Tattoo: Foundling</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/monster_blood_tattoo_foundling_by_david_cornish_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/monster_blood_tattoo_foundling_by_david_cornish_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Monster Blood Tattoo: Foundling by David Cornish Title: Monster Blood Tattoo: Foundling Author: David Cornish Review: Monster Blood Tattoo: Foundling is a thrilling and adventurous children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes readers on a journey through a fantastical world filled with mysterious creatures and unforgettable characters. Written by David Cornish, this book is the first installment in the Monster Blood Tattoo trilogy. The story follows the life of a young orphan named Rossamund, who has just been accepted into the prestigious Branden Rose School for Foundlings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Running Man</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_running_man_by_michael_gerard_bauer_isbn_61455083/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_running_man_by_michael_gerard_bauer_isbn_61455083/</guid>
      <description>The Running Man by Michael Gerard Bauer Title: The Running Man Author: Michael Gerard Bauer Target Age Group: 8-12 years old Review: The Running Man is a heartwarming and engaging children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Michael Gerard Bauer. The story follows the life of a young boy named Joseph who is trying to find his place in the world. Throughout the book, Joseph faces various challenges, including dealing with bullies, making friends, and understanding the importance of family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alex</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/alex_by_tessa_duder_isbn_9780195581690/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/alex_by_tessa_duder_isbn_9780195581690/</guid>
      <description>Alex by Tessa Duder Title: Alex Author: Tessa Duder Review: &amp;ldquo;Alex&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Tessa Duder, which follows the adventures of a young girl named Alex as she navigates the challenges of growing up. The book is a perfect fit for children between the ages of 8 and 12, as it addresses themes that are relatable to this age group, such as friendship, self-discovery, and overcoming obstacles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Listen to My Heart</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/listen_to_my_heart_by_bianca_pitzorno_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/listen_to_my_heart_by_bianca_pitzorno_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Listen to My Heart by Bianca Pitzorno Title: Listen to My Heart Author: Bianca Pitzorno Genre: Children&amp;rsquo;s Fiction, Middle Grade Recommended Age Group: 8-12 years old Listen to My Heart is a beautifully written children&amp;rsquo;s book by Bianca Pitzorno that tells the story of a young girl named Matilda. The book is an engaging and thought-provoking read, perfect for children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old. The story follows Matilda, a girl who lives in a small village and is considered different by the other children due to her love for books and her desire to learn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;m the King of the Castle</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/im_the_king_of_the_castle_by_susan_hill_isbn_9780141041940/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/im_the_king_of_the_castle_by_susan_hill_isbn_9780141041940/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m the King of the Castle by Susan Hill Title: I&amp;rsquo;m the King of the Castle Author: Susan Hill Review: &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m the King of the Castle&amp;rdquo; is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Susan Hill, which takes readers on a thrilling journey through the lives of two young boys, Joseph Hooper and Edmund Hooper. The story is set in the 1950s and is centered around themes of friendship, power dynamics, and the complexities of human relationships.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Friends</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_friends_by_rosa_guy_isbn_9780808554028/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_friends_by_rosa_guy_isbn_9780808554028/</guid>
      <description>The Friends by Rosa Guy Title: The Friends Author: Rosa Guy Review: The Friends is a heartwarming and thought-provoking children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Rosa Guy. This book is a perfect fit for children aged 8-12 years old, as it delves into themes of friendship, understanding, and acceptance. The story revolves around two young girls, Phyllisia and Celie, who come from different cultural backgrounds but develop a strong bond of friendship. Throughout the book, the author beautifully portrays the importance of embracing diversity and understanding the experiences of others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Red Zora</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/red_zora_by_kurt_held_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/red_zora_by_kurt_held_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Red Zora by Kurt Held Title: Red Zora Author: Kurt Held Review: Red Zora is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Kurt Held that takes young readers on an adventurous journey through the life of Zora, a brave and independent girl who lives in a small village. The story is set in the early 20th century and is perfect for children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old. The book&amp;rsquo;s protagonist, Zora, is a strong-willed girl who is not afraid to challenge the norms of her society.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Just Annoying!</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/just_annoying_by_andy_griffiths_isbn_439424712/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/just_annoying_by_andy_griffiths_isbn_439424712/</guid>
      <description>Just Annoying! by Andy Griffiths Title: Just Annoying! Author: Andy Griffiths Review: &amp;ldquo;Just Annoying!&amp;rdquo; is a hilarious and engaging children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the talented author Andy Griffiths. This book is a perfect choice for young readers between the ages of 7 and 12, as it is filled with funny and relatable stories that they can easily connect with. The book revolves around the everyday life of a young boy named Andy, who is known for his annoying habits and antics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Girragundji</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/my_girragundji_by_meme_mcdonald_and_boon_pryor_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/my_girragundji_by_meme_mcdonald_and_boon_pryor_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>My Girragundji by Meme Mcdonald and Boon Pryor Title: My Girragundji Author: Meme McDonald and Boon Pryor Review: My Girragundji is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young boy named Jake and his special bond with a pet fish named Girragundji. The book is beautifully illustrated, and the text is simple and engaging, making it perfect for children aged 4 to 8 years old. The story explores themes of friendship, loss, and the importance of cherishing the memories we create with our loved ones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Utterly Me, Clarice Bean</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/utterly_me_clarice_bean_by_lauren_child_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/utterly_me_clarice_bean_by_lauren_child_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Utterly Me, Clarice Bean by Lauren Child Title: Utterly Me, Clarice Bean Author: Lauren Child Review: &amp;ldquo;Utterly Me, Clarice Bean&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the talented Lauren Child. The story follows the adventures of Clarice Bean, a young girl who is trying to find her place in the world. The book is filled with humor, relatable situations, and vibrant illustrations that capture the essence of childhood. The target age group for this book is 7 to 10-year-olds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manolito Quattrocchi</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/manolito_quattrocchi_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/manolito_quattrocchi_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Manolito Quattrocchi Title: Manolito Quattrocchi Author: Jorge Bucay Manolito Quattrocchi is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Jorge Bucay, which tells the story of a young boy named Manolito who embarks on a journey of self-discovery and learns valuable life lessons along the way. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old and is a perfect read for young readers who are beginning to explore the complexities of life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schoolboy Jia Li</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/schoolboy_jia_li_by_qin_wenjun_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/schoolboy_jia_li_by_qin_wenjun_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Schoolboy Jia Li by Qin Wenjun Title: Schoolboy Jia Li Author: Qin Wenjun Schoolboy Jia Li is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Qin Wenjun, which follows the story of a young boy named Jia Li as he navigates through the ups and downs of school life. This heartwarming tale is perfect for children between the ages of 6 and 10, as it addresses various life lessons and challenges that young readers can relate to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>James and the Giant Peach</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/james_and_the_giant_peach_isbn_9780142407912/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/james_and_the_giant_peach_isbn_9780142407912/</guid>
      <description>James and the Giant Peach Title: James and the Giant Peach Author: Roald Dahl Illustrator: Quentin Blake Target Age Group: 7-10 years old James and the Giant Peach is a captivating and imaginative children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the renowned author Roald Dahl. The story follows the life of James, a young boy who loses his parents and is forced to live with his cruel aunts. One day, James meets a mysterious old man who gives him a bag of magical, glowing green crocodile tongues.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Robinson the Younger</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/robinson_the_younger_by_johann_heinrich_campe_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/robinson_the_younger_by_johann_heinrich_campe_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Robinson the Younger by Johann Heinrich Campe Title: Robinson the Younger Author: Johann Heinrich Campe Review: Robinson the Younger is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Johann Heinrich Campe, which is a sequel to the popular story of Robinson Crusoe. This book is a perfect blend of adventure, self-discovery, and moral lessons that are relatable to children of various ages. The story follows the journey of Robinson the Younger, who is the son of the famous Robinson Crusoe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Three Pigs</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_three_pigs_isbn_9780844208732/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_three_pigs_isbn_9780844208732/</guid>
      <description>The Three Pigs Title: The Three Pigs Age Group: 4-8 years old The Three Pigs is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that retells the classic story of three pigs and their encounters with the big, bad wolf. This timeless tale is perfect for children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old, as it teaches valuable life lessons while being entertaining and engaging. The book features beautiful illustrations that bring the story to life, making it an enjoyable read for both children and parents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wolves</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/wolves_by_emily_gravett_isbn_9781405050821/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/wolves_by_emily_gravett_isbn_9781405050821/</guid>
      <description>Wolves by Emily Gravett Title: Wolves Author: Emily Gravett Review: &amp;ldquo;Wolves&amp;rdquo; by Emily Gravett is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young rabbit who is obsessed with wolves. The book is filled with vibrant illustrations and engaging text, making it an enjoyable read for both children and adults. Target Age Group: The book is best suited for children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little Nicholas</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/little_nicholas_by_rene_goscinny_isbn_9780374312756/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/little_nicholas_by_rene_goscinny_isbn_9780374312756/</guid>
      <description>Little Nicholas by Rene Goscinny Title: Little Nicholas Author: Rene Goscinny Review: Little Nicholas is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the adventures of a young boy named Nicholas and his friends. The book is written by Rene Goscinny, who is well-known for his engaging storytelling and humor. The story is relatable and entertaining for children, making it a perfect read for elementary school students. The book targets children between the ages of 6 and 12, as it explores themes of friendship, honesty, and teamwork.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Martine</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/martine_by_gilbert_delahaye_isbn_2203101555/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/martine_by_gilbert_delahaye_isbn_2203101555/</guid>
      <description>Martine by Gilbert Delahaye Title: Martine Author: Gilbert Delahaye Review: Martine is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Gilbert Delahaye that follows the adventures of a young girl named Martine. The book is perfect for children between the ages of 5 and 8, as it contains simple yet engaging language and beautiful illustrations that capture the imagination of young readers. The story revolves around Martine, who embarks on various exciting journeys and encounters a range of interesting characters along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Do People Do All Day?</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/what_do_people_do_all_day_isbn_7189494/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/what_do_people_do_all_day_isbn_7189494/</guid>
      <description>What Do People Do All Day? Title: What Do People Do All Day? Author: Richard Scarry Review: What Do People Do All Day? is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written and illustrated by Richard Scarry. The book takes young readers on a journey through the daily lives of various characters, showcasing the diverse occupations and activities people engage in. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
