<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Childrens Books that talk about &#39;Dream&#39; on Monsty The Monster Truck</title>
    <link>https://www.monsty.co/tags/childrens-books-that-talk-about-dream/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Childrens Books that talk about &#39;Dream&#39; on Monsty The Monster Truck</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.monsty.co/tags/childrens-books-that-talk-about-dream/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A Boat in the Forest</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/a_boat_in_the_forest_by_paola_mastrocola_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/a_boat_in_the_forest_by_paola_mastrocola_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>A Boat in the Forest by Paola Mastrocola Title: A Boat in the Forest Author: Paola Mastrocola A Boat in the Forest is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young boy named Leo who discovers a mysterious boat hidden deep in the forest. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 5 and 8, as it features colorful illustrations and simple language that is easy for young readers to understand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Across the Nightingale Floor</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/across_the_nightingale_floor_isbn_9781402576423/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/across_the_nightingale_floor_isbn_9781402576423/</guid>
      <description>Across the Nightingale Floor Title: Across the Nightingale Floor Author: Lian Hearn Age Group: 10-14 years old &amp;ldquo;Across the Nightingale Floor&amp;rdquo; is a captivating novel that takes readers on a thrilling journey through a world of intrigue, mystery, and adventure. The story follows the life of a young boy named Takeo, who is thrust into a world of danger and betrayal when he is discovered to have unique abilities. The author, Lian Hearn, has masterfully crafted a tale that is both engaging and thought-provoking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coram Boy</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/coram_boy_by_jamila_gavin_isbn_374413746/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/coram_boy_by_jamila_gavin_isbn_374413746/</guid>
      <description>Coram Boy by Jamila Gavin Title: Coram Boy Author: Jamila Gavin Review: Coram Boy, written by Jamila Gavin, is a captivating and heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes the reader on a journey through the lives of two young boys, Toby and Aaron, living in 18th-century England. The story is centered around the theme of adoption and the importance of family, friendship, and loyalty. The target age group for this book would be children between the ages of 10 and 14.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crispin</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/crispin_isbn_9780606305556/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/crispin_isbn_9780606305556/</guid>
      <description>Crispin Title: Crispin Author: Avi Review: Crispin is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Avi, which tells the story of a young boy named Crispin, who embarks on a thrilling adventure in medieval England. The book is targeted towards children aged 8-12, as it features themes of friendship, bravery, and perseverance. The story follows Crispin, a 13-year-old boy who is falsely accused of a crime and forced to flee his village.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finding Violet Park</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/finding_violet_park_by_jenny_valentine_isbn_7291248/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/finding_violet_park_by_jenny_valentine_isbn_7291248/</guid>
      <description>Finding Violet Park by Jenny Valentine Title: Finding Violet Park Author: Jenny Valentine Review: Finding Violet Park is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Jenny Valentine, which tells the story of a young boy named Lucas who embarks on a journey to find the mysterious Violet Park. The book is suitable for children aged 8-12 years old, as it contains elements of adventure, mystery, and self-discovery. The story follows Lucas as he navigates through various challenges and obstacles in his quest to find Violet Park.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Four Sisters</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/four_sisters_by_malika_ferdjoukh_isbn_1684051967/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/four_sisters_by_malika_ferdjoukh_isbn_1684051967/</guid>
      <description>Four Sisters by Malika Ferdjoukh Title: Four Sisters Author: Malika Ferdjoukh Review: Four Sisters is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Malika Ferdjoukh, which beautifully captures the essence of sisterhood, friendship, and the importance of embracing one&amp;rsquo;s unique qualities. The story revolves around four sisters, each with their own distinct personality and talent, who learn to support and celebrate each other&amp;rsquo;s differences. The book is targeted towards children aged 5 to 10 years old, as it features simple yet engaging illustrations and a heartwarming storyline that will resonate with young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grimpow</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/grimpow_by_rafael_abalos_isbn_9788483462386/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/grimpow_by_rafael_abalos_isbn_9788483462386/</guid>
      <description>Grimpow by Rafael Abalos Title: Grimpow Author: Rafael Abalos Review: Grimpow is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Rafael Abalos, which takes readers on a magical journey through the eyes of its young protagonist. The story follows the adventures of Grimpow, a twelve-year-old boy who discovers a hidden world full of mystery and wonder. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 8 to 12 years old. The age-appropriate language and engaging plot make it an enjoyable read for this age group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keeper</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/keeper_by_mal_peet_isbn_9781406328066/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/keeper_by_mal_peet_isbn_9781406328066/</guid>
      <description>Keeper by Mal Peet Title: Keeper Author: Mal Peet Review: Keeper is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Mal Peet, which takes the reader on a thrilling journey through the world of soccer. The story follows the life of Elvis, a young boy who dreams of becoming a professional soccer player, and his encounter with the mysterious Keeper, who teaches him valuable life lessons. The book is targeted towards children aged 8-12 years old, as it explores themes such as perseverance, teamwork, and the importance of following one&amp;rsquo;s dreams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Molly Goes Shopping</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/molly_goes_shopping_by_eva_eriksson_isbn_9129658195/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/molly_goes_shopping_by_eva_eriksson_isbn_9129658195/</guid>
      <description>Molly Goes Shopping by Eva Eriksson Title: Molly Goes Shopping Author: Eva Eriksson Molly Goes Shopping is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Eva Eriksson, aimed at children between the ages of 4 to 8 years old. The story follows the adventures of a young girl named Molly, who goes shopping with her mother and learns important life lessons along the way. The illustrations in the book are vibrant and engaging, capturing the attention of young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Big Birkett</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/my_big_birkett_by_lisa_shanahan_isbn_9781283918206/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/my_big_birkett_by_lisa_shanahan_isbn_9781283918206/</guid>
      <description>My Big Birkett by Lisa Shanahan Title: My Big Birkett Author: Lisa Shanahan My Big Birkett is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Lisa Shanahan. This beautifully illustrated story is perfect for children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old. The book is filled with valuable life lessons that will help children understand the importance of friendship, love, and self-acceptance. The story follows the life of a young boy named Birkett, who is known for being quite small in size.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Out of the Dust</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/out_of_the_dust_isbn_1845078357/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/out_of_the_dust_isbn_1845078357/</guid>
      <description>Out of the Dust Title: Out of the Dust Author: Karen Hesse Review: Out of the Dust is a poignant and powerful children&amp;rsquo;s novel that captures the heart and soul of its readers. Author Karen Hesse has skillfully crafted a story that is both touching and thought-provoking, making it a must-read for young readers. The book is set in the 1930s during the Great Depression and the Dust Bowl, and follows the life of a young girl named Billie Jo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Messenger</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_messenger_isbn_1426404336/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_messenger_isbn_1426404336/</guid>
      <description>The Messenger Title: The Messenger Author: Lois Lowry Genre: Children&amp;rsquo;s Literature Review: The Messenger is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the renowned author Lois Lowry. The story follows the life of a young boy named Matty, who possesses a unique ability to communicate with animals. Matty&amp;rsquo;s journey takes him to a mysterious village called Village, where he meets a diverse cast of characters and embarks on a quest to save the community from an impending disaster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Slightly True Story of Cedar B Hartley</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_slightly_true_story_of_cedar_b_hartley_by_martine_murray_isbn_043948622x/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_slightly_true_story_of_cedar_b_hartley_by_martine_murray_isbn_043948622x/</guid>
      <description>The Slightly True Story of Cedar B Hartley by Martine Murray Title: The Slightly True Story of Cedar B. Hartley Author: Martine Murray Review: The Slightly True Story of Cedar B. Hartley is a charming and whimsical children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the tale of a young girl named Cedar, who lives in a small town with her loving family. The story follows Cedar as she navigates through the ups and downs of life, making new friends, and learning valuable life lessons along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Wind Singer</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_wind_singer_isbn_606246231/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_wind_singer_isbn_606246231/</guid>
      <description>The Wind Singer Title: The Wind Singer Author: William Nicholson Genre: Children&amp;rsquo;s Fantasy Fiction Recommended Age Group: 8-12 years old The Wind Singer is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s fantasy novel by William Nicholson that tells the story of a young girl named Kestrel, her brother Bowman, and their friend Mumpo, as they embark on a thrilling adventure to save their city from the destructive force of the evil Morah. The book is set in the dystopian city of Aramanth, where the people&amp;rsquo;s lives are controlled by a system of tests and rankings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When the World Was Still Young</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/when_the_world_was_still_young_by_jurg_schubiger_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/when_the_world_was_still_young_by_jurg_schubiger_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>When the World Was Still Young by Jurg Schubiger Title: When the World Was Still Young Author: Jurg Schubiger Review: When the World Was Still Young is a beautifully illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young boy named Jonas who embarks on a magical adventure. The book is suitable for children between the ages of 6 and 10 years old. The story follows Jonas as he discovers a hidden door in his grandfather&amp;rsquo;s attic, which leads him to a world where time has stopped.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Caperucita En Manhattan</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/caperucita_en_manhattan_by_carmen_mart%C3%ADn_gaite_isbn_9788478442010/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/caperucita_en_manhattan_by_carmen_mart%C3%ADn_gaite_isbn_9788478442010/</guid>
      <description>Caperucita En Manhattan by Carmen Martín Gaite Title: Caperucita en Manhattan Author: Carmen Martín Gaite &amp;ldquo;Caperucita en Manhattan&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes the classic fairy tale of Little Red Riding Hood and gives it a modern twist. The story follows Caperucita, a young girl who lives in New York City, as she navigates the bustling streets of Manhattan. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 5 and 10 years old and teaches valuable life lessons along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gold Dust</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/gold_dust_by_geraldine_mc_caughrean_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/gold_dust_by_geraldine_mc_caughrean_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Gold Dust by Geraldine Mc Caughrean Title: Gold Dust Author: Geraldine McCaughrean Review: Gold Dust by Geraldine McCaughrean is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes readers on a thrilling adventure through the African wilderness. The story is filled with vivid descriptions, engaging characters, and thought-provoking life lessons, making it a must-read for young readers. The book is suitable for children aged 8 to 12 years old, as it contains a mix of excitement, adventure, and valuable life lessons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Handles</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/handles_isbn_9781708024031/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/handles_isbn_9781708024031/</guid>
      <description>Handles Title: Handles Author: Jane Doe Review: Handles is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that captures the hearts of young readers with its engaging story and beautiful illustrations. The book, written by Jane Doe, is a perfect fit for children aged 4 to 8 years old. The story revolves around a lovable character named Handles, who is a little boy with a big heart. Handles goes on an adventure in his small town, where he encounters various challenges and learns valuable life lessons along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Madame Doubtfire</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/madame_doubtfire_by_anne_fine_isbn_141939567/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/madame_doubtfire_by_anne_fine_isbn_141939567/</guid>
      <description>Madame Doubtfire by Anne Fine Title: Madame Doubtfire Author: Anne Fine Review: Madame Doubtfire is a heartwarming and humorous children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Anne Fine. The story revolves around a father, Daniel Hillard, who is desperate to spend time with his children after a divorce. To do so, he disguises himself as a lovable and eccentric housekeeper, Madame Doubtfire. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 8 and 12, and it beautifully explores themes of family, love, and the importance of communication.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Memoirs of a Basque Cow</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/memoirs_of_a_basque_cow_by_bernardo_atxaga_isbn_9781912868018/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/memoirs_of_a_basque_cow_by_bernardo_atxaga_isbn_9781912868018/</guid>
      <description>Memoirs of a Basque Cow by Bernardo Atxaga Title: Memoirs of a Basque Cow Author: Bernardo Atxaga Genre: Children&amp;rsquo;s Literature, Fiction Recommended Age Group: 8-12 years old Review: Memoirs of a Basque Cow by Bernardo Atxaga is a charming and heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a cow named Koki, who lives in the Basque Country. Through Koki&amp;rsquo;s eyes, the reader is introduced to a world of farm animals, human characters, and the ups and downs of life on a farm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pagan&#39;s Crusade</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/pagans_crusade_by_catherine_jinks_isbn_9780763625849/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/pagans_crusade_by_catherine_jinks_isbn_9780763625849/</guid>
      <description>Pagan&amp;rsquo;s Crusade by Catherine Jinks Title: Pagan&amp;rsquo;s Crusade Author: Catherine Jinks Pagan&amp;rsquo;s Crusade is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the talented author, Catherine Jinks. The story follows the adventures of a young boy named Pagan as he embarks on a thrilling crusade to rescue his kidnapped sister. The book is primarily targeted towards children aged 8-12 years old, as it contains elements of adventure, history, and fantasy that are likely to captivate young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rocco</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/rocco_by_sherryl_jordan_isbn_9780590540056/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/rocco_by_sherryl_jordan_isbn_9780590540056/</guid>
      <description>Rocco by Sherryl Jordan Title: Rocco Author: Sherryl Jordan Review: Rocco is a heartwarming and adventurous children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Sherryl Jordan. The story follows a young boy named Rocco who lives in a small Italian village with his family. Rocco dreams of becoming a great artist, but his father wants him to follow in his footsteps and become a fisherman. When Rocco&amp;rsquo;s father falls ill, Rocco must make a difficult decision - should he stay and help his family or follow his dreams?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roll of Thunder, Hear My Cry</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/roll_of_thunder_hear_my_cry_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/roll_of_thunder_hear_my_cry_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Roll of Thunder, Hear My Cry Title: Roll of Thunder, Hear My Cry Author: Mildred D. Taylor Age Group: 10-14 years old Roll of Thunder, Hear My Cry is a captivating novel by Mildred D. Taylor that tells the story of a young African American girl named Cassie Logan, who lives with her family in Mississippi during the 1930s. The book offers a unique perspective on the challenges faced by African Americans during the Great Depression and the Jim Crow era.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some of the Kinder Planets</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/some_of_the_kinder_planets_by_tim_wynne-jones_isbn_531087514/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/some_of_the_kinder_planets_by_tim_wynne-jones_isbn_531087514/</guid>
      <description>Some of the Kinder Planets by Tim Wynne-Jones Title: Some of the Kinder Planets Author: Tim Wynne-Jones Review: Some of the Kinder Planets is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes young readers on a whimsical journey through the solar system. Written by Tim Wynne-Jones, this book is perfect for children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old. The story follows a young boy named Leo who, after being scolded by his mother for not cleaning his room, decides to run away to the kinder planets in the solar system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Strollers</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/strollers_by_lesley_beake_isbn_370318536/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/strollers_by_lesley_beake_isbn_370318536/</guid>
      <description>Strollers by Lesley Beake Title: Strollers Author: Lesley Beake Review: Strollers, written by Lesley Beake, is a charming and delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a group of strollers who come to life and embark on a magical adventure. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 5 and 8 years old, and is a perfect blend of imagination, adventure, and important life lessons. The story follows the strollers as they explore the world around them, learning valuable lessons about friendship, teamwork, and overcoming challenges.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Ghost Drum</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_ghost_drum_isbn_571153402/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_ghost_drum_isbn_571153402/</guid>
      <description>The Ghost Drum Title: The Ghost Drum Author: Susan Price The Ghost Drum is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Susan Price, which takes readers on a magical journey through a world filled with mythical creatures and enchanting adventures. This book is an excellent choice for children aged 8 to 12 years old, as it offers a perfect blend of fantasy, mystery, and suspense. The story revolves around a young girl named Siri, who is chosen by the mythical creatures known as the Huldrefolk to become their champion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thunder and Lightnings</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/thunder_and_lightnings_isbn_1484605667/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/thunder_and_lightnings_isbn_1484605667/</guid>
      <description>Thunder and Lightnings Title: Thunder and Lightnings Review: Thunder and Lightnings is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young boy named Tommy who learns the importance of friendship, bravery, and self-confidence. The book is targeted towards children aged 6-10 years old, as it contains engaging illustrations and a simple yet meaningful storyline. The book&amp;rsquo;s central theme revolves around Tommy, who is fascinated by thunder and lightning. He dreams of becoming a storm chaser, and with the help of his friends, he sets out on an adventure to catch a thunderstorm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tulku</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/tulku_isbn_9780140313574/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/tulku_isbn_9780140313574/</guid>
      <description>Tulku Title: Tulku Author: Pearl Zhu Review: &amp;ldquo;Tulku&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that captures the imagination of young readers with its enchanting story and vibrant illustrations. Author Pearl Zhu has crafted a heartwarming tale that follows the adventures of a young boy named Tulku, who embarks on a journey of self-discovery and friendship. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 5 and 10 years old. The language is simple and easy to understand, making it an excellent choice for early readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Kestrel for a Knave</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/a_kestrel_for_a_knave_isbn_1858481465/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/a_kestrel_for_a_knave_isbn_1858481465/</guid>
      <description>A Kestrel for a Knave Title: A Kestrel for a Knave Author: Barry Hines Recommended Age Group: 10-14 years old A Kestrel for a Knave is a captivating and thought-provoking novel by Barry Hines, which tells the story of Billy Casper, a young boy from a working-class family in a small English town. The book is a perfect blend of emotions, struggles, and triumphs, making it an excellent read for children between the ages of 10 and 14.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Captain Thunder</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/captain_thunder_by_victor_mora_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/captain_thunder_by_victor_mora_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Captain Thunder by Victor Mora Title: Captain Thunder Author: Victor Mora Review: Captain Thunder is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Victor Mora, which tells the story of a young boy named Tom who dreams of becoming a superhero. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 6 and 10, and it teaches valuable life lessons while keeping the readers engaged with its captivating storyline. The story follows Tom, who is constantly bullied by his classmates and feels powerless to stand up for himself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flambards</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/flambards_by_km_peyton_isbn_192739328/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/flambards_by_km_peyton_isbn_192739328/</guid>
      <description>Flambards by KM Peyton Title: Flambards Author: KM Peyton Review: Flambards is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by KM Peyton, which tells the story of a young girl named Christina, who goes to live with her cousins in a large country house called Flambards. The book is a perfect blend of adventure, friendship, and self-discovery, making it an ideal read for children aged 8-12 years. The story follows Christina as she navigates the complex relationships within her family, learns to ride horses, and ultimately finds her place in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gentle Ben</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/gentle_ben_by_walt_morey_isbn_9781581181197/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/gentle_ben_by_walt_morey_isbn_9781581181197/</guid>
      <description>Gentle Ben by Walt Morey Title: Gentle Ben Author: Walt Morey Gentle Ben is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Walt Morey, which tells the story of a young boy named Mark and his adventures with a large, lovable bear named Ben. The book is suitable for children aged 8-12, as it contains themes of friendship, loyalty, and the importance of preserving nature. The story begins with Mark, a young boy who is grieving the loss of his father and struggling to adjust to his new life in the Alaskan wilderness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Am David</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/i_am_david_isbn_416233406/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/i_am_david_isbn_416233406/</guid>
      <description>I Am David Title: I Am David Author: Anne Holm Review: I Am David is a heartwarming and adventurous children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young boy named David, who escapes from a Bulgarian labor camp and embarks on a journey to find freedom and a new life. The book is beautifully written by Anne Holm, and it captures the essence of hope, resilience, and the human spirit. The story is suitable for children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old, as it contains themes of friendship, courage, and self-discovery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marianne Dreams</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/marianne_dreams_by_catherine_storr_isbn_140302093/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/marianne_dreams_by_catherine_storr_isbn_140302093/</guid>
      <description>Marianne Dreams by Catherine Storr Title: Marianne Dreams Author: Catherine Storr Marianne Dreams is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Catherine Storr. This imaginative story follows the life of a young girl named Marianne, who is confined to her bed due to an illness. To pass the time, she starts drawing a picture of a house, which in turn, becomes a portal to a mysterious and magical world. The target age group for this book is 8-12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MC Higgins</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/mc_higgins_by_virginia_hamilton_isbn_068971694x/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/mc_higgins_by_virginia_hamilton_isbn_068971694x/</guid>
      <description>MC Higgins by Virginia Hamilton Title: MC Higgins Author: Virginia Hamilton Review: MC Higgins is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Virginia Hamilton, which takes the readers on a journey through the life of a young boy named Mayo Cornelius Higgins. The story is set in the Appalachian Mountains and portrays the challenges faced by the protagonist as he grows up in a poverty-stricken community. The book is targeted towards children aged 8-12 years old, as it deals with themes of friendship, family, and resilience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pastures of the Blue Crane</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/pastures_of_the_blue_crane_by_hf_brinsmead_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/pastures_of_the_blue_crane_by_hf_brinsmead_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Pastures of the Blue Crane by HF Brinsmead Title: Pastures of the Blue Crane Author: HF Brinsmead Review: Pastures of the Blue Crane is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by HF Brinsmead. The story follows the life of a young boy named Jimmie who moves with his family to a new town in the Australian countryside. As Jimmie adjusts to his new surroundings, he befriends a local Aboriginal boy named Andy and learns about their culture, traditions, and the importance of preserving the environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sounder</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/sounder_isbn_575006536/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/sounder_isbn_575006536/</guid>
      <description>Sounder Title: Sounder Author: William H. Armstrong Review: Sounder is a heartwarming and thought-provoking children&amp;rsquo;s book written by William H. Armstrong. The story is set in the rural South during the early 1900s and follows the life of a young African American boy named David and his loyal dog, Sounder. The book primarily targets children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old. It is a great read for this age group as it touches upon themes of family, friendship, and perseverance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Dolphin Crossing</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_dolphin_crossing_by_jill_paton_walsh_isbn_140366245/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_dolphin_crossing_by_jill_paton_walsh_isbn_140366245/</guid>
      <description>The Dolphin Crossing by Jill Paton Walsh Title: The Dolphin Crossing Author: Jill Paton Walsh The Dolphin Crossing is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Jill Paton Walsh, which takes the readers on an exciting adventure through the eyes of a young boy named Martin. This book is suitable for children between the ages of 8 to 12 years old, as it contains a perfect blend of adventure, friendship, and moral lessons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Friends</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_friends_by_rosa_guy_isbn_9780808554028/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_friends_by_rosa_guy_isbn_9780808554028/</guid>
      <description>The Friends by Rosa Guy Title: The Friends Author: Rosa Guy Review: The Friends is a heartwarming and thought-provoking children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Rosa Guy. This book is a perfect fit for children aged 8-12 years old, as it delves into themes of friendship, understanding, and acceptance. The story revolves around two young girls, Phyllisia and Celie, who come from different cultural backgrounds but develop a strong bond of friendship. Throughout the book, the author beautifully portrays the importance of embracing diversity and understanding the experiences of others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The October Child</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_october_child_by_eleanor_spence_isbn_340605480/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_october_child_by_eleanor_spence_isbn_340605480/</guid>
      <description>The October Child by Eleanor Spence Title: The October Child Author: Eleanor Spence Review: The October Child is a beautifully written and illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book that captures the essence of the changing seasons and the magic of childhood. The story follows a young girl named October, who is born on the first day of October and experiences the world around her through the lens of the changing seasons. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Peppermint Pig</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_peppermint_pig_by_nina_bawden_isbn_9780582186897/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_peppermint_pig_by_nina_bawden_isbn_9780582186897/</guid>
      <description>The Peppermint Pig by Nina Bawden Title: The Peppermint Pig Author: Nina Bawden Review: The Peppermint Pig is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Nina Bawden. The story follows the adventures of a family of mice, who live in a dollhouse, as they try to help their youngest member, Timothy, who is suffering from pneumonia. To save Timothy, the family decides to make a peppermint pig, a traditional English good luck charm, in the hopes that it will bring them good fortune and help Timothy recover.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Stowaway of the Ulysses</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_stowaway_of_the_ulysses_by_ana_maria_matute_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_stowaway_of_the_ulysses_by_ana_maria_matute_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Stowaway of the Ulysses by Ana Maria Matute Title: The Stowaway of the Ulysses Author: Ana Maria Matute Review: The Stowaway of the Ulysses is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young boy named David who embarks on a thrilling adventure aboard the ship Ulysses. The book is suitable for children aged 8-12 years old, as it contains elements of excitement, friendship, and self-discovery that will appeal to this age group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Twelve and the Genii</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_twelve_and_the_genii_isbn_9780140309164/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_twelve_and_the_genii_isbn_9780140309164/</guid>
      <description>The Twelve and the Genii Title: The Twelve and the Genii Author: Pauline Baynes Genre: Children&amp;rsquo;s Fantasy Adventure Recommended Age Group: 8-12 years old &amp;ldquo;The Twelve and the Genii&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Pauline Baynes, a talented author and illustrator. The story follows the adventures of twelve children who stumble upon a magical world filled with genii, mythical creatures, and exciting challenges. The book is a perfect blend of fantasy, adventure, and humor, making it an enjoyable read for children aged 8-12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Witch of Blackbird Pond</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_witch_of_blackbird_pond_isbn_9780395913673/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_witch_of_blackbird_pond_isbn_9780395913673/</guid>
      <description>The Witch of Blackbird Pond Title: The Witch of Blackbird Pond Author: Elizabeth George Speare Genre: Historical Fiction, Children&amp;rsquo;s Literature Age Group: 8-12 years old &amp;ldquo;The Witch of Blackbird Pond&amp;rdquo; is a captivating historical fiction novel written by Elizabeth George Speare, which tells the story of a young orphan girl named Kit Tyler who moves from the lush Caribbean island of Barbados to the small, strict town of Wethersfield, Connecticut in 1687.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To Kill a Mockingbird</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/to_kill_a_mockingbird_by_harper_lee_isbn_434012602/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/to_kill_a_mockingbird_by_harper_lee_isbn_434012602/</guid>
      <description>To Kill a Mockingbird by Harper Lee Title: To Kill a Mockingbird Author: Harper Lee Review: To Kill a Mockingbird, written by Harper Lee, is a captivating novel that tells the story of a young girl named Scout Finch and her brother Jem, growing up in the fictional town of Maycomb, Alabama during the 1930s. Through the eyes of these innocent children, the reader is exposed to the harsh realities of racism, prejudice, and injustice that were prevalent in the American South during that time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twopence a Tub</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/twopence_a_tub_by_susan_price_isbn_9780571106240/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/twopence_a_tub_by_susan_price_isbn_9780571106240/</guid>
      <description>Twopence a Tub by Susan Price Title: Twopence a Tub Author: Susan Price Review: Twopence a Tub is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Susan Price, which takes readers on a captivating journey through the life of a young boy named Joe. The story is set in the early 1900s and revolves around Joe&amp;rsquo;s family, who work as washerwomen, washing clothes for wealthy people. The book targets children between the ages of 8 to 12 years old, as it contains a perfect blend of adventure, emotion, and historical context.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Viking&#39;s Dawn</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/vikings_dawn_by_henry_treece_isbn_435121588/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/vikings_dawn_by_henry_treece_isbn_435121588/</guid>
      <description>Viking&amp;rsquo;s Dawn by Henry Treece Title: Viking&amp;rsquo;s Dawn Author: Henry Treece Review: Viking&amp;rsquo;s Dawn is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book that transports young readers into the world of Viking mythology and adventure. Written by the talented author Henry Treece, this book is a perfect blend of excitement, history, and life lessons. The story follows the journey of a young Viking boy named Olaf, who dreams of becoming a great warrior like his father.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Girl of the Limberlost</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/a_girl_of_the_limberlost_by_gene_stratton-porter_isbn_9780517072356/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/a_girl_of_the_limberlost_by_gene_stratton-porter_isbn_9780517072356/</guid>
      <description>A Girl of the Limberlost by Gene Stratton-Porter Title: A Girl of the Limberlost Author: Gene Stratton-Porter A Girl of the Limberlost is a beautifully written classic children&amp;rsquo;s book by Gene Stratton-Porter. The story follows the life of a young girl named Elnora Comstock, who lives in the swamps of the Limberlost forest in Indiana. Elnora&amp;rsquo;s mother has passed away, and her father is cold and distant, leaving her to navigate the challenges of life on her own.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adventures of the Ingenious Alfanhui</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/adventures_of_the_ingenious_alfanhui_by_rafael_sanchez_ferlosio_isbn_1873982593/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/adventures_of_the_ingenious_alfanhui_by_rafael_sanchez_ferlosio_isbn_1873982593/</guid>
      <description>Adventures of the Ingenious Alfanhui by Rafael Sanchez Ferlosio Title: Adventures of the Ingenious Alfanhui Author: Rafael Sanchez Ferlosio Review: Adventures of the Ingenious Alfanhui is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes readers on a whimsical journey through the eyes of its young protagonist, Alfanhui. This book is a perfect choice for children between the ages of 8 and 12, as it is filled with engaging adventures, captivating illustrations, and valuable life lessons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big Tiger and Christian</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/big_tiger_and_christian_by_fritz_muhlenweg_isbn_9780224611114/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/big_tiger_and_christian_by_fritz_muhlenweg_isbn_9780224611114/</guid>
      <description>Big Tiger and Christian by Fritz Muhlenweg Title: Big Tiger and Christian Author: Fritz Muhlenweg Big Tiger and Christian is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Fritz Muhlenweg. The story revolves around a young boy named Christian who befriends a tiger named Big Tiger. The two form a unique bond as they explore the jungle together, learning valuable life lessons along the way. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Carry On, Mr. Bowditch</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/carry_on_mr._bowditch_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/carry_on_mr._bowditch_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Carry On, Mr. Bowditch Title: Carry On, Mr. Bowditch Author: Jean Lee Latham Recommended Age Group: 8-12 years old &amp;ldquo;Carry On, Mr. Bowditch&amp;rdquo; is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of Nathaniel Bowditch, a young boy who grew up to become a famous mathematician, astronomer, and navigator. This book is a perfect read for children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old, as it combines elements of adventure, history, and science.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eclipse of the Crescent Moon</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/eclipse_of_the_crescent_moon_isbn_9789631343687/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/eclipse_of_the_crescent_moon_isbn_9789631343687/</guid>
      <description>Eclipse of the Crescent Moon Title: Eclipse of the Crescent Moon Author: John Sobol Illustrator: Derek Shapton Genre: Children&amp;rsquo;s Fiction, Historical Fiction Age Group: 8-12 years old Review: Eclipse of the Crescent Moon is a beautifully written and illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes readers on a captivating journey through a historical setting. The story is set in the 13th century, where a young boy named Nassir, living in a small village, dreams of adventure and excitement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ede and Unku</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/ede_and_unku_by_alex_wedding_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/ede_and_unku_by_alex_wedding_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Ede and Unku by Alex Wedding Title: &amp;ldquo;Ede and Unku&amp;rdquo; by Alex Wedding &amp;ldquo;Ede and Unku&amp;rdquo; is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes young readers on a delightful adventure through the eyes of two lovable characters, Ede and Unku. Written by Alex Wedding, this book is a perfect choice for children between the ages of 4 to 8 years old. The story revolves around Ede and Unku, two friends who live in a small village.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emily Climbs</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/emily_climbs_isbn_1844089894/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/emily_climbs_isbn_1844089894/</guid>
      <description>Emily Climbs Title: Emily Climbs Author: L.M. Montgomery Emily Climbs is the second book in the Emily series by L.M. Montgomery, following the story of a young orphan girl named Emily Starr. The book is set in the early 20th century and takes place in the fictional town of New Moon, where Emily lives with her strict and traditional relatives. The story follows Emily&amp;rsquo;s journey as she navigates her way through adolescence, her passion for writing, and the challenges of growing up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heart</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/heart_by_edmondo_de_amicis_isbn_9781410103154/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/heart_by_edmondo_de_amicis_isbn_9781410103154/</guid>
      <description>Heart by Edmondo De Amicis Title: Heart Author: Edmondo De Amicis Review: Heart, written by Edmondo De Amicis, is a beautifully crafted children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes young readers on a heartwarming journey through the ups and downs of life. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 8 and 12, as it deals with themes of friendship, kindness, and empathy. The story follows the adventures of a young boy named Enrico, who learns valuable life lessons from his interactions with the people around him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kidnapped</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/kidnapped_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/kidnapped_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Kidnapped Title: Kidnapped Author: Robert Louis Stevenson Genre: Adventure/Historical Fiction Recommended Age Group: 9-12 years old Kidnapped, written by Robert Louis Stevenson, is a thrilling adventure novel that follows the story of a young man named David Balfour. The book is set in the 18th century Scotland and is filled with exciting events, intriguing characters, and vivid descriptions of the Scottish landscape. The story begins when David, an orphan, sets out to meet his uncle, Ebenezer Balfour, in order to claim his inheritance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Red Zora</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/red_zora_by_kurt_held_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/red_zora_by_kurt_held_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Red Zora by Kurt Held Title: Red Zora Author: Kurt Held Review: Red Zora is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Kurt Held that takes young readers on an adventurous journey through the life of Zora, a brave and independent girl who lives in a small village. The story is set in the early 20th century and is perfect for children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old. The book&amp;rsquo;s protagonist, Zora, is a strong-willed girl who is not afraid to challenge the norms of her society.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seven Little Australians</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/seven_little_australians_isbn_9798595793711/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/seven_little_australians_isbn_9798595793711/</guid>
      <description>Seven Little Australians Title: Seven Little Australians Author: Ethel Turner Review: Seven Little Australians is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the adventures of the seven Woolcot siblings living in the late 19th century in Australia. The story is filled with fun, mischief, and a touch of drama that will keep young readers engaged and entertained. The book is suitable for children aged 8-12 years old, as it is easy to read and understand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Call of the Wild</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_call_of_the_wild_by_jack_london_isbn_151473138x/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_call_of_the_wild_by_jack_london_isbn_151473138x/</guid>
      <description>The Call of the Wild by Jack London Title: The Call of the Wild Author: Jack London Review: The Call of the Wild, written by Jack London, is a captivating and thought-provoking adventure story that follows the journey of a domesticated dog named Buck. Set in the late 1800s during the Klondike Gold Rush, the book explores themes of resilience, survival, and the power of instinct. The story is suitable for children aged 10 and up, as it contains some mature themes and challenging vocabulary.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Path</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_path_by_miguel_deibes_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_path_by_miguel_deibes_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Path by Miguel Deibes Title: The Path Author: Miguel Deibes Review: The Path, written by Miguel Deibes, is a beautifully crafted children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes readers on a journey through the life of a young boy named Juan. The story is filled with vivid illustrations and thought-provoking messages that will captivate the hearts and minds of young readers. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 6 and 10 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Prisoner of Zenda</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_prisoner_of_zenda_by_anthony_hope_isbn_9781582877082/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_prisoner_of_zenda_by_anthony_hope_isbn_9781582877082/</guid>
      <description>The Prisoner of Zenda by Anthony Hope Title: The Prisoner of Zenda Author: Anthony Hope Review: The Prisoner of Zenda is a captivating adventure story that follows the journey of Rudolf Rassendyll, an English gentleman who bears a striking resemblance to the King of Ruritania. The book is set in a fictional European country and is filled with intrigue, romance, and suspense. Target Age Group: The Prisoner of Zenda is suitable for children aged 10 and above.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Woods in Windri</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/woods_in_windri_by_violet_needham_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/woods_in_windri_by_violet_needham_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Woods in Windri by Violet Needham Title: Woods in Windri Author: Violet Needham Review: Woods in Windri is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Violet Needham. The story is set in a charming and magical world, filled with enchanting creatures and beautiful landscapes. The book is suitable for children between the ages of 8 and 12, as it offers an engaging and captivating narrative that will keep young readers entertained while also teaching valuable life lessons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Captain Fracasse</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/captain_fracasse_by_theophile_gautier_isbn_9781419211980/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/captain_fracasse_by_theophile_gautier_isbn_9781419211980/</guid>
      <description>Captain Fracasse by Theophile Gautier Title: Captain Fracasse Author: Theophile Gautier Review: Captain Fracasse is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Theophile Gautier, which takes the readers on an exciting adventure filled with humor, wit, and valuable life lessons. The story revolves around a group of traveling actors, led by the titular character, Captain Fracasse, as they journey through the countryside, encountering various challenges and learning valuable lessons along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/harry_potter_and_the_goblet_of_fire_isbn_1413185096/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/harry_potter_and_the_goblet_of_fire_isbn_1413185096/</guid>
      <description>Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire Title: Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire Author: J.K. Rowling Target Age Group: 9-12 years old Review: Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire is the fourth book in the Harry Potter series by J.K. Rowling. This thrilling and magical adventure takes readers on a journey with Harry Potter and his friends, Ron Weasley and Hermione Granger, as they navigate the challenges of their fourth year at Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little Women</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/little_women_by_louisa_may_alcott_isbn_1974138135/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/little_women_by_louisa_may_alcott_isbn_1974138135/</guid>
      <description>Little Women by Louisa May Alcott Title: Little Women Author: Louisa May Alcott Little Women, written by Louisa May Alcott, is a timeless classic that has captured the hearts of readers for generations. This heartwarming novel tells the story of the March sisters - Meg, Jo, Beth, and Amy - as they navigate their lives during the American Civil War. The book is an excellent choice for children aged 8 to 12 years old, as it provides valuable life lessons and a glimpse into the lives of these remarkable young women.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rabbit and Coyote</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/rabbit_and_coyote_by_beatriz_donnet_isbn_9789706438294/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/rabbit_and_coyote_by_beatriz_donnet_isbn_9789706438294/</guid>
      <description>Rabbit and Coyote by Beatriz Donnet Title: Rabbit and Coyote Author: Beatriz Donnet Review: &amp;ldquo;Rabbit and Coyote&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a mischievous rabbit who constantly outwits a hungry coyote. The story is set in a vibrant and colorful South American landscape, and the illustrations are both engaging and educational. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 4 to 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rupert the Rapper and Aunt Deep Freeze</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/rupert_the_rapper_and_aunt_deep_freeze_by_sinikka_and_tiina_nopola_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/rupert_the_rapper_and_aunt_deep_freeze_by_sinikka_and_tiina_nopola_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Rupert the Rapper and Aunt Deep Freeze by Sinikka and Tiina Nopola Title: Rupert the Rapper and Aunt Deep Freeze Author: Sinikka and Tiina Nopola Review: Rupert the Rapper and Aunt Deep Freeze is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young boy named Rupert who discovers his passion for rapping. The book is filled with engaging illustrations and an entertaining storyline that captures the attention of young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Something&#39;s Fishy, Hazel Green!</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/somethings_fishy_hazel_green_by_odo_hirsch_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/somethings_fishy_hazel_green_by_odo_hirsch_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Something&amp;rsquo;s Fishy, Hazel Green! by Odo Hirsch Title: Something&amp;rsquo;s Fishy, Hazel Green! Author: Odo Hirsch Review: &amp;ldquo;Something&amp;rsquo;s Fishy, Hazel Green!&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Odo Hirsch, which takes readers on a captivating journey through the eyes of its protagonist, Hazel Green. The story follows Hazel as she sets out to uncover the mystery behind a peculiar smell that has been plaguing her school. The book is primarily targeted towards children between the ages of 7 to 10 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Adventures of Baron Munchhausen</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_adventures_of_baron_munchhausen_by_gottfried_burger_isbn_9788420655956/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_adventures_of_baron_munchhausen_by_gottfried_burger_isbn_9788420655956/</guid>
      <description>The Adventures of Baron Munchhausen by Gottfried Burger Title: The Adventures of Baron Munchhausen Author: Gottfried Burger The Adventures of Baron Munchhausen is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Gottfried Burger. This book takes the reader on a thrilling journey with the legendary character, Baron Munchhausen, who embarks on a series of extraordinary adventures. The story is filled with vivid descriptions and exciting illustrations that will captivate the imagination of young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Scarlet Letter</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_scarlet_letter_by_nathaniel_hawthorne_isbn_1561035025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_scarlet_letter_by_nathaniel_hawthorne_isbn_1561035025/</guid>
      <description>The Scarlet Letter by Nathaniel Hawthorne Title: The Scarlet Letter Author: Nathaniel Hawthorne Review: The Scarlet Letter, written by Nathaniel Hawthorne, is a captivating novel that tells the story of Hester Prynne, a young woman who faces societal judgment and shame after committing adultery in a Puritan community. The book is set in the 17th century and explores themes of sin, guilt, and redemption. The story follows Hester as she navigates life with her daughter, Pearl, and deals with the consequences of her actions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three Fairy Tales</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/three_fairy_tales_by_gustavo_martin_garzo_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/three_fairy_tales_by_gustavo_martin_garzo_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Three Fairy Tales by Gustavo Martin Garzo Title: Three Fairy Tales Author: Gustavo Martin Garzo Review: &amp;ldquo;Three Fairy Tales&amp;rdquo; by Gustavo Martin Garzo is a delightful collection of enchanting stories that captivate the imagination of young readers. The book is beautifully illustrated and designed to appeal to children between the ages of 5 and 10. The first tale, &amp;ldquo;The Little Frog,&amp;rdquo; teaches children the importance of self-confidence and believing in oneself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Katy Did</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/what_katy_did_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/what_katy_did_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>What Katy Did Title: What Katy Did Author: Susan Coolidge Target Age Group: 8-12 years old &amp;ldquo;What Katy Did&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Susan Coolidge, originally published in 1872. The story revolves around the life of a young girl named Katy Carr and her family. The book has been cherished by generations of readers and continues to be a favorite among children today. The story is set in the 19th century and follows Katy, a lively and adventurous girl who loves to play with her siblings and friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Haroun and the Sea of Stories by Salman Rushdie</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/haroun_and_the_sea_of_stories_isbn_571196934/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/haroun_and_the_sea_of_stories_isbn_571196934/</guid>
      <description>Haroun and the Sea of Stories Title: Haroun and the Sea of Stories Author: Salman Rushdie Recommended Age Group: 8-12 years old Haroun and the Sea of Stories is a captivating and imaginative children&amp;rsquo;s book by Salman Rushdie. The story follows the adventures of a young boy named Haroun, who embarks on a magical journey to the fantastical world of Kahani. This enchanting world is filled with talking animals, wondrous creatures, and mysterious beings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kensuke&#39;s Kingdom</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/kensukes_kingdom_by_michael_morpurgo_isbn_1405267372/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/kensukes_kingdom_by_michael_morpurgo_isbn_1405267372/</guid>
      <description>Kensuke&amp;rsquo;s Kingdom by Michael Morpurgo Title: Kensuke&amp;rsquo;s Kingdom Author: Michael Morpurgo Review: Kensuke&amp;rsquo;s Kingdom is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Michael Morpurgo. The story revolves around a young boy named Michael who embarks on a thrilling adventure with his family. The book is targeted towards children aged 8-12 years old and is a perfect blend of adventure, friendship, and self-discovery. The story begins with Michael and his family setting sail on a yacht to fulfill their dream of exploring the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manolito Quattrocchi</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/manolito_quattrocchi_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/manolito_quattrocchi_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Manolito Quattrocchi Title: Manolito Quattrocchi Author: Jorge Bucay Manolito Quattrocchi is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Jorge Bucay, which tells the story of a young boy named Manolito who embarks on a journey of self-discovery and learns valuable life lessons along the way. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old and is a perfect read for young readers who are beginning to explore the complexities of life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pit Pony</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/pit_pony_by_joyce_barkhouse_isbn_771570236/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/pit_pony_by_joyce_barkhouse_isbn_771570236/</guid>
      <description>Pit Pony by Joyce Barkhouse Title: Pit Pony Author: Joyce Barkhouse Review: &amp;ldquo;Pit Pony&amp;rdquo; by Joyce Barkhouse is a heartwarming and engaging children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young boy named Ben and his special bond with a pit pony named Gem. The book is set in a small coal-mining town in Nova Scotia, Canada, during the early 20th century. The target age group for this book is 8-12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shiloh</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/shiloh_isbn_9681658051/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/shiloh_isbn_9681658051/</guid>
      <description>Shiloh Title: Shiloh Author: Phyllis Reynolds Naylor Genre: Children&amp;rsquo;s Fiction, Realistic Fiction Recommended Age Group: 8-12 years old Shiloh is a heartwarming and engaging children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of an 11-year-old boy named Marty Preston who rescues a beagle named Shiloh. The book explores themes of friendship, loyalty, and the importance of standing up for what is right. The story is set in a small town in West Virginia, where Marty finds Shiloh, a mistreated beagle, and decides to take care of him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stories to Fernando</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/stories_to_fernando_by_ema_wolf_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/stories_to_fernando_by_ema_wolf_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Stories to Fernando by Ema Wolf Title: Stories to Fernando Author: Ema Wolf Review: Stories to Fernando is a charming collection of stories that are perfect for young readers. The book is filled with delightful tales that are sure to capture the imagination of children aged 5 to 8 years old. The stories are beautifully illustrated, making it a visual treat for the young readers. One of the key strengths of this book is the way it seamlessly incorporates important life lessons into the stories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tashi</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/tashi_by_anna__barbara_fienberg_isbn_9781760525200/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/tashi_by_anna__barbara_fienberg_isbn_9781760525200/</guid>
      <description>Tashi by Anna &amp;amp; Barbara Fienberg Title: Tashi Author: Anna &amp;amp; Barbara Fienberg Illustrator: Kim Gamble Review: Tashi is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that captures the imagination of young readers with its whimsical storytelling and vibrant illustrations. Written by Anna &amp;amp; Barbara Fienberg and beautifully illustrated by Kim Gamble, Tashi tells the story of a young boy named Jack, who befriends a mischievous and magical character named Tashi. Together, they embark on a series of exciting adventures in a fantastical world filled with talking animals, mythical creatures, and mysterious lands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Bed and Breakfast Star</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_bed_and_breakfast_star_isbn_9780440863243/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_bed_and_breakfast_star_isbn_9780440863243/</guid>
      <description>The Bed and Breakfast Star Title: The Bed and Breakfast Star Author: Jacqueline Wilson Illustrator: Nick Sharratt Recommended Age Group: 8-12 years old The Bed and Breakfast Star is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the talented Jacqueline Wilson. The story revolves around a young girl named Elsa, who is forced to move in with her unconventional aunt, along with her siblings, when her parents are unable to take care of them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Composition</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_composition_isbn_9781305633858/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_composition_isbn_9781305633858/</guid>
      <description>The Composition Title: The Composition Author: Antonia Banyard Genre: Children&amp;rsquo;s Picture Book Target Age Group: 4-8 years old Review: &amp;ldquo;The Composition&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s picture book that tells the story of a young boy named Sam who is tasked with creating a picture for his school&amp;rsquo;s art competition. The book takes readers on a journey as Sam struggles to find inspiration for his artwork, eventually discovering that the beauty of nature can be found in the most unexpected places.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Dog With the Yellow Heart</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_dog_with_the_yellow_heart_by_jutta_richter_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_dog_with_the_yellow_heart_by_jutta_richter_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Dog With the Yellow Heart by Jutta Richter Title: The Dog with the Yellow Heart Author: Jutta Richter The Dog with the Yellow Heart is a heartwarming and engaging children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Jutta Richter. The story follows a young girl named Lena, who is struggling to adjust to her new life in a foster home. Lena finds solace in a special dog with a yellow heart, who helps her navigate the challenges of her new life and teaches her important life lessons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Painted House</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_painted_house_by_montserrate_del_amo_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_painted_house_by_montserrate_del_amo_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Painted House by Montserrate Del Amo Title: The Painted House Author: Montserrate Del Amo Review: The Painted House is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that captures the imagination of young readers with its vibrant illustrations and heartwarming story. The book is perfect for children aged 4-8, as it is both engaging and educational. The story follows the adventures of a young girl named Lily, who loves to paint and dreams of creating a colorful world around her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Story of a Seagull</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_story_of_a_seagull_by_luis_sepulveda_isbn_9780439401869/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_story_of_a_seagull_by_luis_sepulveda_isbn_9780439401869/</guid>
      <description>The Story of a Seagull by Luis Sepulveda Title: The Story of a Seagull Author: Luis Sepulveda The Story of a Seagull by Luis Sepulveda is a heartwarming and engaging children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young seagull who embarks on a journey of self-discovery and friendship. This book is suitable for children between the ages of 6 and 10, as it features simple language and beautiful illustrations that will captivate young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Story of Tracy Beaker</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_story_of_tracy_beaker_isbn_9781855497887/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_story_of_tracy_beaker_isbn_9781855497887/</guid>
      <description>The Story of Tracy Beaker Title: The Story of Tracy Beaker Author: Jacqueline Wilson The Story of Tracy Beaker is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the talented Jacqueline Wilson. The story revolves around a 10-year-old girl named Tracy, who lives in a children&amp;rsquo;s home and dreams of finding a loving family to adopt her. Tracy is a spunky, independent, and sometimes mischievous character who is easy to love and root for.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Whipping Boy</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_whipping_boy_isbn_416088120/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_whipping_boy_isbn_416088120/</guid>
      <description>The Whipping Boy Title: The Whipping Boy Author: Sid Fleischman The Whipping Boy is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young prince named Horace and his whipping boy, Jemmy. The whipping boy, Jemmy, is a commoner who receives the punishments for the prince&amp;rsquo;s misbehavior, as it was believed that it would help the prince learn from his mistakes. The book is set in a medieval kingdom and follows the adventures of Horace and Jemmy as they escape from the castle and embark on a thrilling journey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whale Rider</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/whale_rider_isbn_9780143503279/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/whale_rider_isbn_9780143503279/</guid>
      <description>Whale Rider Title: Whale Rider Author: Witi Ihimaera Age Group: 8-12 years old &amp;ldquo;Whale Rider&amp;rdquo; is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Witi Ihimaera that tells the story of a young Maori girl named Kahu, who is the only living descendant of her tribe&amp;rsquo;s legendary chief. The book is a heartwarming tale of courage, determination, and the power of believing in oneself. The story follows Kahu as she navigates through the challenges of being a young girl in a male-dominated society, striving to prove her worth as a future leader of her tribe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gargling With Jelly</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/gargling_with_jelly_by_brian_patten_isbn_9780573050923/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/gargling_with_jelly_by_brian_patten_isbn_9780573050923/</guid>
      <description>Gargling With Jelly by Brian Patten Title: Gargling with Jelly Author: Brian Patten &amp;ldquo;Gargling with Jelly&amp;rdquo; is a whimsical and delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book by Brian Patten, a well-known poet and author. This book is perfect for young readers aged 6-10, as it captures their imaginations with its fantastical tales and engaging illustrations. The book is a collection of short stories, each one more captivating than the last. The stories range from the amusing tale of a boy who tries to catch the wind to the touching story of a lonely man who finds friendship in a magical fish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pirate&#39;s Heart</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/pirates_heart_by_benno_pludra_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/pirates_heart_by_benno_pludra_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Pirate&amp;rsquo;s Heart by Benno Pludra Title: Pirate&amp;rsquo;s Heart Author: Benno Pludra Review: Pirate&amp;rsquo;s Heart is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Benno Pludra that takes young readers on an exciting adventure on the high seas. The story is engaging and filled with colorful illustrations that will capture the imagination of children aged 6 to 10 years old. The book follows the adventures of a young boy named Tom who dreams of becoming a pirate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Redwall</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/redwall_isbn_9780091767297/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/redwall_isbn_9780091767297/</guid>
      <description>Redwall Title: Redwall Author: Brian Jacques Redwall is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes readers on an adventurous journey through the world of anthropomorphic animals. The story is set in the abbey of Redwall, where the kind and peaceful inhabitants live in harmony with nature. The main character, Matthias, is a young mouse who dreams of becoming a warrior like the legendary Martin the Warrior. The target age group for this book is 8-12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schoolboy Jia Li</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/schoolboy_jia_li_by_qin_wenjun_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/schoolboy_jia_li_by_qin_wenjun_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Schoolboy Jia Li by Qin Wenjun Title: Schoolboy Jia Li Author: Qin Wenjun Schoolboy Jia Li is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Qin Wenjun, which follows the story of a young boy named Jia Li as he navigates through the ups and downs of school life. This heartwarming tale is perfect for children between the ages of 6 and 10, as it addresses various life lessons and challenges that young readers can relate to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The BFG</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_bfg_isbn_60852739/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_bfg_isbn_60852739/</guid>
      <description>The BFG Title: The BFG Author: Roald Dahl Review: The BFG, written by Roald Dahl, is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young orphan girl named Sophie who encounters a Big Friendly Giant (BFG). The book is set in a world where giants roam the land, and the BFG is an outcast due to his gentle nature and preference for capturing dreams instead of eating humans like the other giants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Valley of the Fireflies</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_valley_of_the_fireflies_by_gloria_cecilia_diaz_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_valley_of_the_fireflies_by_gloria_cecilia_diaz_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Valley of the Fireflies by Gloria Cecilia Diaz Title: The Valley of the Fireflies Author: Gloria Cecilia Diaz The Valley of the Fireflies is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Gloria Cecilia Diaz, which takes readers on a magical journey through a mystical land filled with enchanting creatures and valuable life lessons. The book is primarily targeted at children between the ages of 7 and 12, although it can be enjoyed by readers of all ages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anastasia Krupnik</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/anastasia_krupnik_isbn_9788423927791/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/anastasia_krupnik_isbn_9788423927791/</guid>
      <description>Anastasia Krupnik Title: Anastasia Krupnik Author: Lois Lowry Review: Anastasia Krupnik is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Lois Lowry, which tells the story of a young girl named Anastasia who is trying to find her place in the world. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 8 and 12, and it is a perfect read for those who enjoy heartwarming stories with relatable characters. Anastasia Krupnik is a charming and witty protagonist who faces various challenges and experiences a wide range of emotions throughout the book.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fray Perico and His Donkey</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/fray_perico_and_his_donkey_by_juan_munoz_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/fray_perico_and_his_donkey_by_juan_munoz_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Fray Perico and His Donkey by Juan Munoz Title: Fray Perico and His Donkey Author: Juan Munoz Review: Fray Perico and His Donkey is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the adventures of Fray Perico, a kind-hearted monk, and his loyal donkey. The story takes place in a small village where Fray Perico and his donkey become beloved figures due to their generosity and helpful nature. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 5 and 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Storm Boy</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/storm_boy_isbn_1921024658/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/storm_boy_isbn_1921024658/</guid>
      <description>Storm Boy Title: Storm Boy Author: Colin Thiele Review: Storm Boy is a heartwarming and poignant children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Colin Thiele. The story revolves around a young boy who lives alone with his father in a small shack on the coast of South Australia. The boy befriends a group of pelicans and forms a special bond with one of them, whom he names Mr. Percival. The book targets the age group of 8-12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Pair of Jesus Boots</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/a_pair_of_jesus_boots_by_sylvia_sherry_isbn_224615769/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/a_pair_of_jesus_boots_by_sylvia_sherry_isbn_224615769/</guid>
      <description>A Pair of Jesus Boots by Sylvia Sherry Title: A Pair of Jesus Boots Author: Sylvia Sherry Review: A Pair of Jesus Boots is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Sylvia Sherry. The story follows a young boy named Timmy, who desperately wants a pair of Jesus Boots - boots that can walk on water just like Jesus did. The book is targeted towards children aged 4-8 years old and is a perfect blend of adventure, imagination, and heartwarming lessons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bridge to Terabithia</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/bridge_to_terabithia_isbn_9786051732077/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/bridge_to_terabithia_isbn_9786051732077/</guid>
      <description>Bridge to Terabithia Title: Bridge to Terabithia Author: Katherine Paterson Review: Bridge to Terabithia is a captivating and heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s novel written by Katherine Paterson. The story follows the lives of two young protagonists, Jess Aarons and Leslie Burke, as they embark on a journey of friendship, imagination, and self-discovery. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old. The themes and life lessons presented in the story are relatable and relevant to this age group, making it an excellent choice for young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crusade in Jeans</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/crusade_in_jeans_isbn_9781935954071/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/crusade_in_jeans_isbn_9781935954071/</guid>
      <description>Crusade in Jeans Title: Crusade in Jeans Author: Thea Beckman Review: Crusade in Jeans is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young boy named Dolf, who is unexpectedly transported back in time to the Middle Ages. The book, written by Thea Beckman, is an engaging and thought-provoking adventure that is perfect for children aged 10-14. The story is filled with historical details, and it provides an exciting and immersive way for young readers to learn about the past.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doraemon: Gadget Cat From the Future</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/doraemon_gadget_cat_from_the_future_by_fujiko_fujio_isbn_9784092270176/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/doraemon_gadget_cat_from_the_future_by_fujiko_fujio_isbn_9784092270176/</guid>
      <description>Doraemon: Gadget Cat From the Future by Fujiko Fujio Title: Doraemon: Gadget Cat From the Future Author: Fujiko Fujio Review: Doraemon: Gadget Cat From the Future is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a robotic cat named Doraemon who travels back in time to help a young boy named Nobita. The book is filled with fun adventures, imaginative gadgets, and valuable life lessons. Target Age Group: This book is suitable for children between the ages of 6 and 12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Efrem the Knight</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/efrem_the_knight_by_mino_milani_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/efrem_the_knight_by_mino_milani_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Efrem the Knight by Mino Milani Title: Efrem the Knight Author: Mino Milani Review: Efrem the Knight is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Mino Milani that takes young readers on a thrilling adventure with its titular character, Efrem. The story is set in a medieval world where knights, castles, and dragons come to life. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 6 and 10, and its captivating illustrations and engaging narrative make it a perfect choice for this age group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Granny</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/granny_by_peter_hartling_isbn_905478118/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/granny_by_peter_hartling_isbn_905478118/</guid>
      <description>Granny by Peter Hartling Title: Granny Author: Peter Hartling Review: Granny, written by Peter Hartling, is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that captures the heart of its young readers with its simple yet profound message. The story revolves around a young boy named Tommy, who lives with his grandmother, Granny, in a small village. Granny is the heart and soul of the village, always ready to help anyone in need with her kindness and wisdom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Sweet-Orange Tree</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/my_sweet-orange_tree_by_jose_mauro_de_vasconcelos_isbn_9780718108779/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/my_sweet-orange_tree_by_jose_mauro_de_vasconcelos_isbn_9780718108779/</guid>
      <description>My Sweet-Orange Tree by Jose Mauro De Vasconcelos Title: My Sweet-Orange Tree Author: Jose Mauro De Vasconcelos &amp;ldquo;My Sweet-Orange Tree&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Jose Mauro De Vasconcelos, which takes readers on a heartwarming journey through the life of a young boy named Zezé. The story is set in a small Brazilian town and beautifully portrays the innocence and joy of childhood, as well as the importance of friendship, love, and imagination.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stradbroke Dreamtime</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/stradbroke_dreamtime_by_oodgeroo_noonucal_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/stradbroke_dreamtime_by_oodgeroo_noonucal_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Stradbroke Dreamtime by Oodgeroo Noonucal Title: Stradbroke Dreamtime Author: Oodgeroo Noonucal Review: Stradbroke Dreamtime is a beautifully written and illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes readers on a captivating journey through the rich cultural heritage of the Aboriginal people of Australia. Authored by the renowned Oodgeroo Noonucal, this book is a perfect blend of storytelling, art, and education. The book primarily targets children between the ages of 6 and 12, making it an ideal choice for elementary school students.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Bagthorpe Saga: Ordinary Jack</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_bagthorpe_saga_ordinary_jack_by_helen_cresswell_isbn_27255409/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_bagthorpe_saga_ordinary_jack_by_helen_cresswell_isbn_27255409/</guid>
      <description>The Bagthorpe Saga: Ordinary Jack by Helen Cresswell Title: The Bagthorpe Saga: Ordinary Jack Author: Helen Cresswell Review: The Bagthorpe Saga: Ordinary Jack is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Helen Cresswell. This engaging story follows the life of a young boy named Jack and his adventures with his eccentric family, the Bagthorpes. The book is filled with humor, relatable characters, and a heartwarming message that will resonate with readers of all ages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Brothers Lionheart</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_brothers_lionheart_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_brothers_lionheart_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Brothers Lionheart Title: The Brothers Lionheart Author: Astrid Lindgren Review: The Brothers Lionheart is a heartwarming and adventurous children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Astrid Lindgren. The story follows the lives of two brothers, Karl and Jonatan Lionheart, who embark on a magical journey to a fantastical land called Nangijala. The book targets children aged 8-12 years old and teaches valuable life lessons about love, bravery, and the importance of standing up for what is right.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Iron Man: A Children&#39;s Story in Five Nights</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_iron_man_a_childrens_story_in_five_nights_by_ted_hughes_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_iron_man_a_childrens_story_in_five_nights_by_ted_hughes_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Iron Man: A Children&amp;rsquo;s Story in Five Nights by Ted Hughes Title: The Iron Man: A Children&amp;rsquo;s Story in Five Nights Author: Ted Hughes Review: The Iron Man: A Children&amp;rsquo;s Story in Five Nights is a captivating and imaginative story written by the renowned poet and author, Ted Hughes. This book is a perfect blend of adventure, science fiction, and fantasy, making it an ideal read for children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Charlie and the Chocolate Factory</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/charlie_and_the_chocolate_factory_by_roald_dahl_isbn_1417688920/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/charlie_and_the_chocolate_factory_by_roald_dahl_isbn_1417688920/</guid>
      <description>Charlie and the Chocolate Factory by Roald Dahl Title: Charlie and the Chocolate Factory Author: Roald Dahl Review: Charlie and the Chocolate Factory is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the talented Roald Dahl. The story follows the adventures of young Charlie Bucket, a boy from a poor family, who wins a golden ticket to visit the magical and mysterious chocolate factory owned by the eccentric Willy Wonka. The book is targeted towards children aged 8-12 years old, but it can be enjoyed by readers of all ages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fantomette</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/fantomette_by_georges_chaulet_isbn_2010177886/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/fantomette_by_georges_chaulet_isbn_2010177886/</guid>
      <description>Fantomette by Georges Chaulet Title: Fantomette Author: Georges Chaulet Review: Fantomette is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Georges Chaulet that tells the story of a young girl named Fantomette, who is a mysterious superheroine. This book is a perfect read for children between the ages of 7 to 12 years old. The story revolves around Fantomette, who uses her superpowers to help people in need and fight against injustice. Throughout the book, the readers are taken on an exciting adventure filled with action, suspense, and mystery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How the Whale Became</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/how_the_whale_became_by_ted_hughes_isbn_9780571056156/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/how_the_whale_became_by_ted_hughes_isbn_9780571056156/</guid>
      <description>How the Whale Became by Ted Hughes Title: How the Whale Became Author: Ted Hughes Review: How the Whale Became is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the renowned poet and author, Ted Hughes. The story revolves around a whale who, in search of its true identity, embarks on a journey to discover its purpose in life. The book is beautifully illustrated by the talented artist, Andrew Davidson, whose vivid and captivating illustrations bring the story to life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>James and the Giant Peach</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/james_and_the_giant_peach_isbn_9780142407912/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/james_and_the_giant_peach_isbn_9780142407912/</guid>
      <description>James and the Giant Peach Title: James and the Giant Peach Author: Roald Dahl Illustrator: Quentin Blake Target Age Group: 7-10 years old James and the Giant Peach is a captivating and imaginative children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the renowned author Roald Dahl. The story follows the life of James, a young boy who loses his parents and is forced to live with his cruel aunts. One day, James meets a mysterious old man who gives him a bag of magical, glowing green crocodile tongues.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jim Button and Luke the Engine Driver</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/jim_button_and_luke_the_engine_driver_by_michael_ende_isbn_9780879513917/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/jim_button_and_luke_the_engine_driver_by_michael_ende_isbn_9780879513917/</guid>
      <description>Jim Button and Luke the Engine Driver by Michael Ende Title: Jim Button and Luke the Engine Driver Author: Michael Ende Jim Button and Luke the Engine Driver is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Michael Ende, which tells the story of two young friends, Jim Button and Luke, who embark on a thrilling adventure together. The book is a perfect blend of fantasy, friendship, and bravery, making it an excellent choice for young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Knight&#39;s Fee</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/knights_fee_by_rosemary_sutcliff_isbn_99776308/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/knights_fee_by_rosemary_sutcliff_isbn_99776308/</guid>
      <description>Knight&amp;rsquo;s Fee by Rosemary Sutcliff Title: Knight&amp;rsquo;s Fee Author: Rosemary Sutcliff Genre: Children&amp;rsquo;s Historical Fiction Recommended Age Group: 8-12 years old Knight&amp;rsquo;s Fee by Rosemary Sutcliff is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s historical fiction novel that transports young readers to the medieval era. The story follows the life of a young boy named Bevis, who dreams of becoming a knight and serving his lord. Throughout the book, Bevis encounters various challenges, friendships, and life lessons that help shape his character and prepare him for the responsibilities of knighthood.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Boy the Swallow and the Cat</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_boy_the_swallow_and_the_cat_by_miguel_bunuel_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_boy_the_swallow_and_the_cat_by_miguel_bunuel_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Boy the Swallow and the Cat by Miguel Bunuel Title: The Boy, the Swallow, and the Cat Author: Miguel Bunuel Review: The Boy, the Swallow, and the Cat is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young boy who befriends a swallow and a cat, and together they embark on a journey of adventure and self-discovery. The book is beautifully illustrated, with vibrant colors and detailed images that capture the reader&amp;rsquo;s attention and imagination.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Garden</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_garden_by_jiri_trnka_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_garden_by_jiri_trnka_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Garden by Jiri Trnka Title: The Garden Author: Jiri Trnka The Garden is a beautifully illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book by Jiri Trnka, which tells the story of a young boy named John who embarks on a magical adventure in a mysterious garden. This book is a perfect read for children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old, as it is filled with vibrant pictures and simple yet engaging text.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Goalkeeper&#39;s Revenge</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_goalkeepers_revenge_by_bill_naughton_isbn_340149418/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_goalkeepers_revenge_by_bill_naughton_isbn_340149418/</guid>
      <description>The Goalkeeper&amp;rsquo;s Revenge by Bill Naughton Title: The Goalkeeper&amp;rsquo;s Revenge Author: Bill Naughton Age Group: 8-12 years old The Goalkeeper&amp;rsquo;s Revenge is a charming and engaging children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Bill Naughton. The story follows the adventures of a young boy named Tommy who dreams of becoming a great soccer player. As Tommy faces various challenges and learns valuable life lessons, the reader is taken on a journey filled with humor, excitement, and heartwarming moments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Little Fox</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_little_fox_by_istan_fekete_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_little_fox_by_istan_fekete_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Little Fox by Istan Fekete Title: The Little Fox Author: Istan Fekete The Little Fox is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Istan Fekete that takes readers on a journey through the enchanting world of a young fox. This book is perfect for children aged 4 to 8 years old, as it features beautiful illustrations and a simple yet engaging storyline. The story revolves around a little fox who, after losing his mother, sets out on a quest to find a new home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Little Pot Boiler</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_little_pot_boiler_by_spike_milligan_isbn_9780234777558/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_little_pot_boiler_by_spike_milligan_isbn_9780234777558/</guid>
      <description>The Little Pot Boiler by Spike Milligan Title: The Little Pot Boiler Author: Spike Milligan Review: The Little Pot Boiler is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the talented Spike Milligan. This delightful story is a perfect fit for children between the ages of 5 and 8 years old. The book&amp;rsquo;s engaging illustrations and simple language make it an enjoyable read for young readers. The story revolves around a little pot that dreams of becoming a boiler, just like the big, shiny ones in the factory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Seasons in the City</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_seasons_in_the_city_by_italo_calvino_isbn_151570817/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_seasons_in_the_city_by_italo_calvino_isbn_151570817/</guid>
      <description>The Seasons in the City by Italo Calvino Title: The Seasons in the City Author: Italo Calvino The Seasons in the City is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Italo Calvino. The book is a collection of short stories that take place in a city, each story representing a different season. The stories are beautifully written and engaging, making it a perfect read for children aged 6 to 10 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Warden&#39;s Niece</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/wardens_niece_by_gillian_avery_isbn_6707947/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/wardens_niece_by_gillian_avery_isbn_6707947/</guid>
      <description>Warden&amp;rsquo;s Niece by Gillian Avery Title: The Warden&amp;rsquo;s Niece Author: Gillian Avery Review: The Warden&amp;rsquo;s Niece is a charming and delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Gillian Avery. This story follows the adventures of a young girl named Matilda, who is sent to live with her uncle, the warden of a castle, after her parents pass away. As Matilda navigates her new life, she learns valuable lessons about friendship, courage, and the importance of embracing one&amp;rsquo;s unique qualities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where the Red Fern Grows</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/where_the_red_fern_grows_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/where_the_red_fern_grows_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Where the Red Fern Grows Title: Where the Red Fern Grows Author: Phyllis Reynolds Naylor Review: Where the Red Fern Grows is a heartwarming and adventurous story that follows the life of a young boy named Billy Colman, who dreams of owning two redbone coonhounds to hunt with in the Ozark Mountains. The story is set in the 1930s and beautifully captures the essence of life in a small rural community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Kid for Two Farthings</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/a_kid_for_two_farthings_by_wolf_mankowitz_isbn_850467632/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/a_kid_for_two_farthings_by_wolf_mankowitz_isbn_850467632/</guid>
      <description>A Kid for Two Farthings by Wolf Mankowitz Title: A Kid for Two Farthings Author: Wolf Mankowitz Review: A Kid for Two Farthings is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Wolf Mankowitz. The story follows the life of a young boy named Joe, who lives in a bustling market in London&amp;rsquo;s East End. Joe dreams of owning a unicorn, believing that it will bring him good luck and happiness. The book is beautifully written, with vivid descriptions of the market and its colorful characters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Half Magic</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/half_magic_isbn_156379902/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/half_magic_isbn_156379902/</guid>
      <description>Half Magic Title: Half Magic Author: Edward Eager Genre: Children&amp;rsquo;s Fantasy Fiction Recommended Age Group: 8-12 years old &amp;ldquo;Half Magic&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes readers on a magical adventure with four siblings who stumble upon a wish-granting coin. The story is filled with humor, adventure, and valuable life lessons that children can learn from. The four siblings, Jane, Mark, Katharine, and Martha, are the main characters in the book.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marcelino, Bread and Wine</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/marcelino_bread_and_wine_by_jose_maria_sanchez_silva_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/marcelino_bread_and_wine_by_jose_maria_sanchez_silva_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Marcelino, Bread and Wine by Jose Maria Sanchez Silva Title: Marcelino, Bread and Wine Author: José María Sánchez-Silva Target Age Group: 8-12 years old Marcelino, Bread and Wine is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young boy named Marcelino who lives in a monastery. The book, written by José María Sánchez-Silva, is a beautiful tale of friendship, love, and the power of faith. The story follows Marcelino as he forms a deep bond with the monks in the monastery, who become his family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Autumn Term</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/autumn_term_by_antonia_forest_isbn_057106521x/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/autumn_term_by_antonia_forest_isbn_057106521x/</guid>
      <description>Autumn Term by Antonia Forest Title: Autumn Term Author: Antonia Forest Review: Autumn Term is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that captures the essence of school life, friendship, and the challenges faced by young children as they navigate their way through elementary school. The story follows a group of young students at a boarding school, and their various adventures throughout the autumn term. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 8 and 12, and is a perfect read for young readers who are just beginning to explore the world of chapter books.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Misty of Chincoteague</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/misty_of_chincoteague_isbn_9781559947664/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/misty_of_chincoteague_isbn_9781559947664/</guid>
      <description>Misty of Chincoteague Title: Misty of Chincoteague Author: Marguerite Henry Review: Misty of Chincoteague is a heartwarming and engaging children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Marguerite Henry. The story follows the adventures of two young siblings, Paul and Maureen, who live on the island of Chincoteague and dream of owning a wild pony from nearby Assateague Island. The book is beautifully written, with vivid descriptions of the island and its inhabitants, making it easy for readers to immerse themselves in the story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_lion_the_witch_and_the_wardrobe_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_lion_the_witch_and_the_wardrobe_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe Title: The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe Author: C.S. Lewis The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by C.S. Lewis, which takes the reader on a magical journey through the enchanted land of Narnia. The story is set during World War II and follows the adventures of four siblings, Peter, Susan, Edmund, and Lucy, who stumble upon a magical wardrobe that leads them to Narnia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Twenty-One Balloons</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_twenty-one_balloons_isbn_670734411/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_twenty-one_balloons_isbn_670734411/</guid>
      <description>The Twenty-One Balloons Title: The Twenty-One Balloons Author: William Pène du Bois The Twenty-One Balloons is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of Professor William Waterman Sherman, who embarks on a journey in a hot air balloon. The book, written by William Pène du Bois, is an exciting adventure that takes readers on a thrilling ride through the skies and to the mysterious and fantastical land of Krakatoa. The story is suitable for children aged 8 to 12 years old, as it contains elements of adventure, humor, and suspense.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Pony for Jean</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/a_pony_for_jean_by_joanna_cannan_isbn_9780340104071/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/a_pony_for_jean_by_joanna_cannan_isbn_9780340104071/</guid>
      <description>A Pony for Jean by Joanna Cannan Title: A Pony for Jean Author: Joanna Cannan Review: A Pony for Jean is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the story of a young girl named Jean who dreams of owning her very own pony. The book, written by Joanna Cannan, is a heartwarming tale that teaches children about the importance of perseverance, hard work, and responsibility. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 6 and 10 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ballet Shoes</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/ballet_shoes_by_noel_streatfeild_isbn_1400094976/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/ballet_shoes_by_noel_streatfeild_isbn_1400094976/</guid>
      <description>Ballet Shoes by Noel Streatfeild Title: Ballet Shoes Author: Noel Streatfeild &amp;ldquo;Ballet Shoes&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Noel Streatfeild. The story revolves around three orphaned sisters, Pauline, Petrova, and Posy, who are sent to live with their eccentric and absent-minded great-uncle, Matthew, and his no-nonsense housekeeper, Sylvia. As the sisters grow up, they each discover their own unique talents and passions, with Pauline excelling in acting, Petrova in aviation, and Posy in ballet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Friend Mr Leakey</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/my_friend_mr_leakey_by_jbs_haldane_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/my_friend_mr_leakey_by_jbs_haldane_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>My Friend Mr Leakey by JBS Haldane Title: My Friend Mr. Leakey Author: J.B.S. Haldane Review: My Friend Mr. Leakey is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young boy named Sam and his extraordinary friendship with a talking, time-traveling Neanderthal named Mr. Leakey. The book is targeted towards children aged 8-12 years old and is a perfect blend of adventure, humor, and learning. The story begins when Sam stumbles upon Mr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pigeon Post</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/pigeon_post_isbn_9781446483145/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/pigeon_post_isbn_9781446483145/</guid>
      <description>Pigeon Post Title: Pigeon Post Author: Michael Morpurgo Review: Pigeon Post is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the renowned author Michael Morpurgo. The story revolves around a young boy named Fergus, who discovers a love for homing pigeons and dreams of using them to help his father, who is a miner, find a safer job. The book is set in the early 20th century and takes the reader on a journey through the lives of miners and their families during that time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Platero and I</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/platero_and_i_isbn_9780292733282/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/platero_and_i_isbn_9780292733282/</guid>
      <description>Platero and I Title: Platero and I Author: Juan Ramón Jiménez Recommended Age Group: 8-12 years old Platero and I is a beautifully written and illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book that captures the essence of a young boy&amp;rsquo;s adventures with his loyal donkey, Platero, in a small Andalusian village. The book is filled with heartwarming stories that touch upon various life lessons, making it an excellent choice for children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pollyanna</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/pollyanna_isbn_1484819187/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/pollyanna_isbn_1484819187/</guid>
      <description>Pollyanna Title: Pollyanna Author: Eleanor H. Porter Age Group: 8-12 years old Pollyanna is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Eleanor H. Porter, first published in 1913. The story revolves around a young orphan girl named Pollyanna, who is sent to live with her stern and strict Aunt Polly in a small town. Despite her challenging circumstances, Pollyanna maintains a positive and optimistic outlook on life, which she refers to as &amp;ldquo;The Glad Game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Adventures of Gian Burrasca</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_adventures_of_gian_burrasca_by_vamba_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_adventures_of_gian_burrasca_by_vamba_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Adventures of Gian Burrasca by Vamba Title: The Adventures of Gian Burrasca Author: Vamba Review: The Adventures of Gian Burrasca is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the talented author Vamba. The story follows the mischievous adventures of Gian Burrasca, a young boy who loves to play pranks and cause trouble in his town. The book is targeted towards children aged 8-12 years old, making it an excellent choice for young readers who enjoy humor and adventure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Adventures of the Wishing-Chair</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_adventures_of_the_wishing-chair_by_enid_blyton_isbn_1405278633/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_adventures_of_the_wishing-chair_by_enid_blyton_isbn_1405278633/</guid>
      <description>The Adventures of the Wishing-Chair by Enid Blyton Title: The Adventures of the Wishing-Chair Author: Enid Blyton Review: The Adventures of the Wishing-Chair is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the prolific author Enid Blyton. This enchanting story follows the adventures of two siblings, Mollie and Peter, who discover a magical wishing-chair in their playroom. The chair has the power to grant wishes and take the children on exciting and educational journeys to far-off lands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Family From One End Street</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_family_from_one_end_street_isbn_9780140351453/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_family_from_one_end_street_isbn_9780140351453/</guid>
      <description>The Family From One End Street Title: The Family from One End Street Author: Eve Garnett Genre: Children&amp;rsquo;s Literature Age Group: 7-10 years old The Family from One End Street is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of the Ruggles family, who live in a small house on One End Street. The book was written by Eve Garnett and first published in 1937. The story follows the daily lives of the Ruggles family, who, despite their humble circumstances, are full of love, warmth, and good humor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Red U: A Story for Lads</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_red_u_a_story_for_lads_by_wilhelm_matthiessen_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_red_u_a_story_for_lads_by_wilhelm_matthiessen_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Red U: A Story for Lads by Wilhelm Matthiessen Title: The Red U: A Story for Lads Author: Wilhelm Matthiessen The Red U: A Story for Lads is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Wilhelm Matthiessen. The book is a perfect blend of adventure, friendship, and self-discovery, making it an ideal read for children between the ages of 8 and 12. The story revolves around a group of young lads who embark on a thrilling journey to find a hidden treasure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The School at the Chalet</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_school_at_the_chalet_by_elinor_m._brent-dyer_isbn_6903347/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_school_at_the_chalet_by_elinor_m._brent-dyer_isbn_6903347/</guid>
      <description>The School at the Chalet by Elinor M. Brent-Dyer Title: The School at the Chalet Author: Elinor M. Brent-Dyer Review: The School at the Chalet is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Elinor M. Brent-Dyer. The story follows the adventures of Jo Bettany, a young girl who finds herself at a new boarding school in the Swiss Alps called the Chalet School. The book is filled with heartwarming friendships, exciting adventures, and valuable life lessons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Secret Garden</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_secret_garden_isbn_9780721406329/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_secret_garden_isbn_9780721406329/</guid>
      <description>The Secret Garden Title: The Secret Garden Author: Frances Hodgson Burnett Review: The Secret Garden is a timeless classic that has captured the hearts of young readers for generations. Written by Frances Hodgson Burnett, this enchanting story takes us on a journey of self-discovery, friendship, and the power of nature. The story revolves around a young girl named Mary Lennox, who is orphaned and sent to live with her uncle in a mysterious and secluded manor on the Yorkshire Moors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Swish of the Curtain</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_swish_of_the_curtain_by_pamela_brown_isbn_9780340041451/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_swish_of_the_curtain_by_pamela_brown_isbn_9780340041451/</guid>
      <description>The Swish of the Curtain by Pamela Brown Title: The Swish of the Curtain Author: Pamela Brown Review: The Swish of the Curtain is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes the reader on a captivating journey through the lives of a group of young friends who decide to put on their own play. This heartwarming story, written by Pamela Brown, is an ideal read for children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Young Visiters</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_young_visiters_by_daisy_ashford_isbn_9781448104086/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_young_visiters_by_daisy_ashford_isbn_9781448104086/</guid>
      <description>The Young Visiters by Daisy Ashford Title: The Young Visiters Author: Daisy Ashford Review: The Young Visiters is a charming and whimsical children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the young and talented Daisy Ashford. The story follows the adventures of a group of young visitors as they navigate the complexities of life and love. The book is targeted towards children aged 8-12 years old, as it features relatable characters and situations that young readers can easily connect with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Celia Says</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/what_celia_says_by_elena_fortun_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/what_celia_says_by_elena_fortun_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>What Celia Says by Elena Fortun Title: What Celia Says Author: Elena Fortun &amp;ldquo;What Celia Says&amp;rdquo; is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Elena Fortun, which tells the story of a young girl named Celia who has a unique way of looking at the world. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 5 to 10 years old, and it is an excellent choice for parents and teachers looking for a book that teaches valuable life lessons in a fun and engaging manner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anne of Green Gables</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/anne_of_green_gables_isbn_9798632974271/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/anne_of_green_gables_isbn_9798632974271/</guid>
      <description>Anne of Green Gables Title: Anne of Green Gables Author: Lucy Maud Montgomery Age Group: 8-12 years old Anne of Green Gables is a timeless classic that has captured the hearts of readers for generations. Written by Lucy Maud Montgomery, this children&amp;rsquo;s novel tells the story of Anne Shirley, an orphan girl who is sent to live with Matthew and Marilla Cuthbert, an elderly brother and sister, on their farm called Green Gables.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arsene Lupin Gentleman Thief</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/arsene_lupin_gentleman_thief_isbn_1538707462/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/arsene_lupin_gentleman_thief_isbn_1538707462/</guid>
      <description>Arsene Lupin Gentleman Thief Title: Arsene Lupin, Gentleman Thief Author: Maurice Leblanc Genre: Children&amp;rsquo;s Adventure Target Age Group: 8-12 years old &amp;ldquo;Arsene Lupin, Gentleman Thief&amp;rdquo; is a thrilling adventure story that follows the cunning exploits of the master thief, Arsene Lupin. Written by Maurice Leblanc, this book is a delightful read for children between the ages of 8 and 12. The story is filled with mystery, suspense, and humor, making it an engaging read for young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Captain Storm</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/captain_storm_by_emilio_salgari_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/captain_storm_by_emilio_salgari_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Captain Storm by Emilio Salgari Title: Captain Storm Author: Emilio Salgari Review: Captain Storm is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Emilio Salgari, which takes young readers on an exciting adventure on the high seas. The story follows the adventures of Captain Storm, a brave and kind-hearted pirate who embarks on a quest to find a hidden treasure. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 8 and 12, as it contains elements of adventure, mystery, and humor that will appeal to this age group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Carrot Top</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/carrot_top_by_jules_renard_isbn_883730243/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/carrot_top_by_jules_renard_isbn_883730243/</guid>
      <description>Carrot Top by Jules Renard Title: Carrot Top Author: Jules Renard Review: Carrot Top is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young carrot named Carrot Top, who dreams of becoming a great dancer. The book is beautifully illustrated and engaging for young readers, with a simple yet powerful message about following your dreams and never giving up. The book is targeted towards children aged 4-8 years old, as it is easy to read and understand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pinocchio</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/pinocchio_isbn_1584724471/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/pinocchio_isbn_1584724471/</guid>
      <description>Pinocchio Title: Pinocchio Author: Carlo Collodi Genre: Children&amp;rsquo;s Literature, Fantasy Recommended Age Group: 5-10 years old Pinocchio, written by Carlo Collodi, is a classic children&amp;rsquo;s book that has captured the hearts of readers for generations. The story follows the adventures of a wooden puppet named Pinocchio, who dreams of becoming a real boy. Throughout the book, Pinocchio encounters various challenges and experiences valuable life lessons. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 5 and 10 years old, as it contains themes and messages that are both entertaining and educational for this age group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rebecca of Sunnybrook Farm</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/rebecca_of_sunnybrook_farm_by_kate_douglas_wiggin_isbn_9798445751250/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/rebecca_of_sunnybrook_farm_by_kate_douglas_wiggin_isbn_9798445751250/</guid>
      <description>Rebecca of Sunnybrook Farm by Kate Douglas Wiggin Title: Rebecca of Sunnybrook Farm Author: Kate Douglas Wiggin Review: Rebecca of Sunnybrook Farm is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s novel written by Kate Douglas Wiggin, first published in 1903. The story follows the adventures of Rebecca Rowena Randall, a young girl who is sent to live with her spinster aunts in the small town of Riverboro. The book is targeted towards children aged 8-12 years old and is filled with valuable life lessons that are relevant even today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sussi and Biribissi</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/sussi_and_biribissi_by_collodi_nipote_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/sussi_and_biribissi_by_collodi_nipote_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Sussi and Biribissi by Collodi Nipote Title: Sussi and Biribissi Author: Collodi Nipote Review: Sussi and Biribissi is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the adventures of two lovable characters, Sussi and Biribissi, as they explore the wonders of the natural world. With its engaging storyline and vibrant illustrations, this book is sure to capture the hearts of young readers and spark their curiosity about the world around them. Target Age Group: Sussi and Biribissi is an ideal read for children between the ages of 4 and 8.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Adventures of Huckleberry Finn</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_adventures_of_huckleberry_finn_by_mark_twain_isbn_8190732617/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_adventures_of_huckleberry_finn_by_mark_twain_isbn_8190732617/</guid>
      <description>The Adventures of Huckleberry Finn by Mark Twain Title: The Adventures of Huckleberry Finn Author: Mark Twain Review: The Adventures of Huckleberry Finn is a classic American novel written by Mark Twain, which has been cherished by readers for generations. The story follows the adventures of a young boy named Huckleberry Finn, who escapes his abusive father and sets sail on a raft down the Mississippi River with a runaway slave named Jim.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Black Corsair</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_black_corsair_by_emilio_salgari_isbn_6077200069/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_black_corsair_by_emilio_salgari_isbn_6077200069/</guid>
      <description>The Black Corsair by Emilio Salgari Title: The Black Corsair Author: Emilio Salgari Review: The Black Corsair, written by Emilio Salgari, is a thrilling adventure story that is perfect for elementary school-aged children. The book is filled with action, excitement, and valuable life lessons that will captivate young readers. The story follows the adventures of Emilio, a young boy who is captured by pirates and forced to join their crew. As Emilio becomes part of the pirate world, he learns about courage, friendship, and the importance of standing up for what is right.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Prince and the Pauper</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_prince_and_the_pauper_isbn_1410503631/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_prince_and_the_pauper_isbn_1410503631/</guid>
      <description>The Prince and the Pauper Title: The Prince and the Pauper Author: Mark Twain The Prince and the Pauper is a timeless children&amp;rsquo;s classic written by Mark Twain. The story is set in 16th century England and revolves around the lives of two boys who, by a stroke of fate, switch places. The book is targeted towards children aged 8-12 years old, and it is a perfect read for children who enjoy adventure and historical fiction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sophie&#39;s Misfortunes</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/sophies_misfortunes_by_comtesse_de_segur_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/sophies_misfortunes_by_comtesse_de_segur_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Sophie&amp;rsquo;s Misfortunes by Comtesse De Segur Title: Sophie&amp;rsquo;s Misfortunes Author: Comtesse De Segur Review: Sophie&amp;rsquo;s Misfortunes is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Comtesse De Segur. The story follows the adventures of a young girl named Sophie, who often finds herself in trouble due to her mischievous nature. This charming book is perfect for children between the ages of 7 and 12 years old. The book is filled with valuable life lessons that are presented in a simple and engaging manner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tales From Shakespeare</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/tales_from_shakespeare_isbn_9780786103997/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/tales_from_shakespeare_isbn_9780786103997/</guid>
      <description>Tales From Shakespeare Title: Tales From Shakespeare Author: Charles and Mary Lamb Recommended Age Group: 8-12 years old Tales From Shakespeare is a beautifully written and illustrated collection of stories adapted from the works of the famous playwright, William Shakespeare. The book is a perfect introduction to Shakespeare&amp;rsquo;s world for young readers, as it presents the tales in a simplified and easy-to-understand manner. The stories in Tales From Shakespeare cover a wide range of themes and life lessons, including love, friendship, betrayal, and the importance of honesty and integrity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Boy Who Grew Flowers</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_boy_who_grew_flowers_by_jen_wojtowicz_isbn_1846867495/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_boy_who_grew_flowers_by_jen_wojtowicz_isbn_1846867495/</guid>
      <description>The Boy Who Grew Flowers by Jen Wojtowicz Title: The Boy Who Grew Flowers Author: Jen Wojtowicz Review: The Boy Who Grew Flowers is a heartwarming and imaginative children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Jen Wojtowicz. The story follows a young boy named Rink, who possesses a unique ability to grow flowers from his body. Initially, Rink feels embarrassed and isolated due to his extraordinary gift, but he eventually learns to embrace his differences and make friends with a kind and understanding girl named Angelina.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Night Pirates</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_night_pirates_by_peter_harris_isbn_9780545004893/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_night_pirates_by_peter_harris_isbn_9780545004893/</guid>
      <description>The Night Pirates by Peter Harris Title: The Night Pirates Author: Peter Harris The Night Pirates is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Peter Harris, which is perfect for young readers between the ages of 4 and 8. The story follows a group of young pirates who, under the cover of darkness, take over a little girl&amp;rsquo;s bedroom and transform it into their pirate ship. Together, they embark on a thrilling adventure filled with treasure, mermaids, and even a giant sea monster!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beegu</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/beegu_by_alexis_deacon_isbn_9780091768294/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/beegu_by_alexis_deacon_isbn_9780091768294/</guid>
      <description>Beegu by Alexis Deacon Title: Beegu Author: Alexis Deacon Beegu is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written and illustrated by Alexis Deacon. The story follows the adventures of Beegu, an adorable, lovable, and friendly alien who becomes stranded on Earth. As Beegu encounters various animals and people, she struggles to find a way back to her home planet. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 4 to 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Henry and Amy</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/henry_and_amy_by_stephen_michael_king_isbn_802786871/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/henry_and_amy_by_stephen_michael_king_isbn_802786871/</guid>
      <description>Henry and Amy by Stephen Michael King Title: Henry and Amy Author: Stephen Michael King Target Age Group: 4-8 years old Henry and Amy is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book written and illustrated by the talented Stephen Michael King. The story revolves around the friendship between a young boy named Henry and a magical, flying pig named Amy. Together, they embark on a series of adventures, learning valuable life lessons along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Hate School</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/i_hate_school_by_jeanne_willis_isbn_9786077352655/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/i_hate_school_by_jeanne_willis_isbn_9786077352655/</guid>
      <description>I Hate School by Jeanne Willis Title: I Hate School Author: Jeanne Willis Review: &amp;ldquo;I Hate School&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Jeanne Willis, which is perfect for young readers between the ages of 4 to 8 years old. The story revolves around a young boy named Charlie, who is not very fond of going to school. The book explores the various reasons behind Charlie&amp;rsquo;s dislike for school and how his perspective changes over time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Kingdom for a Horse</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/my_kingdom_for_a_horse_by_ana_m_machado_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/my_kingdom_for_a_horse_by_ana_m_machado_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>My Kingdom for a Horse by Ana M Machado Title: My Kingdom for a Horse Author: Ana M Machado Review: My Kingdom for a Horse is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Ana M Machado. The story revolves around a young boy named Tim who dreams of owning a horse. Tim&amp;rsquo;s determination and perseverance to achieve his goal teaches valuable life lessons to young readers. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 6 to 10 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Biggest Kiss in the World</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_biggest_kiss_in_the_world_by_r_chavez_castaneda_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_biggest_kiss_in_the_world_by_r_chavez_castaneda_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Biggest Kiss in the World by R Chavez Castaneda Title: The Biggest Kiss in the World Author: R. Chavez Castaneda Review: The Biggest Kiss in the World is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes young readers on a heartwarming journey through the world of animals. The story follows a mother elephant who, upon hearing about the biggest kiss in the world, sets out on a quest to find it. Along the way, she encounters various animals, each with their own unique interpretation of what the biggest kiss could be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Great Escape From City Zoo</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_great_escape_from_city_zoo_by_tohby_riddle_isbn_207189544/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_great_escape_from_city_zoo_by_tohby_riddle_isbn_207189544/</guid>
      <description>The Great Escape From City Zoo by Tohby Riddle Title: The Great Escape From City Zoo Author: Tohby Riddle Review: The Great Escape From City Zoo is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a group of animals who plan an elaborate escape from their city zoo. Author Tohby Riddle has created a world filled with adventure, humor, and heart, making this book a must-read for children of all ages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anancy Spiderman</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/anancy_spiderman_by_james_berry_isbn_744513111/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/anancy_spiderman_by_james_berry_isbn_744513111/</guid>
      <description>Anancy Spiderman by James Berry Title: Anancy Spiderman Author: James Berry Review: Anancy Spiderman is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of Anancy, a young boy who dreams of becoming a superhero like Spiderman. The book is filled with colorful illustrations and engaging dialogue that captures the attention of young readers. Target Age Group: Anancy Spiderman is suitable for children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Friends From the Other Side</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/friends_from_the_other_side_by_gloria_anzaldua_isbn_9780892391134/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/friends_from_the_other_side_by_gloria_anzaldua_isbn_9780892391134/</guid>
      <description>Friends From the Other Side by Gloria Anzaldua Title: Friends From the Other Side Author: Gloria Anzaldua Review: &amp;ldquo;Friends From the Other Side&amp;rdquo; is a beautifully written and illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young girl named Marisol, who lives near the U.S.-Mexico border. The book explores themes of friendship, empathy, and understanding, as Marisol befriends a group of children from the other side of the border. The story is engaging and age-appropriate for children between the ages of 6 and 10 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joyful Noise: Poems for Two Voices by Paul Fleischman</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/joyful_noise_poems_for_two_voices_isbn_590981838/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/joyful_noise_poems_for_two_voices_isbn_590981838/</guid>
      <description>Joyful Noise: Poems for Two Voices Title: Joyful Noise: Poems for Two Voices Author: Paul Fleischman Age Group: 6-10 years old &amp;ldquo;Joyful Noise: Poems for Two Voices&amp;rdquo; is a delightful and engaging collection of poems written by Paul Fleischman, specifically designed for two people to read aloud together. This book is perfect for children aged 6-10 years old, as it encourages collaboration, creativity, and a love for poetry. The book features a variety of poems, each with its own unique theme and message.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matilda</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/matilda_isbn_9780754065098/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/matilda_isbn_9780754065098/</guid>
      <description>Matilda Title: Matilda Author: Roald Dahl Matilda, written by the renowned children&amp;rsquo;s author Roald Dahl, is a captivating and heartwarming story that follows the life of a young girl named Matilda. This book is a perfect choice for children aged 7 to 12 years old, as it explores themes of courage, resilience, and the power of intelligence. The story revolves around Matilda, a precocious and brilliant young girl who has a passion for books and learning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Friend Percy&#39;s Magical Gym Shoes</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/my_friend_percys_magical_gym_shoes_by_ulf_stark_isbn_095825981x/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/my_friend_percys_magical_gym_shoes_by_ulf_stark_isbn_095825981x/</guid>
      <description>My Friend Percy&amp;rsquo;s Magical Gym Shoes by Ulf Stark Title: My Friend Percy&amp;rsquo;s Magical Gym Shoes Author: Ulf Stark &amp;ldquo;My Friend Percy&amp;rsquo;s Magical Gym Shoes&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Ulf Stark, which tells the story of Percy, a young boy who receives a pair of magical gym shoes from his grandmother. The shoes have the power to grant Percy&amp;rsquo;s wishes, which leads to a series of exciting adventures and valuable life lessons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tar Beach</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/tar_beach_isbn_590463810/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/tar_beach_isbn_590463810/</guid>
      <description>Tar Beach Title: Tar Beach Author: Faith Ringgold Target Age Group: 5-10 years old Tar Beach is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Faith Ringgold, which takes readers on a magical journey through the eyes of a young girl named Cassie. The story is set in the 1930s and is based on the author&amp;rsquo;s own experiences growing up in Harlem. The book is beautifully illustrated with Faith Ringgold&amp;rsquo;s quilt-like artwork, which adds to the charm and uniqueness of the story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Chair for My Mother</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/a_chair_for_my_mother_isbn_9780874993356/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/a_chair_for_my_mother_isbn_9780874993356/</guid>
      <description>A Chair for My Mother Title: A Chair for My Mother Author: Vera B. Williams Recommended Age Group: 4-8 years old &amp;ldquo;A Chair for My Mother&amp;rdquo; is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Vera B. Williams, which beautifully captures the spirit of love, family, and perseverance. The story follows a young girl named Rosa, who lives with her mother and grandmother in a small apartment. After their previous home was destroyed by a fire, the family saved coins in a jar to buy a comfortable chair for Rosa&amp;rsquo;s hardworking mother.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Pocket for Corduroy</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/a_pocket_for_corduroy_by_don_freeman_isbn_140951245/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/a_pocket_for_corduroy_by_don_freeman_isbn_140951245/</guid>
      <description>A Pocket for Corduroy by Don Freeman Title: A Pocket for Corduroy Author: Don Freeman &amp;ldquo;A Pocket for Corduroy&amp;rdquo; is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Don Freeman, which follows the adventures of a lovable teddy bear named Corduroy. This charming story is perfect for young readers between the ages of 4 and 8 years old. The book revolves around Corduroy, who lives in a department store and dreams of finding a home with a loving family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dragon Ball</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/dragon_ball_by_akira_toriyama_isbn_9781404699618/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/dragon_ball_by_akira_toriyama_isbn_9781404699618/</guid>
      <description>Dragon Ball by Akira Toriyama Title: Dragon Ball Author: Akira Toriyama Review: Dragon Ball, written by Akira Toriyama, is a thrilling and action-packed adventure story that is perfect for children aged 8-12 years old. The book follows the journey of a young boy named Goku, who discovers that he possesses extraordinary powers. Along with his friends, Goku embarks on a quest to find the seven magical Dragon Balls, which, when brought together, can grant any wish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fungus the Bogeyman</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/fungus_the_bogeyman_by_raymond_briggs_isbn_9780394738208/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/fungus_the_bogeyman_by_raymond_briggs_isbn_9780394738208/</guid>
      <description>Fungus the Bogeyman by Raymond Briggs Title: Fungus the Bogeyman Author: Raymond Briggs &amp;ldquo;Fungus the Bogeyman&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the talented author and illustrator, Raymond Briggs. This book is perfect for children aged 7-10 years old and provides an engaging and humorous insight into the life of a bogeyman. The story follows Fungus, a bogeyman who lives underground with his family, and their daily lives filled with slime, mud, and other unmentionable things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hey, Al</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/hey_al_isbn_913358010/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/hey_al_isbn_913358010/</guid>
      <description>Hey, Al Title: Hey, Al Author: Arthur Yorinks Illustrator: Richard Egielski Recommended Age Group: 4-8 years old &amp;ldquo;Hey, Al&amp;rdquo; is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a man named Al and his pet dog, Eddie. The story takes place in a city where Al lives in a small apartment. Eddie is a lovable and loyal companion who enjoys spending time with Al. The book&amp;rsquo;s target age group is 4-8 years old, as it is a simple and engaging story with beautiful illustrations that capture the attention of young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lend Me Your Wings</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/lend_me_your_wings_by_john_agard_isbn_9780316020107/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/lend_me_your_wings_by_john_agard_isbn_9780316020107/</guid>
      <description>Lend Me Your Wings by John Agard Title: Lend Me Your Wings Author: John Agard Lend Me Your Wings is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by John Agard, a well-known poet and author. This engaging story is perfect for children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old. The book is filled with beautiful illustrations that capture the imagination and bring the story to life. The story follows a young boy named Joe, who discovers a magical pair of wings that allow him to fly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mind Your Own Business</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/mind_your_own_business_by_michael_rosen_isbn_9780233964683/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/mind_your_own_business_by_michael_rosen_isbn_9780233964683/</guid>
      <description>Mind Your Own Business by Michael Rosen Title: Mind Your Own Business Author: Michael Rosen Review: Mind Your Own Business, written by Michael Rosen, is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that captivates young readers with its engaging story and colorful illustrations. The book is primarily targeted towards children aged 5 to 8 years old, as it features simple language and an easy-to-follow narrative. The story revolves around a young boy named Bert, who is curious about the people in his neighborhood and their various occupations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mog the Forgetful Cat</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/mog_the_forgetful_cat_by_judith_kerr_isbn_9780819305442/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/mog_the_forgetful_cat_by_judith_kerr_isbn_9780819305442/</guid>
      <description>Mog the Forgetful Cat by Judith Kerr Title: Mog the Forgetful Cat Author: Judith Kerr Review: Mog the Forgetful Cat is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Judith Kerr. The story revolves around Mog, a charming and lovable cat who is known for her forgetfulness. This book is perfect for children between the ages of 4 to 8 years old. The book is filled with colorful illustrations and simple, easy-to-understand language, making it an ideal read for young children.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Strega Nona</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/strega_nona_isbn_9780590659673/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/strega_nona_isbn_9780590659673/</guid>
      <description>Strega Nona Title: Strega Nona Author: Tomie dePaola Review: Strega Nona is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Tomie dePaola, which tells the story of a wise old witch named Strega Nona who lives in a small Italian village. The book is filled with beautiful illustrations that bring the story to life and captivate the reader&amp;rsquo;s attention. The story is aimed at children between the ages of 4 to 8 years old, and it teaches important life lessons such as the importance of hard work, responsibility, and the consequences of not following instructions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Cat That Lived a Million Times</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_cat_that_lived_a_million_times_by_yoko_sano_isbn_9780824820985/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_cat_that_lived_a_million_times_by_yoko_sano_isbn_9780824820985/</guid>
      <description>The Cat That Lived a Million Times by Yoko Sano Title: The Cat That Lived a Million Times Author: Yoko Sano Review: The Cat That Lived a Million Times is a heartwarming and enchanting children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a cat with an extraordinary ability to reincarnate and live multiple lives. The book is a perfect read for children aged 6-10 years old, as it features beautiful illustrations and a captivating narrative that will keep young readers engaged.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Companions</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_companions_by_lygia_bojunga_nunes_isbn_9780434954155/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_companions_by_lygia_bojunga_nunes_isbn_9780434954155/</guid>
      <description>The Companions by Lygia Bojunga Nunes Title: The Companions Author: Lygia Bojunga Nunes Review: The Companions is a heartwarming and engaging children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a group of animals who come together to help a little bird find her way home. Written by Lygia Bojunga Nunes, this book is a perfect choice for young readers between the ages of 4 and 8 years old. The story revolves around a little bird named Zizi who gets lost while exploring the forest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Giant Jam Sandwich</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_giant_jam_sandwich_by_janet_burroway_isbn_330303546/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_giant_jam_sandwich_by_janet_burroway_isbn_330303546/</guid>
      <description>The Giant Jam Sandwich by Janet Burroway Title: The Giant Jam Sandwich Author: Janet Burroway Review: The Giant Jam Sandwich is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Janet Burroway. This story is perfect for children between the ages of 4 to 8 years old, as it is filled with colorful illustrations and simple yet engaging language. The story revolves around four bakers who decide to take action against a swarm of wasps that have been causing trouble in their village.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Quinkins</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_quinkins_by_percy_trezise_and_dick_roughsey_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_quinkins_by_percy_trezise_and_dick_roughsey_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Quinkins by Percy Trezise and Dick Roughsey Title: The Quinkins Author: Percy Trezise and Dick Roughsey Review: The Quinkins is a beautifully illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes the readers on an enchanting journey through the Australian Aboriginal folklore. The story is centered around the Quinkins, which are mischievous and magical creatures that can change their appearance at will. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 6 to 10 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Real Thief</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_real_thief_by_william_steig_isbn_1782691456/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_real_thief_by_william_steig_isbn_1782691456/</guid>
      <description>The Real Thief by William Steig Title: The Real Thief Author: William Steig Target Age Group: 5-10 years old The Real Thief is a beautifully illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book by William Steig, which tells the story of a young mouse named Pearl who is accused of stealing a cherished diamond ring. The book explores themes of friendship, trust, and honesty, making it a perfect read for children between the ages of 5 and 10 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Toad Who Wanted to Be a Star</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/a_toad_who_wanted_to_be_a_star_by_oscar_alfaro_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/a_toad_who_wanted_to_be_a_star_by_oscar_alfaro_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>A Toad Who Wanted to Be a Star by Oscar Alfaro Title: A Toad Who Wanted to Be a Star Author: Oscar Alfaro A Toad Who Wanted to Be a Star is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Oscar Alfaro that tells the story of a little toad who dreams of becoming a star. The book is beautifully illustrated and targets children between the ages of 4 to 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cion Cion Blue</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/cion_cion_blue_by_pinin_carpi_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/cion_cion_blue_by_pinin_carpi_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Cion Cion Blue by Pinin Carpi Title: Cion Cion Blue Author: Pinin Carpi Review: Cion Cion Blue is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that captures the imagination of young readers with its charming illustrations and engaging storyline. The book is written by Pinin Carpi, who has done an excellent job of creating a world that is both whimsical and educational. The story revolves around a little blue elephant named Cion Cion, who embarks on a journey to find his true colors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dailan Kifki</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/dailan_kifki_by_maria_elena_walsh_isbn_950070109x/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/dailan_kifki_by_maria_elena_walsh_isbn_950070109x/</guid>
      <description>Dailan Kifki by Maria Elena Walsh Title: Dailan Kifki Author: Maria Elena Walsh Dailan Kifki is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Maria Elena Walsh, which takes young readers on an adventurous journey with its protagonist, Dailan Kifki. This book is suitable for children between the ages of 5 and 8 years old, and is a perfect blend of engaging storytelling and valuable life lessons. The story revolves around Dailan Kifki, a young boy who is eager to explore the world and embark on new adventures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frederick</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/frederick_isbn_1979021686/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/frederick_isbn_1979021686/</guid>
      <description>Frederick Title: Frederick Author: Leo Lionni Recommended Age Group: 4-8 years old Frederick is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Leo Lionni, which tells the story of a family of field mice living in a beautiful meadow. The book primarily focuses on the character of Frederick, a field mouse who spends his time daydreaming and observing the world around him, rather than actively participating in the preparations for winter like the other mice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mr. Rabbit and the Lovely Present</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/mr._rabbit_and_the_lovely_present_isbn_9780060887049/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/mr._rabbit_and_the_lovely_present_isbn_9780060887049/</guid>
      <description>Mr. Rabbit and the Lovely Present Title: Mr. Rabbit and the Lovely Present Author: Charlotte Zolotow Illustrator: Maurice Sendak Target Age Group: 4-8 years old &amp;ldquo;Mr. Rabbit and the Lovely Present&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Charlotte Zolotow and beautifully illustrated by Maurice Sendak. The story follows a young girl named Annabelle who is searching for the perfect present for her friend Mr. Rabbit. Annabelle embarks on a journey through the woods, encountering various animals who offer suggestions for the present.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sylvester and the Magic Pebble</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/sylvester_and_the_magic_pebble_isbn_043973522x/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/sylvester_and_the_magic_pebble_isbn_043973522x/</guid>
      <description>Sylvester and the Magic Pebble Title: Sylvester and the Magic Pebble Author: William Steig Recommended Age Group: 4-8 years old &amp;ldquo;Sylvester and the Magic Pebble&amp;rdquo; is a heartwarming and enchanting children&amp;rsquo;s book written by William Steig. The story follows Sylvester, a young donkey who finds a magic pebble that grants wishes. When a series of unfortunate events occur, Sylvester and his family learn valuable life lessons about love, patience, and the importance of family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Dreams of the Toad</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_dreams_of_the_toad_by_javier_villafane_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_dreams_of_the_toad_by_javier_villafane_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Dreams of the Toad by Javier Villafane Title: The Dreams of the Toad Author: Javier Villafane Review: The Dreams of the Toad is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Javier Villafane that tells the story of a toad named Tito who dreams of doing something extraordinary. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 4 to 8 years old and is filled with beautiful illustrations that will captivate the young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Orange Cow</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_orange_cow_by_nathan_hale_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_orange_cow_by_nathan_hale_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Orange Cow by Nathan Hale Title: The Orange Cow Author: Nathan Hale Review: The Orange Cow is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Nathan Hale, which tells the story of a young boy named Timmy who befriends a talking orange cow named Bessie. The book is a perfect blend of humor, adventure, and valuable life lessons, making it an ideal read for children between the ages of 5 and 10 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Child&#39;s Garden of Verses</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/a_childs_garden_of_verses_isbn_872260518/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/a_childs_garden_of_verses_isbn_872260518/</guid>
      <description>A Child&amp;rsquo;s Garden of Verses Title: A Child&amp;rsquo;s Garden of Verses Author: Robert Louis Stevenson Review: A Child&amp;rsquo;s Garden of Verses is a delightful collection of poems that captures the essence of childhood, written by the renowned Scottish author Robert Louis Stevenson. This timeless classic has been a favorite among children and adults alike since its publication in 1885. The book targets children in the age group of 5 to 12 years old, making it an ideal choice for elementary school students.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apoutsiak</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/apoutsiak_by_paul-emile_victor_isbn_9782081604452/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/apoutsiak_by_paul-emile_victor_isbn_9782081604452/</guid>
      <description>Apoutsiak by Paul-Emile Victor Title: Apoutsiak Author: Paul-Emile Victor Review: Apoutsiak is a beautifully illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young Inuit boy named Apoutsiak who goes on a thrilling adventure with his family. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 5 and 10, and it offers a wonderful blend of adventure, cultural exploration, and important life lessons. The story begins with Apoutsiak and his family embarking on a journey to find a new place to live.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cole&#39;s Funny Picture Book</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/coles_funny_picture_book_by_edward_william_cole_isbn_9781849024808/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/coles_funny_picture_book_by_edward_william_cole_isbn_9781849024808/</guid>
      <description>Cole&amp;rsquo;s Funny Picture Book by Edward William Cole Title: Cole&amp;rsquo;s Funny Picture Book Author: Edward William Cole Review: Cole&amp;rsquo;s Funny Picture Book is a delightful and engaging children&amp;rsquo;s book that is perfect for young readers between the ages of 4 and 8. The book is filled with vibrant illustrations and humorous stories that will keep your child entertained and engaged. The book follows the adventures of Cole, a young boy who encounters various funny situations and learns valuable life lessons along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Come Hither</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/come_hither_by_waler_de_la_mare_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/come_hither_by_waler_de_la_mare_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Come Hither by Waler De La Mare Title: Come Hither Author: Waler De La Mare Review: Come Hither is a charming and whimsical children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Waler De La Mare. The story follows a group of children as they embark on a magical adventure in the enchanted forest. With beautiful illustrations and captivating prose, this book is sure to captivate the imagination of young readers. Target Age Group: Come Hither is best suited for children between the ages of 5 and 10 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Josephine and Her Dolls</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/josephine_and_her_dolls_by_h.c._cradock_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/josephine_and_her_dolls_by_h.c._cradock_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Josephine and Her Dolls by H.C. Cradock Title: Josephine and Her Dolls Author: H.C. Cradock &amp;ldquo;Josephine and Her Dolls&amp;rdquo; is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by H.C. Cradock that tells the story of a young girl named Josephine who loves her dolls dearly. This delightful book is perfect for children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old. The story follows Josephine as she plays with her dolls, each with its unique personality and characteristics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little Tim and the Brave Sea Captain</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/little_tim_and_the_brave_sea_captain_by_edward_ardizzone_isbn_809810425/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/little_tim_and_the_brave_sea_captain_by_edward_ardizzone_isbn_809810425/</guid>
      <description>Little Tim and the Brave Sea Captain by Edward Ardizzone Title: Little Tim and the Brave Sea Captain Author: Edward Ardizzone Review: Little Tim and the Brave Sea Captain is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written and illustrated by Edward Ardizzone. The story follows the adventures of Little Tim, a young boy who dreams of becoming a sailor. Tim&amp;rsquo;s journey takes him on a thrilling sea voyage, where he encounters various challenges and learns valuable life lessons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michka</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/michka_by_marie_colmont_isbn_9782081602403/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/michka_by_marie_colmont_isbn_9782081602403/</guid>
      <description>Michka by Marie Colmont Title: Michka Author: Marie Colmont Michka is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Marie Colmont, which takes the readers on a heartwarming journey of a young girl named Michka. The story is engaging and thought-provoking, making it an excellent choice for children between the ages of 8 and 12. The book&amp;rsquo;s central theme revolves around the importance of friendship, self-discovery, and the power of believing in oneself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mr Popper&#39;s Penguins</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/mr_poppers_penguins_by_richard_and_florence_atwater_isbn_9780788727245/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/mr_poppers_penguins_by_richard_and_florence_atwater_isbn_9780788727245/</guid>
      <description>Mr Popper&amp;rsquo;s Penguins by Richard and Florence Atwater Title: Mr. Popper&amp;rsquo;s Penguins Author: Richard and Florence Atwater &amp;ldquo;Mr. Popper&amp;rsquo;s Penguins&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Richard and Florence Atwater. This heartwarming story follows the adventures of Mr. Popper, a house painter who dreams of exploring the Antarctic and the South Pole. One day, he receives a surprise gift: a penguin! As more penguins join the family, Mr. Popper and his children embark on a series of amusing and entertaining experiences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Morning in Maine</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/one_morning_in_maine_isbn_9780808536338/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/one_morning_in_maine_isbn_9780808536338/</guid>
      <description>One Morning in Maine Title: One Morning in Maine Author: Robert McCloskey One Morning in Maine is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written and illustrated by Robert McCloskey. The story follows the adventures of a young girl named Sal and her little sister, Jane, as they spend a day exploring the coast of Maine with their mother. The book is filled with beautiful illustrations that capture the essence of the Maine coastline and the charm of a small fishing village.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perez the Mouse</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/perez_the_mouse_by_luis_coloma_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/perez_the_mouse_by_luis_coloma_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Perez the Mouse by Luis Coloma Title: Perez the Mouse Author: Luis Coloma &amp;ldquo;Perez the Mouse&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Luis Coloma, which tells the story of a curious and adventurous little mouse named Perez. The book is perfect for children aged 4 to 8 years old, as it is filled with beautiful illustrations and simple language that young readers can easily understand and enjoy. The story revolves around Perez, who embarks on a journey to find a new home for his family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roule Galette</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/roule_galette_by_natha_caputo_isbn_9782081285477/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/roule_galette_by_natha_caputo_isbn_9782081285477/</guid>
      <description>Roule Galette by Natha Caputo Title: Roule Galette Author: Natha Caputo Roule Galette is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a little galette (a type of French pastry) who dreams of exploring the world and embarks on a thrilling adventure. This book is perfect for children aged 4 to 8 years old, as it captures their imagination and teaches them valuable life lessons. The illustrations in Roule Galette are vibrant and eye-catching, which will keep the young readers engaged.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Dutch Twins</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_dutch_twins_by_lucy_fitch_perkins_isbn_9780891904687/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_dutch_twins_by_lucy_fitch_perkins_isbn_9780891904687/</guid>
      <description>The Dutch Twins by Lucy Fitch Perkins Title: The Dutch Twins Author: Lucy Fitch Perkins Review: The Dutch Twins is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Lucy Fitch Perkins. The story follows the lives of two young Dutch twins, Jan and Nelly, as they navigate their daily adventures in their small village. The book is beautifully illustrated, with vivid pictures that capture the essence of Dutch culture and life. The target age group for this book is 5-8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The House That Jack Built</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_house_that_jack_built_by_unknown_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_house_that_jack_built_by_unknown_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The House That Jack Built by Unknown Title: The House That Jack Built Author: Unknown Review: The House That Jack Built is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes readers on a journey through a house built by Jack, a young and ambitious boy. The story is told in a simple and engaging manner, making it perfect for children aged 4 to 8 years old. The book features beautiful illustrations that bring the story to life, capturing the imagination of young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Little Red Engine Gets a Name</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_little_red_engine_gets_a_name_by_diana_ross_isbn_571064396/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_little_red_engine_gets_a_name_by_diana_ross_isbn_571064396/</guid>
      <description>The Little Red Engine Gets a Name by Diana Ross Title: The Little Red Engine Gets a Name Author: Diana Ross Review: The Little Red Engine Gets a Name is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Diana Ross. This delightful story follows the adventures of a little red engine who doesn&amp;rsquo;t have a name. The little red engine embarks on a journey to find a name that truly represents who they are.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Little Wooden Horse</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_little_wooden_horse_by_ursula_m_williams_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_little_wooden_horse_by_ursula_m_williams_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Little Wooden Horse by Ursula M Williams Title: The Little Wooden Horse Author: Ursula M. Williams The Little Wooden Horse is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Ursula M. Williams. This heartwarming story is perfect for children aged 5-8 years old, as it contains simple language and engaging illustrations that will capture their attention. The story revolves around a little wooden horse named Timothy, who dreams of becoming a real horse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Magic Pudding</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_magic_pudding_by_norman_lindsay_isbn_9781479368822/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_magic_pudding_by_norman_lindsay_isbn_9781479368822/</guid>
      <description>The Magic Pudding by Norman Lindsay Title: The Magic Pudding Author: Norman Lindsay Review: The Magic Pudding is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written and illustrated by Norman Lindsay. The story revolves around a talking pudding named Albert, who is the center of a hilarious adventure. The book is targeted towards children aged 5-10 years old, and it is filled with engaging illustrations and captivating characters that will keep young readers entertained.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jamela&#39;s Dress</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/jamelas_dress_by_niki_daly_isbn_141769775x/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/jamelas_dress_by_niki_daly_isbn_141769775x/</guid>
      <description>Jamela&amp;rsquo;s Dress by Niki Daly Title: Jamela&amp;rsquo;s Dress Author: Niki Daly Jamela&amp;rsquo;s Dress is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Niki Daly, which tells the story of a young girl named Jamela who dreams of owning a beautiful dress. The book targets children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old and teaches valuable life lessons through its engaging narrative and vibrant illustrations. The story revolves around Jamela, who lives in a South African township and has a passion for fashion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Magic Fishbone</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_magic_fishbone_by_charles_dickens_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_magic_fishbone_by_charles_dickens_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Magic Fishbone by Charles Dickens Title: The Magic Fishbone Author: Charles Dickens The Magic Fishbone is a charming and enchanting children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the renowned author Charles Dickens. This delightful story, first published in 1868, has been captivating young readers for generations with its whimsical characters and magical adventures. The story follows the life of a young girl named Princess Alicia and her family, who live in a small kingdom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Ugly Duckling</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_ugly_duckling_isbn_9781530297054/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_ugly_duckling_isbn_9781530297054/</guid>
      <description>The Ugly Duckling Title: The Ugly Duckling Author: Hans Christian Andersen The Ugly Duckling is a classic children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Hans Christian Andersen, originally published in 1843. This heartwarming tale has been captivating young readers for generations with its beautiful illustrations and valuable life lessons. The story revolves around a young swan who is mistakenly hatched in a duck&amp;rsquo;s nest. As the swan grows up, it is constantly mocked and bullied by the other ducks for its appearance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Poems for the Very Young</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/poems_for_the_very_young_by_michael_rosen_isbn_9781856971164/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/poems_for_the_very_young_by_michael_rosen_isbn_9781856971164/</guid>
      <description>Poems for the Very Young by Michael Rosen Title: Poems for the Very Young Author: Michael Rosen Target Age Group: 4-8 years old &amp;ldquo;Poems for the Very Young&amp;rdquo; is a delightful collection of poems by Michael Rosen, specifically designed for young children. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old, making it an excellent choice for parents, teachers, and caregivers looking for engaging and educational content for their little ones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Runaway Train</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/runaway_train_by_benedict_blathwayt_isbn_9781856810777/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/runaway_train_by_benedict_blathwayt_isbn_9781856810777/</guid>
      <description>Runaway Train by Benedict Blathwayt Title: Runaway Train Author: Benedict Blathwayt Review: Runaway Train is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Benedict Blathwayt, which tells the story of a little boy named Jack who is fascinated by trains. The book is a perfect blend of adventure, excitement, and learning, making it an ideal read for children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old. The story begins with Jack dreaming about his favorite train, the &amp;ldquo;Runaway Train.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sleep Well, Little Bear</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/sleep_well_little_bear_by_quint_buckholz_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/sleep_well_little_bear_by_quint_buckholz_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Sleep Well, Little Bear by Quint Buckholz Title: Sleep Well, Little Bear Author: Quint Buckholz Sleep Well, Little Bear is a beautifully illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young bear named Little Bear who is having trouble sleeping. The book is written by Quint Buckholz and is perfect for children between the ages of 3 to 8 years old. The story begins with Little Bear feeling restless and unable to sleep.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazing Grace</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/amazing_grace_isbn_9781423320166/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/amazing_grace_isbn_9781423320166/</guid>
      <description>Amazing Grace Title: Amazing Grace Author: Mary Hoffman Illustrator: Caroline Binch Amazing Grace is a beautifully illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young girl named Grace who loves to act out stories and dreams of being in a play. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 4 to 8 years old, as it features simple language and engaging illustrations that will capture the attention of young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fire-Engine Lil</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/fire-engine_lil_by_janet_mclean_andrew_mclean_isbn_9780048200358/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/fire-engine_lil_by_janet_mclean_andrew_mclean_isbn_9780048200358/</guid>
      <description>Fire-Engine Lil by Janet McLean, Andrew McLean Title: Fire-Engine Lil Author: Janet McLean, Andrew McLean Review: Fire-Engine Lil is a charming and delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young girl named Lil, who dreams of becoming a firefighter. The book is beautifully illustrated with vibrant colors and engaging images that capture the imagination of young readers. The target age group for this book is 4 to 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mousehole Cat</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/mousehole_cat_by_antonia_barber_isbn_8426436374/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/mousehole_cat_by_antonia_barber_isbn_8426436374/</guid>
      <description>Mousehole Cat by Antonia Barber Title: The Mousehole Cat Author: Antonia Barber Illustrator: Nicola Bayley Review: The Mousehole Cat is a beautifully illustrated and engaging children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a magical cat named Mowzer, who lives in the Cornish village of Mousehole. The book is set in the 16th century and revolves around the legend of the evil owl-king, who has cast a spell on the village, causing the fishermen to be unable to catch any fish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Angelina Ballerina</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/angelina_ballerina_by_katharine_holabird_isbn_1854060104/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/angelina_ballerina_by_katharine_holabird_isbn_1854060104/</guid>
      <description>Angelina Ballerina by Katharine Holabird Title: Angelina Ballerina Author: Katharine Holabird Illustrator: Helen Craig Review: Angelina Ballerina is a charming and delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Katharine Holabird and illustrated by Helen Craig. The story follows the adventures of a young mouse named Angelina, who dreams of becoming a famous ballerina. This book is perfect for children between the ages of 4 to 8 years old, as it captures their imagination and teaches valuable life lessons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Avocado Baby</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/avocado_baby_by_john_burningham_isbn_690042434/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/avocado_baby_by_john_burningham_isbn_690042434/</guid>
      <description>Avocado Baby by John Burningham Title: Avocado Baby Author: John Burningham Review: Avocado Baby is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book by the talented author and illustrator John Burningham. The story follows the journey of a young couple who, after trying various methods to have a baby, finally succeed in growing one from an avocado seed. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old. It is filled with colorful and engaging illustrations that capture the imagination of young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Church Mouse</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/church_mouse_by_graham_oakley_isbn_689704755/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/church_mouse_by_graham_oakley_isbn_689704755/</guid>
      <description>Church Mouse by Graham Oakley Title: Church Mouse Author: Graham Oakley Review: Church Mouse is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Graham Oakley, which tells the story of a small mouse named Arthur who lives in a church. The book is a perfect blend of charming illustrations and a heartwarming story that captures the essence of friendship, courage, and the importance of being true to oneself. The book is targeted towards children aged 4 to 8 years old, as it features simple language and engaging illustrations that are sure to captivate young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corduroy</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/corduroy_isbn_9780140558555/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/corduroy_isbn_9780140558555/</guid>
      <description>Corduroy Title: Corduroy Author: Don Freeman Target Age Group: 3-7 years old Corduroy, written by Don Freeman, is a heartwarming and timeless children&amp;rsquo;s book that has captured the hearts of young readers for generations. The story follows the adventures of a small, lovable teddy bear named Corduroy, who lives in a department store and dreams of finding a home with a loving child. The book is beautifully illustrated with vibrant colors and charming characters that engage the young readers&amp;rsquo; imagination.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Green Eggs and Ham</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/green_eggs_and_ham_isbn_1717952/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/green_eggs_and_ham_isbn_1717952/</guid>
      <description>Green Eggs and Ham Title: Green Eggs and Ham Author: Dr. Seuss Review: Green Eggs and Ham is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the renowned author Dr. Seuss. This book is a classic and has been enjoyed by children for generations. The story follows the adventures of Sam-I-Am, who tries to convince an unnamed character to try green eggs and ham. The unnamed character is initially hesitant, but eventually gives in and ends up enjoying the dish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In the Night Kitchen</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/in_the_night_kitchen_isbn_440847303/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/in_the_night_kitchen_isbn_440847303/</guid>
      <description>In the Night Kitchen Title: In the Night Kitchen Author: Maurice Sendak Review: In the Night Kitchen is a whimsical and imaginative children&amp;rsquo;s book written and illustrated by Maurice Sendak. The story follows a young boy named Mickey, who falls into a dream-like world where he embarks on a thrilling adventure in the night kitchen. The book targets children between the ages of 4 to 8 years old. It offers a fun and engaging storyline that captures the attention of young readers and encourages their curiosity and imagination.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lotta&#39;s Bike</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/lottas_bike_by_astrid_lindgren_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/lottas_bike_by_astrid_lindgren_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Lotta&amp;rsquo;s Bike by Astrid Lindgren Title: Lotta&amp;rsquo;s Bike Author: Astrid Lindgren &amp;ldquo;Lotta&amp;rsquo;s Bike&amp;rdquo; is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the talented Astrid Lindgren. This heartwarming story follows the adventures of Lotta, a young girl who dreams of owning a bicycle. The book is beautifully illustrated and is perfect for children aged 4-8 years old. The story is filled with valuable life lessons that children can learn and appreciate. It teaches the importance of perseverance, hard work, and determination.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lyle, Lyle Crocodile</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/lyle_lyle_crocodile_by_bernard_waber_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/lyle_lyle_crocodile_by_bernard_waber_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Lyle, Lyle Crocodile by Bernard Waber Title: Lyle, Lyle Crocodile Author: Bernard Waber Review: Lyle, Lyle Crocodile is a charming and delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Bernard Waber. The story revolves around a friendly crocodile named Lyle, who lives in a house on East 88th Street in New York City with the Primm family. Lyle loves to sing and perform, and he becomes a beloved member of the community. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Martine</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/martine_by_gilbert_delahaye_isbn_2203101555/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/martine_by_gilbert_delahaye_isbn_2203101555/</guid>
      <description>Martine by Gilbert Delahaye Title: Martine Author: Gilbert Delahaye Review: Martine is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Gilbert Delahaye that follows the adventures of a young girl named Martine. The book is perfect for children between the ages of 5 and 8, as it contains simple yet engaging language and beautiful illustrations that capture the imagination of young readers. The story revolves around Martine, who embarks on various exciting journeys and encounters a range of interesting characters along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Is the Bear</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/this_is_the_bear_by_sarah_hayes_isbn_64431037/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/this_is_the_bear_by_sarah_hayes_isbn_64431037/</guid>
      <description>This Is the Bear by Sarah Hayes Title: This Is the Bear Author: Sarah Hayes Review: This Is the Bear is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the story of a little boy named Ben and his beloved teddy bear. The book is written by Sarah Hayes, who has done an excellent job of creating a story that is both engaging and educational for young readers. The illustrations in the book are vibrant and eye-catching, making it an enjoyable read for children aged 3 to 7 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bedtime for Frances</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/bedtime_for_frances_by_russell_hoban_isbn_9780571052745/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/bedtime_for_frances_by_russell_hoban_isbn_9780571052745/</guid>
      <description>Bedtime for Frances by Russell Hoban Title: Bedtime for Frances Author: Russell Hoban Review: Bedtime for Frances is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Russell Hoban. The story follows a young badger named Frances who is reluctant to go to bed, as she is afraid of the dark and monsters under her bed. With the help of her loving and patient parents, Frances learns to overcome her fears and embrace bedtime.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fly, Little Bird</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/fly_little_bird_by_francesco_tullio_altan_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/fly_little_bird_by_francesco_tullio_altan_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Fly, Little Bird by Francesco Tullio Altan Title: Fly, Little Bird Author: Francesco Tullio Altan Fly, Little Bird is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book by Francesco Tullio Altan that tells the story of a young bird who dreams of flying high and exploring the world. The book is perfect for children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old, as it is filled with colorful illustrations and simple, yet engaging language.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good Night, Alfie Atkins</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/good_night_alfie_atkins_by_gunilla_bergstrom_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/good_night_alfie_atkins_by_gunilla_bergstrom_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Good Night, Alfie Atkins by Gunilla Bergstrom Title: Good Night, Alfie Atkins Author: Gunilla Bergstrom Good Night, Alfie Atkins is a charming and heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the adventures of a young boy named Alfie. The story is written by Gunilla Bergstrom, who has beautifully crafted a tale that captures the imagination of young readers. The book is targeted towards children aged 4 to 8 years old and is filled with vibrant illustrations that add to the overall appeal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Julian the Rabbit</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/julian_the_rabbit_by_nicoletta_costa_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/julian_the_rabbit_by_nicoletta_costa_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Julian the Rabbit by Nicoletta Costa Title: Julian the Rabbit Author: Nicoletta Costa Review: Julian the Rabbit is a charming and delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that captures the hearts of young readers with its vibrant illustrations and engaging story. Author Nicoletta Costa has created a world filled with colorful characters and valuable life lessons that are sure to resonate with children of all ages. The story follows Julian, a curious and adventurous rabbit who embarks on a journey to discover the true meaning of friendship and the importance of embracing one&amp;rsquo;s unique qualities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little Spook&#39;s Baby Sister</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/little_spooks_baby_sister_by_inger_sandberg_isbn_9780416869200/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/little_spooks_baby_sister_by_inger_sandberg_isbn_9780416869200/</guid>
      <description>Little Spook&amp;rsquo;s Baby Sister by Inger Sandberg Title: Little Spook&amp;rsquo;s Baby Sister Author: Inger Sandberg Review: Little Spook&amp;rsquo;s Baby Sister is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Inger Sandberg, which tells the story of Little Spook, a friendly ghost, who is excited to become a big brother. The book is beautifully illustrated and has a charming, whimsical quality that is sure to capture the attention of young readers. The story follows Little Spook as he prepares for the arrival of his baby sister.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Bear Went Over the Mountain</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_bear_went_over_the_mountain_by_john_prater_isbn_9780370323688/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_bear_went_over_the_mountain_by_john_prater_isbn_9780370323688/</guid>
      <description>The Bear Went Over the Mountain by John Prater Title: The Bear Went Over the Mountain Author: John Prater Review: The Bear Went Over the Mountain is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a curious bear who decides to explore the world beyond his familiar mountain home. With vibrant illustrations and engaging storytelling, author John Prater captures the imagination of young readers and takes them on a journey of discovery and adventure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Little Engine That Could</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_little_engine_that_could_by_watty_piper_isbn_448189631/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_little_engine_that_could_by_watty_piper_isbn_448189631/</guid>
      <description>The Little Engine That Could by Watty Piper Title: The Little Engine That Could Author: Watty Piper The Little Engine That Could is a classic children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Watty Piper. This heartwarming story has been a favorite among children and parents alike for generations. The book is beautifully illustrated and has a simple, yet powerful message that resonates with readers of all ages. The story revolves around a little blue engine that is faced with the daunting task of pulling a long train over a steep mountain.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
