<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Childrens Books that talk about &#39;Humble&#39; on Monsty The Monster Truck</title>
    <link>https://www.monsty.co/tags/childrens-books-that-talk-about-humble/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Childrens Books that talk about &#39;Humble&#39; on Monsty The Monster Truck</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.monsty.co/tags/childrens-books-that-talk-about-humble/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Call of the Wild</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_call_of_the_wild_by_jack_london_isbn_151473138x/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_call_of_the_wild_by_jack_london_isbn_151473138x/</guid>
      <description>The Call of the Wild by Jack London Title: The Call of the Wild Author: Jack London Review: The Call of the Wild, written by Jack London, is a captivating and thought-provoking adventure story that follows the journey of a domesticated dog named Buck. Set in the late 1800s during the Klondike Gold Rush, the book explores themes of resilience, survival, and the power of instinct. The story is suitable for children aged 10 and up, as it contains some mature themes and challenging vocabulary.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tom Brown&#39;s School Days</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/tom_browns_school_days_by_thomas_hughes_isbn_9781096966081/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/tom_browns_school_days_by_thomas_hughes_isbn_9781096966081/</guid>
      <description>Tom Brown&amp;rsquo;s School Days by Thomas Hughes Title: Tom Brown&amp;rsquo;s School Days Author: Thomas Hughes Review: Tom Brown&amp;rsquo;s School Days is a classic children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Thomas Hughes, first published in 1857. The story follows the life of Tom Brown, a young boy who attends Rugby School, a boarding school in England. The book is set in the early 19th century and provides an insightful look into the life of a schoolboy during that time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Carrot Top</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/carrot_top_by_jules_renard_isbn_883730243/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/carrot_top_by_jules_renard_isbn_883730243/</guid>
      <description>Carrot Top by Jules Renard Title: Carrot Top Author: Jules Renard Review: Carrot Top is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young carrot named Carrot Top, who dreams of becoming a great dancer. The book is beautifully illustrated and engaging for young readers, with a simple yet powerful message about following your dreams and never giving up. The book is targeted towards children aged 4-8 years old, as it is easy to read and understand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Canterville Ghost</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_canterville_ghost_isbn_9783842451155/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_canterville_ghost_isbn_9783842451155/</guid>
      <description>The Canterville Ghost Title: The Canterville Ghost Author: Oscar Wilde Review: The Canterville Ghost is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the renowned author Oscar Wilde. The story revolves around a family who moves into an old castle haunted by a ghost, Sir Simon. The ghost tries to scare the family away but to his surprise, they are not afraid of him. Instead, they try to help him and understand his story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Family From One End Street</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_family_from_one_end_street_isbn_9780140351453/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_family_from_one_end_street_isbn_9780140351453/</guid>
      <description>The Family From One End Street Title: The Family from One End Street Author: Eve Garnett Genre: Children&amp;rsquo;s Literature Age Group: 7-10 years old The Family from One End Street is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of the Ruggles family, who live in a small house on One End Street. The book was written by Eve Garnett and first published in 1937. The story follows the daily lives of the Ruggles family, who, despite their humble circumstances, are full of love, warmth, and good humor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beegu</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/beegu_by_alexis_deacon_isbn_9780091768294/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/beegu_by_alexis_deacon_isbn_9780091768294/</guid>
      <description>Beegu by Alexis Deacon Title: Beegu Author: Alexis Deacon Beegu is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written and illustrated by Alexis Deacon. The story follows the adventures of Beegu, an adorable, lovable, and friendly alien who becomes stranded on Earth. As Beegu encounters various animals and people, she struggles to find a way back to her home planet. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 4 to 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snip Snap</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/snip_snap_by_mara_bergman_isbn_9780060777548/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/snip_snap_by_mara_bergman_isbn_9780060777548/</guid>
      <description>Snip Snap by Mara Bergman Title: Snip Snap Author: Mara Bergman Snip Snap is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Mara Bergman, which takes young readers on a magical adventure through the world of whimsical creatures. The book is filled with vibrant illustrations by the talented Nick Maland, which adds to the overall charm of the story. Target Age Group: Snip Snap is best suited for children between the ages of 4 to 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Sea at the End of the Forest</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_sea_at_the_end_of_the_forest_by_pinin_carpi_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_sea_at_the_end_of_the_forest_by_pinin_carpi_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Sea at the End of the Forest by Pinin Carpi Title: The Sea at the End of the Forest Author: Pinin Carpi Review: The Sea at the End of the Forest is a beautifully written and illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book that captivates the imagination of young readers. This enchanting story follows the adventures of a young boy named Timmy, who embarks on a journey to find the sea at the end of the forest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elmer the Patchwork Elephant</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/elmer_the_patchwork_elephant_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/elmer_the_patchwork_elephant_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Elmer the Patchwork Elephant Title: Elmer the Patchwork Elephant Author: David McKee Elmer the Patchwork Elephant is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by David McKee. The story follows Elmer, a young elephant with a unique appearance - he is covered in a patchwork of colors. The book is suitable for children between the ages of 3 and 8 years old, and it teaches valuable life lessons about embracing one&amp;rsquo;s individuality and the importance of friendship.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
