<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Childrens Books that talk about &#39;Choose&#39; on Monsty The Monster Truck</title>
    <link>https://www.monsty.co/tags/childrens-books-that-talk-about-choose/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Childrens Books that talk about &#39;Choose&#39; on Monsty The Monster Truck</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.monsty.co/tags/childrens-books-that-talk-about-choose/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>There Will Be Wolves</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/there_will_be_wolves_by_karleen_bradford_isbn_9780525675396/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/there_will_be_wolves_by_karleen_bradford_isbn_9780525675396/</guid>
      <description>There Will Be Wolves by Karleen Bradford Title: There Will Be Wolves Author: Karleen Bradford Review: There Will Be Wolves is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Karleen Bradford, which tells the story of a young boy named Connor who is forced to confront his fears and overcome challenges in a thrilling adventure. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 8 and 12, and it teaches valuable life lessons about courage, resilience, and the importance of family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tomorrow, When the War Began</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/tomorrow_when_the_war_began_by_john_marsden_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/tomorrow_when_the_war_began_by_john_marsden_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Tomorrow, When the War Began by John Marsden Title: Tomorrow, When the War Began Author: John Marsden Review: Tomorrow, When the War Began is a gripping novel written by John Marsden, which takes the readers on an adventurous journey through the eyes of a group of teenagers. The book is a perfect blend of action, suspense, and emotional depth, making it an ideal read for young adults. The story revolves around a group of seven friends who embark on a camping trip to a remote area, only to return and find their hometown occupied by a foreign military force.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kensuke&#39;s Kingdom</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/kensukes_kingdom_by_michael_morpurgo_isbn_1405267372/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/kensukes_kingdom_by_michael_morpurgo_isbn_1405267372/</guid>
      <description>Kensuke&amp;rsquo;s Kingdom by Michael Morpurgo Title: Kensuke&amp;rsquo;s Kingdom Author: Michael Morpurgo Review: Kensuke&amp;rsquo;s Kingdom is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Michael Morpurgo. The story revolves around a young boy named Michael who embarks on a thrilling adventure with his family. The book is targeted towards children aged 8-12 years old and is a perfect blend of adventure, friendship, and self-discovery. The story begins with Michael and his family setting sail on a yacht to fulfill their dream of exploring the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Platero and I</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/platero_and_i_isbn_9780292733282/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/platero_and_i_isbn_9780292733282/</guid>
      <description>Platero and I Title: Platero and I Author: Juan Ramón Jiménez Recommended Age Group: 8-12 years old Platero and I is a beautifully written and illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book that captures the essence of a young boy&amp;rsquo;s adventures with his loyal donkey, Platero, in a small Andalusian village. The book is filled with heartwarming stories that touch upon various life lessons, making it an excellent choice for children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Madeline</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/madeline_isbn_9863380156/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/madeline_isbn_9863380156/</guid>
      <description>Madeline Title: Madeline Author: Ludwig Bemelmans Madeline is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the adventures of a young girl named Madeline, who lives in a boarding school in Paris. The story, written by Ludwig Bemelmans, is a timeless classic that has been cherished by generations of children and adults alike. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 4 and 8, making it an excellent choice for early readers or as a bedtime story.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
