<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Childrens Books that talk about &#39;Simplicity&#39; on Monsty The Monster Truck</title>
    <link>https://www.monsty.co/tags/childrens-books-that-talk-about-simplicity/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Childrens Books that talk about &#39;Simplicity&#39; on Monsty The Monster Truck</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.monsty.co/tags/childrens-books-that-talk-about-simplicity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>When the World Was Still Young</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/when_the_world_was_still_young_by_jurg_schubiger_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/when_the_world_was_still_young_by_jurg_schubiger_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>When the World Was Still Young by Jurg Schubiger Title: When the World Was Still Young Author: Jurg Schubiger Review: When the World Was Still Young is a beautifully illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young boy named Jonas who embarks on a magical adventure. The book is suitable for children between the ages of 6 and 10 years old. The story follows Jonas as he discovers a hidden door in his grandfather&amp;rsquo;s attic, which leads him to a world where time has stopped.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Summer Book</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_summer_book_isbn_140042725/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_summer_book_isbn_140042725/</guid>
      <description>The Summer Book Title: The Summer Book Review: The Summer Book is a charming and delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that captures the essence of a summer spent on a beautiful island. Written by Tove Jansson, the book follows the adventures of a young girl named Sophia and her grandmother as they explore the island, its flora, and fauna, and learn valuable life lessons along the way. Target Age Group: The Summer Book is perfect for children between the ages of 6 and 12.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marianne Dreams</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/marianne_dreams_by_catherine_storr_isbn_140302093/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/marianne_dreams_by_catherine_storr_isbn_140302093/</guid>
      <description>Marianne Dreams by Catherine Storr Title: Marianne Dreams Author: Catherine Storr Marianne Dreams is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Catherine Storr. This imaginative story follows the life of a young girl named Marianne, who is confined to her bed due to an illness. To pass the time, she starts drawing a picture of a house, which in turn, becomes a portal to a mysterious and magical world. The target age group for this book is 8-12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Woods in Windri</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/woods_in_windri_by_violet_needham_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/woods_in_windri_by_violet_needham_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Woods in Windri by Violet Needham Title: Woods in Windri Author: Violet Needham Review: Woods in Windri is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Violet Needham. The story is set in a charming and magical world, filled with enchanting creatures and beautiful landscapes. The book is suitable for children between the ages of 8 and 12, as it offers an engaging and captivating narrative that will keep young readers entertained while also teaching valuable life lessons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The White Stone</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_white_stone_by_gunnel_linde_isbn_152959106/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_white_stone_by_gunnel_linde_isbn_152959106/</guid>
      <description>The White Stone by Gunnel Linde Title: The White Stone Author: Gunnel Linde Review: The White Stone is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Gunnel Linde that tells the story of a young girl named Mia, who is trying to find her place in the world. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old and covers various life lessons that are essential for their growth and development.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little Onion</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/little_onion_by_gianni_rodari_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/little_onion_by_gianni_rodari_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Little Onion by Gianni Rodari Title: Little Onion Author: Gianni Rodari Review: Little Onion, written by Gianni Rodari, is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that captivates the imagination of young readers. The story follows the adventures of a young boy named Onion who embarks on a series of magical journeys with his animal friends. The book is filled with whimsical illustrations that add to the charm of the story. Target Age Group: Little Onion is perfect for children between the ages of 4 and 8.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Night on the Galactic Railroad</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/night_on_the_galactic_railroad_by_kenji_miyazawa_isbn_9781935548997/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/night_on_the_galactic_railroad_by_kenji_miyazawa_isbn_9781935548997/</guid>
      <description>Night on the Galactic Railroad by Kenji Miyazawa Title: Night on the Galactic Railroad Author: Kenji Miyazawa Review: Night on the Galactic Railroad is a beautifully written children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes readers on a magical journey through the cosmos. Author Kenji Miyazawa has crafted a captivating story that is perfect for young readers between the ages of 8 and 12. The book follows the adventures of two young boys, Giovanni and Campanella, as they embark on a fantastical train ride through the stars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peter Pan in Kensington Gardens</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/peter_pan_in_kensington_gardens_isbn_9781653813407/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/peter_pan_in_kensington_gardens_isbn_9781653813407/</guid>
      <description>Peter Pan in Kensington Gardens Title: Peter Pan in Kensington Gardens Author: J.M. Barrie Review: Peter Pan in Kensington Gardens is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that captures the essence of childhood innocence and imagination. Written by J.M. Barrie, the author of the classic tale of Peter Pan, this book takes readers on a magical journey through the eyes of Peter Pan as a young boy. The story follows Peter Pan as he explores the enchanted Kensington Gardens, where he encounters various fairies, animals, and other magical creatures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Platero and I</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/platero_and_i_isbn_9780292733282/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/platero_and_i_isbn_9780292733282/</guid>
      <description>Platero and I Title: Platero and I Author: Juan Ramón Jiménez Recommended Age Group: 8-12 years old Platero and I is a beautifully written and illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book that captures the essence of a young boy&amp;rsquo;s adventures with his loyal donkey, Platero, in a small Andalusian village. The book is filled with heartwarming stories that touch upon various life lessons, making it an excellent choice for children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In Mr. Thunder&#39;s House</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/in_mr._thunders_house_by_guido_quarzo_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/in_mr._thunders_house_by_guido_quarzo_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>In Mr. Thunder&amp;rsquo;s House by Guido Quarzo Title: In Mr. Thunder&amp;rsquo;s House Author: Guido Quarzo In Mr. Thunder&amp;rsquo;s House is a charming and delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Guido Quarzo. The story follows the adventures of a young boy named Tommy, who stumbles upon a magical house belonging to the enigmatic Mr. Thunder. As Tommy explores the house, he encounters various fantastical creatures and learns valuable life lessons along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lend Me Your Wings</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/lend_me_your_wings_by_john_agard_isbn_9780316020107/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/lend_me_your_wings_by_john_agard_isbn_9780316020107/</guid>
      <description>Lend Me Your Wings by John Agard Title: Lend Me Your Wings Author: John Agard Lend Me Your Wings is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by John Agard, a well-known poet and author. This engaging story is perfect for children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old. The book is filled with beautiful illustrations that capture the imagination and bring the story to life. The story follows a young boy named Joe, who discovers a magical pair of wings that allow him to fly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Real Thief</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_real_thief_by_william_steig_isbn_1782691456/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_real_thief_by_william_steig_isbn_1782691456/</guid>
      <description>The Real Thief by William Steig Title: The Real Thief Author: William Steig Target Age Group: 5-10 years old The Real Thief is a beautifully illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book by William Steig, which tells the story of a young mouse named Pearl who is accused of stealing a cherished diamond ring. The book explores themes of friendship, trust, and honesty, making it a perfect read for children between the ages of 5 and 10 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amos and Boris</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/amos_and_boris_by_william_steig_isbn_9781846145254/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/amos_and_boris_by_william_steig_isbn_9781846145254/</guid>
      <description>Amos and Boris by William Steig Title: Amos and Boris Author: William Steig Review: Amos and Boris is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the talented William Steig. The story follows the adventures of Amos, a mouse, and Boris, a whale, as they form an unlikely friendship. The book is beautifully illustrated with Steig&amp;rsquo;s signature style, making it visually appealing for young readers. The target age group for Amos and Boris is 4 to 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blueberries for Sal</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/blueberries_for_sal_by_robert_mccloskey_isbn_9780812422085/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/blueberries_for_sal_by_robert_mccloskey_isbn_9780812422085/</guid>
      <description>Blueberries for Sal by Robert McCloskey Title: Blueberries for Sal Author: Robert McCloskey Review: Blueberries for Sal is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written and illustrated by Robert McCloskey. First published in 1948, this timeless classic has continued to charm readers of all ages with its heartwarming story and beautiful illustrations. The book tells the story of a young girl named Sal and her mother, who go blueberry picking on a beautiful summer day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harold and the Purple Crayon</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/harold_and_the_purple_crayon_isbn_9780439132534/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/harold_and_the_purple_crayon_isbn_9780439132534/</guid>
      <description>Harold and the Purple Crayon Title: Harold and the Purple Crayon Author: Crockett Johnson Recommended Age Group: 4-8 years old &amp;ldquo;Harold and the Purple Crayon&amp;rdquo; is a timeless classic that has been enjoyed by children for generations. The story follows the adventures of a young boy named Harold, who uses his purple crayon to create a world of his own. This imaginative tale teaches valuable life lessons and is perfect for children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Emperor&#39;s New Clothes</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_emperors_new_clothes_isbn_9780831727369/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_emperors_new_clothes_isbn_9780831727369/</guid>
      <description>The Emperor&amp;rsquo;s New Clothes Title: The Emperor&amp;rsquo;s New Clothes Author: Hans Christian Andersen Illustrator: Virginia Lee Burton Target Age Group: 4-8 years old The Emperor&amp;rsquo;s New Clothes is a classic children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Hans Christian Andersen and beautifully illustrated by Virginia Lee Burton. The story is about an Emperor who is obsessed with his appearance and clothing. He is tricked by two swindlers who claim to make the most magnificent clothes that can only be seen by the wise and competent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mr Archimedes&#39; Bath</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/mr_archimedes_bath_by_pamela_allen_isbn_688419194/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/mr_archimedes_bath_by_pamela_allen_isbn_688419194/</guid>
      <description>Mr Archimedes&amp;rsquo; Bath by Pamela Allen Title: Mr Archimedes&amp;rsquo; Bath Author: Pamela Allen &amp;ldquo;Mr Archimedes&amp;rsquo; Bath&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the talented author, Pamela Allen. The story follows the adventures of a dog named Mr. Archimedes, who loves taking baths in the bathtub. One day, he discovers that the water level in the bathtub is rising, and he embarks on a journey to find out why. This book is an excellent choice for children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fly, Little Bird</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/fly_little_bird_by_francesco_tullio_altan_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/fly_little_bird_by_francesco_tullio_altan_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Fly, Little Bird by Francesco Tullio Altan Title: Fly, Little Bird Author: Francesco Tullio Altan Fly, Little Bird is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book by Francesco Tullio Altan that tells the story of a young bird who dreams of flying high and exploring the world. The book is perfect for children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old, as it is filled with colorful illustrations and simple, yet engaging language.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
