<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Childrens Books that talk about &#39;Discrimination&#39; on Monsty The Monster Truck</title>
    <link>https://www.monsty.co/tags/childrens-books-that-talk-about-discrimination/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Childrens Books that talk about &#39;Discrimination&#39; on Monsty The Monster Truck</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.monsty.co/tags/childrens-books-that-talk-about-discrimination/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Crispin</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/crispin_isbn_9780606305556/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/crispin_isbn_9780606305556/</guid>
      <description>Crispin Title: Crispin Author: Avi Review: Crispin is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Avi, which tells the story of a young boy named Crispin, who embarks on a thrilling adventure in medieval England. The book is targeted towards children aged 8-12, as it features themes of friendship, bravery, and perseverance. The story follows Crispin, a 13-year-old boy who is falsely accused of a crime and forced to flee his village.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Johnny, My Friend</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/johnny_my_friend_by_peter_pohl_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/johnny_my_friend_by_peter_pohl_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Johnny, My Friend by Peter Pohl Title: Johnny, My Friend Author: Peter Pohl Review: &amp;ldquo;Johnny, My Friend&amp;rdquo; is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Peter Pohl. The story follows the adventures of a young boy named Johnny and his best friend, a magical talking dog named Rover. Together, they embark on a series of exciting and imaginative adventures that teach valuable life lessons along the way. The book is beautifully illustrated, with vibrant and engaging pictures that capture the essence of each scene.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stone Cold</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/stone_cold_by_robert_swindells_isbn_9780745173993/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/stone_cold_by_robert_swindells_isbn_9780745173993/</guid>
      <description>Stone Cold by Robert Swindells Title: Stone Cold Author: Robert Swindells Review: Stone Cold by Robert Swindells is a captivating and thought-provoking children&amp;rsquo;s book that explores the complex themes of homelessness, family dynamics, and the power of friendship. The story follows the life of a young boy named Link, who finds himself homeless after his father&amp;rsquo;s death and his mother&amp;rsquo;s inability to cope. The book is well-written and engaging, making it an excellent choice for children aged 10-14.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Devil&#39;s Arithmetic</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_devils_arithmetic_by_jane_yolen_isbn_9781664495296/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_devils_arithmetic_by_jane_yolen_isbn_9781664495296/</guid>
      <description>The Devil&amp;rsquo;s Arithmetic by Jane Yolen Title: The Devil&amp;rsquo;s Arithmetic Author: Jane Yolen Review: The Devil&amp;rsquo;s Arithmetic, written by Jane Yolen, is a poignant and thought-provoking children&amp;rsquo;s book that delves into the harsh realities of the Holocaust. The story follows a young girl named Hannah, who is transported back in time to a concentration camp during the Holocaust. Through her experiences, she learns the importance of remembering and honoring the past, as well as the value of courage and resilience in the face of adversity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Carrie&#39;s War</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/carries_war_isbn_9780575016316/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/carries_war_isbn_9780575016316/</guid>
      <description>Carrie&amp;rsquo;s War Title: Carrie&amp;rsquo;s War Author: Nina Bawden Review: Carrie&amp;rsquo;s War is a heartwarming and engaging children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Nina Bawden. The story is set during World War II and follows the adventures of two siblings, Carrie and Nick, who are evacuated from London to a small Welsh village. The book targets the age group of 8-12 years old and provides an excellent opportunity for young readers to learn about the historical context of World War II.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gentle Ben</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/gentle_ben_by_walt_morey_isbn_9781581181197/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/gentle_ben_by_walt_morey_isbn_9781581181197/</guid>
      <description>Gentle Ben by Walt Morey Title: Gentle Ben Author: Walt Morey Gentle Ben is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Walt Morey, which tells the story of a young boy named Mark and his adventures with a large, lovable bear named Ben. The book is suitable for children aged 8-12, as it contains themes of friendship, loyalty, and the importance of preserving nature. The story begins with Mark, a young boy who is grieving the loss of his father and struggling to adjust to his new life in the Alaskan wilderness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Am David</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/i_am_david_isbn_416233406/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/i_am_david_isbn_416233406/</guid>
      <description>I Am David Title: I Am David Author: Anne Holm Review: I Am David is a heartwarming and adventurous children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young boy named David, who escapes from a Bulgarian labor camp and embarks on a journey to find freedom and a new life. The book is beautifully written by Anne Holm, and it captures the essence of hope, resilience, and the human spirit. The story is suitable for children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old, as it contains themes of friendship, courage, and self-discovery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To Kill a Mockingbird</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/to_kill_a_mockingbird_by_harper_lee_isbn_434012602/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/to_kill_a_mockingbird_by_harper_lee_isbn_434012602/</guid>
      <description>To Kill a Mockingbird by Harper Lee Title: To Kill a Mockingbird Author: Harper Lee Review: To Kill a Mockingbird, written by Harper Lee, is a captivating novel that tells the story of a young girl named Scout Finch and her brother Jem, growing up in the fictional town of Maycomb, Alabama during the 1930s. Through the eyes of these innocent children, the reader is exposed to the harsh realities of racism, prejudice, and injustice that were prevalent in the American South during that time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heart</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/heart_by_edmondo_de_amicis_isbn_9781410103154/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/heart_by_edmondo_de_amicis_isbn_9781410103154/</guid>
      <description>Heart by Edmondo De Amicis Title: Heart Author: Edmondo De Amicis Review: Heart, written by Edmondo De Amicis, is a beautifully crafted children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes young readers on a heartwarming journey through the ups and downs of life. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 8 and 12, as it deals with themes of friendship, kindness, and empathy. The story follows the adventures of a young boy named Enrico, who learns valuable life lessons from his interactions with the people around him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Something&#39;s Fishy, Hazel Green!</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/somethings_fishy_hazel_green_by_odo_hirsch_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/somethings_fishy_hazel_green_by_odo_hirsch_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Something&amp;rsquo;s Fishy, Hazel Green! by Odo Hirsch Title: Something&amp;rsquo;s Fishy, Hazel Green! Author: Odo Hirsch Review: &amp;ldquo;Something&amp;rsquo;s Fishy, Hazel Green!&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Odo Hirsch, which takes readers on a captivating journey through the eyes of its protagonist, Hazel Green. The story follows Hazel as she sets out to uncover the mystery behind a peculiar smell that has been plaguing her school. The book is primarily targeted towards children between the ages of 7 to 10 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Am Susannah</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/i_am_susannah_by_libby_gleeson_isbn_082340742x/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/i_am_susannah_by_libby_gleeson_isbn_082340742x/</guid>
      <description>I Am Susannah by Libby Gleeson Title: I Am Susannah Author: Libby Gleeson Target Age Group: 6-10 years old Review: &amp;ldquo;I Am Susannah&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young girl named Susannah, who embarks on a journey of self-discovery and learns the importance of embracing her unique qualities. The book, written by Libby Gleeson, is an engaging and heartwarming tale that is perfect for children between the ages of 6 and 10 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Journey to Jo&#39;burg</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/journey_to_joburg_by_beverley_naidoo_isbn_9780064402378/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/journey_to_joburg_by_beverley_naidoo_isbn_9780064402378/</guid>
      <description>Journey to Jo&amp;rsquo;burg by Beverley Naidoo Title: Journey to Jo&amp;rsquo;burg Author: Beverley Naidoo Review: Journey to Jo&amp;rsquo;burg is a heartwarming and thought-provoking children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Beverley Naidoo. The story follows two siblings, Naledi and Tiro, as they embark on a journey from their small village to the big city of Johannesburg in search of their mother. Set against the backdrop of apartheid-era South Africa, the book tackles important themes such as family, friendship, and the struggle for equality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schoolboy Jia Li</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/schoolboy_jia_li_by_qin_wenjun_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/schoolboy_jia_li_by_qin_wenjun_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Schoolboy Jia Li by Qin Wenjun Title: Schoolboy Jia Li Author: Qin Wenjun Schoolboy Jia Li is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Qin Wenjun, which follows the story of a young boy named Jia Li as he navigates through the ups and downs of school life. This heartwarming tale is perfect for children between the ages of 6 and 10, as it addresses various life lessons and challenges that young readers can relate to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two Weeks With the Queen</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/two_weeks_with_the_queen_by_morris_gleitzman_isbn_3300781/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/two_weeks_with_the_queen_by_morris_gleitzman_isbn_3300781/</guid>
      <description>Two Weeks With the Queen by Morris Gleitzman Title: Two Weeks With the Queen Author: Morris Gleitzman Review: Two Weeks With the Queen is a heartwarming and poignant children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Morris Gleitzman. The story follows the journey of a young boy named Colin, who embarks on a mission to find a cure for his terminally ill brother. Along the way, he encounters various characters, each with their own lessons to teach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crusade in Jeans</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/crusade_in_jeans_isbn_9781935954071/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/crusade_in_jeans_isbn_9781935954071/</guid>
      <description>Crusade in Jeans Title: Crusade in Jeans Author: Thea Beckman Review: Crusade in Jeans is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young boy named Dolf, who is unexpectedly transported back in time to the Middle Ages. The book, written by Thea Beckman, is an engaging and thought-provoking adventure that is perfect for children aged 10-14. The story is filled with historical details, and it provides an exciting and immersive way for young readers to learn about the past.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Celia Says</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/what_celia_says_by_elena_fortun_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/what_celia_says_by_elena_fortun_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>What Celia Says by Elena Fortun Title: What Celia Says Author: Elena Fortun &amp;ldquo;What Celia Says&amp;rdquo; is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Elena Fortun, which tells the story of a young girl named Celia who has a unique way of looking at the world. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 5 to 10 years old, and it is an excellent choice for parents and teachers looking for a book that teaches valuable life lessons in a fun and engaging manner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gumdrop</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/gumdrop_by_val_biro_isbn_340714492/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/gumdrop_by_val_biro_isbn_340714492/</guid>
      <description>Gumdrop by Val Biro Title: Gumdrop Author: Val Biro Gumdrop, written by Val Biro, is a charming and engaging children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the adventures of a little car named Gumdrop. The story is perfect for children between the ages of 4 and 8, as it is filled with colorful illustrations and simple language that young readers can easily understand and enjoy. The book&amp;rsquo;s main character, Gumdrop, is a friendly and curious little car who loves to explore the world around him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Doll&#39;s House</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_dolls_house_by_rumer_godden_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_dolls_house_by_rumer_godden_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Doll&amp;rsquo;s House by Rumer Godden Title: The Doll&amp;rsquo;s House Author: Rumer Godden The Doll&amp;rsquo;s House, written by Rumer Godden, is a charming and enchanting children&amp;rsquo;s book that captures the essence of childhood imagination and the importance of friendship. The story revolves around two young sisters, Tottie and Emily, who receive a beautiful dollhouse as a gift. The dollhouse becomes a magical world where the dolls come to life and experience their own adventures.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
