<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Childrens Books that talk about &#39;Trust&#39; on Monsty The Monster Truck</title>
    <link>https://www.monsty.co/tags/childrens-books-that-talk-about-trust/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Childrens Books that talk about &#39;Trust&#39; on Monsty The Monster Truck</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.monsty.co/tags/childrens-books-that-talk-about-trust/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A Boat in the Forest</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/a_boat_in_the_forest_by_paola_mastrocola_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/a_boat_in_the_forest_by_paola_mastrocola_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>A Boat in the Forest by Paola Mastrocola Title: A Boat in the Forest Author: Paola Mastrocola A Boat in the Forest is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young boy named Leo who discovers a mysterious boat hidden deep in the forest. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 5 and 8, as it features colorful illustrations and simple language that is easy for young readers to understand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crispin</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/crispin_isbn_9780606305556/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/crispin_isbn_9780606305556/</guid>
      <description>Crispin Title: Crispin Author: Avi Review: Crispin is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Avi, which tells the story of a young boy named Crispin, who embarks on a thrilling adventure in medieval England. The book is targeted towards children aged 8-12, as it features themes of friendship, bravery, and perseverance. The story follows Crispin, a 13-year-old boy who is falsely accused of a crime and forced to flee his village.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Am Not Esther</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/i_am_not_esther_by_fleur_beale_isbn_9781864470598/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/i_am_not_esther_by_fleur_beale_isbn_9781864470598/</guid>
      <description>I Am Not Esther by Fleur Beale Title: I Am Not Esther Author: Fleur Beale Review: I Am Not Esther is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Fleur Beale, which tells the story of a young girl named Kirby who is forced to live with her estranged relatives after her mother&amp;rsquo;s sudden death. The book primarily targets children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old, as it explores themes of family, friendship, and self-discovery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monster Blood Tattoo: Foundling</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/monster_blood_tattoo_foundling_by_david_cornish_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/monster_blood_tattoo_foundling_by_david_cornish_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Monster Blood Tattoo: Foundling by David Cornish Title: Monster Blood Tattoo: Foundling Author: David Cornish Review: Monster Blood Tattoo: Foundling is a thrilling and adventurous children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes readers on a journey through a fantastical world filled with mysterious creatures and unforgettable characters. Written by David Cornish, this book is the first installment in the Monster Blood Tattoo trilogy. The story follows the life of a young orphan named Rossamund, who has just been accepted into the prestigious Branden Rose School for Foundlings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>River Boy</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/river_boy_isbn_1421804271/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/river_boy_isbn_1421804271/</guid>
      <description>River Boy Title: River Boy Author: Tim Bowler Review: River Boy is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Tim Bowler, which tells the story of a young boy named Tom who embarks on a journey to find the truth about his father&amp;rsquo;s mysterious disappearance. The book is filled with adventure, suspense, and emotional depth, making it an engaging read for young readers. Target Age Group: River Boy is suitable for children between the ages of 9 and 12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>See How They Run</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/see_how_they_run_by_david_mcrobbie_isbn_140381015/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/see_how_they_run_by_david_mcrobbie_isbn_140381015/</guid>
      <description>See How They Run by David Mcrobbie Title: See How They Run Author: David McRobbie &amp;ldquo;See How They Run&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by David McRobbie, which takes young readers on a captivating journey through the world of animals. This book is an excellent choice for children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old, as it is filled with vibrant illustrations and simple, yet engaging text. The story follows a group of animals as they race through the forest, each with their unique abilities and personalities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slaves of Quentaris</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/slaves_of_quentaris_by_paul_collins_isbn_9780734405579/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/slaves_of_quentaris_by_paul_collins_isbn_9780734405579/</guid>
      <description>Slaves of Quentaris by Paul Collins Title: Slaves of Quentaris Author: Paul Collins Slaves of Quentaris is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Paul Collins, which takes the reader on a thrilling adventure through the fantastical world of Quentaris. The story follows the journey of two young protagonists, Tilda and Tobin, who find themselves enslaved in the underground city of Quentaris. Target Age Group: The book is primarily targeted towards children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Gifting</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_gifting_by_sophie_masson_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_gifting_by_sophie_masson_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Gifting by Sophie Masson Title: The Gifting Author: Sophie Masson The Gifting is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Sophie Masson, which takes readers on a magical journey through the enchanting world of the Faraway Tree. The story is a perfect blend of adventure, friendship, and self-discovery, making it an ideal read for children between the ages of 8 and 12. The book revolves around the life of a young girl named Emily, who finds herself embarking on a thrilling quest to save the enchanted world of the Faraway Tree from an evil sorcerer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Red Shoe</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_red_shoe_by_ursula_dubosarsky_isbn_9781406358742/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_red_shoe_by_ursula_dubosarsky_isbn_9781406358742/</guid>
      <description>The Red Shoe by Ursula Dubosarsky Title: The Red Shoe Author: Ursula Dubosarsky Genre: Children&amp;rsquo;s Fiction, Mystery Age Group: 8-12 years old &amp;ldquo;The Red Shoe&amp;rdquo; is a captivating and thought-provoking children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Ursula Dubosarsky. This intriguing mystery story is suitable for children aged 8-12 years old and offers valuable life lessons that can be appreciated by readers of all ages. The story revolves around a young girl named Matilda, who stumbles upon a pair of mysterious red shoes while exploring her grandmother&amp;rsquo;s attic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Running Man</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_running_man_by_michael_gerard_bauer_isbn_61455083/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_running_man_by_michael_gerard_bauer_isbn_61455083/</guid>
      <description>The Running Man by Michael Gerard Bauer Title: The Running Man Author: Michael Gerard Bauer Target Age Group: 8-12 years old Review: The Running Man is a heartwarming and engaging children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Michael Gerard Bauer. The story follows the life of a young boy named Joseph who is trying to find his place in the world. Throughout the book, Joseph faces various challenges, including dealing with bullies, making friends, and understanding the importance of family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Witch Child</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_witch_child_isbn_722658389/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_witch_child_isbn_722658389/</guid>
      <description>The Witch Child Title: The Witch Child Author: Virginia Pilegard Review: The Witch Child is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young girl named Mary who lives in a small village. Mary is different from the other children because she has a special gift - she can talk to animals. The story follows Mary as she uses her gift to help the animals in her village and teaches valuable life lessons along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Walk Two Moons</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/walk_two_moons_isbn_9780590649438/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/walk_two_moons_isbn_9780590649438/</guid>
      <description>Walk Two Moons Title: Walk Two Moons Author: Sharon Creech Review: Walk Two Moons is a beautifully written children&amp;rsquo;s novel by Sharon Creech, which tells the story of a young girl named Salamanca Tree Hiddle, who embarks on a journey to find her missing mother. The book is an engaging and thought-provoking read that explores themes of family, friendship, and the power of storytelling. Target Age Group: The book is suitable for children aged 9-12 years old, as it contains relatable themes and characters that resonate well with this age group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When the Snow Fell</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/when_the_snow_fell_by_henning_menkell_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/when_the_snow_fell_by_henning_menkell_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>When the Snow Fell by Henning Menkell Title: When the Snow Fell Author: Henning Menkell Review: When the Snow Fell is a heartwarming and engaging children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes young readers on a magical journey through the eyes of a young boy named Jonas. This beautifully illustrated book is perfect for children between the ages of 5 and 10 years old. The story follows Jonas as he experiences the wonders of a snowy winter day for the first time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whispers in the Graveyard</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/whispers_in_the_graveyard_isbn_749744804/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/whispers_in_the_graveyard_isbn_749744804/</guid>
      <description>Whispers in the Graveyard Title: Whispers in the Graveyard Author: Theresa Breslin Target Age Group: 8-12 years old &amp;ldquo;Whispers in the Graveyard&amp;rdquo; is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Theresa Breslin, which tells the story of a young boy named Solomon who possesses a unique gift – he can hear the whispers of the dead. The book is suitable for children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old, and it offers valuable life lessons that can help them navigate through various challenges in life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Pack of Lies</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/a_pack_of_lies_isbn_019271788x/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/a_pack_of_lies_isbn_019271788x/</guid>
      <description>A Pack of Lies Title: A Pack of Lies Author: Laurel Remington Genre: Children&amp;rsquo;s Fiction, Mystery A Pack of Lies is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes readers on a thrilling adventure filled with mystery and intrigue. Laurel Remington has done an excellent job of creating a story that captures the imagination of young readers and keeps them engaged from beginning to end. The book is targeted towards children aged 8-12 years old, making it an ideal choice for elementary school students.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Parcel of Patterns</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/a_parcel_of_patterns_by_jill_paton_walsh_isbn_722658982/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/a_parcel_of_patterns_by_jill_paton_walsh_isbn_722658982/</guid>
      <description>A Parcel of Patterns by Jill Paton Walsh Title: A Parcel of Patterns Author: Jill Paton Walsh A Parcel of Patterns is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book by Jill Paton Walsh, set in the 17th century during the time of the Great Plague. The story revolves around a young girl named Matilda, who lives in the village of Eyam. When the plague strikes, Matilda&amp;rsquo;s life takes a dramatic turn, and she must learn to cope with the challenges that come her way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brother in the Land</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/brother_in_the_land_by_robert_swindells_isbn_9780140317985/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/brother_in_the_land_by_robert_swindells_isbn_9780140317985/</guid>
      <description>Brother in the Land by Robert Swindells Title: Brother in the Land Author: Robert Swindells Target Age Group: 10-14 years old &amp;ldquo;Brother in the Land&amp;rdquo; is a poignant and thought-provoking novel by Robert Swindells that delves into the harsh realities of a post-apocalyptic world. The story is set in a small town in northern England, where the devastating effects of a nuclear war have left the landscape barren and the community struggling to survive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Caperucita En Manhattan</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/caperucita_en_manhattan_by_carmen_mart%C3%ADn_gaite_isbn_9788478442010/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/caperucita_en_manhattan_by_carmen_mart%C3%ADn_gaite_isbn_9788478442010/</guid>
      <description>Caperucita En Manhattan by Carmen Martín Gaite Title: Caperucita en Manhattan Author: Carmen Martín Gaite &amp;ldquo;Caperucita en Manhattan&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes the classic fairy tale of Little Red Riding Hood and gives it a modern twist. The story follows Caperucita, a young girl who lives in New York City, as she navigates the bustling streets of Manhattan. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 5 and 10 years old and teaches valuable life lessons along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First of Midnight</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/first_of_midnight_by_marjorie_darke_isbn_9780140327700/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/first_of_midnight_by_marjorie_darke_isbn_9780140327700/</guid>
      <description>First of Midnight by Marjorie Darke Title: First of Midnight Author: Marjorie Darke First of Midnight is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Marjorie Darke, which takes the readers on an enchanting journey through a world of magic, adventure, and self-discovery. This book is perfect for children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old, as it is filled with vivid imagery, engaging characters, and valuable life lessons. The story follows the protagonist, Midnight, a young girl who discovers she possesses magical powers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gold Dust</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/gold_dust_by_geraldine_mc_caughrean_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/gold_dust_by_geraldine_mc_caughrean_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Gold Dust by Geraldine Mc Caughrean Title: Gold Dust Author: Geraldine McCaughrean Review: Gold Dust by Geraldine McCaughrean is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes readers on a thrilling adventure through the African wilderness. The story is filled with vivid descriptions, engaging characters, and thought-provoking life lessons, making it a must-read for young readers. The book is suitable for children aged 8 to 12 years old, as it contains a mix of excitement, adventure, and valuable life lessons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Handles</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/handles_isbn_9781708024031/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/handles_isbn_9781708024031/</guid>
      <description>Handles Title: Handles Author: Jane Doe Review: Handles is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that captures the hearts of young readers with its engaging story and beautiful illustrations. The book, written by Jane Doe, is a perfect fit for children aged 4 to 8 years old. The story revolves around a lovable character named Handles, who is a little boy with a big heart. Handles goes on an adventure in his small town, where he encounters various challenges and learns valuable life lessons along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heart&#39;s Delight</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/hearts_delight_by_per_nilsson_isbn_9781886910928/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/hearts_delight_by_per_nilsson_isbn_9781886910928/</guid>
      <description>Heart&amp;rsquo;s Delight by Per Nilsson Title: Heart&amp;rsquo;s Delight Author: Per Nilsson Review: Heart&amp;rsquo;s Delight is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that captures the hearts of young readers with its charming story and beautiful illustrations. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 4 and 8, and it teaches valuable life lessons through its engaging narrative. The story revolves around a young girl named Elsa, who is given a special heart-shaped box by her grandmother.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hey, Dollface</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/hey_dollface_by_deborah_hautzig_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/hey_dollface_by_deborah_hautzig_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Hey, Dollface by Deborah Hautzig Title: Hey, Dollface Author: Deborah Hautzig Review: Hey, Dollface is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Deborah Hautzig. The story revolves around a young girl named Dollface, who is struggling to find her identity and place in the world. Throughout the book, Dollface encounters various challenges and experiences that help her grow and learn valuable life lessons. Target Age Group: Hey, Dollface is primarily targeted towards children between the ages of 8 and 12.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Memoirs of a Basque Cow</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/memoirs_of_a_basque_cow_by_bernardo_atxaga_isbn_9781912868018/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/memoirs_of_a_basque_cow_by_bernardo_atxaga_isbn_9781912868018/</guid>
      <description>Memoirs of a Basque Cow by Bernardo Atxaga Title: Memoirs of a Basque Cow Author: Bernardo Atxaga Genre: Children&amp;rsquo;s Literature, Fiction Recommended Age Group: 8-12 years old Review: Memoirs of a Basque Cow by Bernardo Atxaga is a charming and heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a cow named Koki, who lives in the Basque Country. Through Koki&amp;rsquo;s eyes, the reader is introduced to a world of farm animals, human characters, and the ups and downs of life on a farm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pagan&#39;s Crusade</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/pagans_crusade_by_catherine_jinks_isbn_9780763625849/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/pagans_crusade_by_catherine_jinks_isbn_9780763625849/</guid>
      <description>Pagan&amp;rsquo;s Crusade by Catherine Jinks Title: Pagan&amp;rsquo;s Crusade Author: Catherine Jinks Pagan&amp;rsquo;s Crusade is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the talented author, Catherine Jinks. The story follows the adventures of a young boy named Pagan as he embarks on a thrilling crusade to rescue his kidnapped sister. The book is primarily targeted towards children aged 8-12 years old, as it contains elements of adventure, history, and fantasy that are likely to captivate young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rocco</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/rocco_by_sherryl_jordan_isbn_9780590540056/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/rocco_by_sherryl_jordan_isbn_9780590540056/</guid>
      <description>Rocco by Sherryl Jordan Title: Rocco Author: Sherryl Jordan Review: Rocco is a heartwarming and adventurous children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Sherryl Jordan. The story follows a young boy named Rocco who lives in a small Italian village with his family. Rocco dreams of becoming a great artist, but his father wants him to follow in his footsteps and become a fisherman. When Rocco&amp;rsquo;s father falls ill, Rocco must make a difficult decision - should he stay and help his family or follow his dreams?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rowan of Rin</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/rowan_of_rin_by_emily_rodda_isbn_590556576/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/rowan_of_rin_by_emily_rodda_isbn_590556576/</guid>
      <description>Rowan of Rin by Emily Rodda Title: Rowan of Rin Author: Emily Rodda Review: Rowan of Rin is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes the reader on an exciting adventure with its relatable characters and engaging storyline. The author, Emily Rodda, has skillfully crafted a tale that will appeal to young readers and keep them entertained from beginning to end. The story revolves around Rowan, a young boy who is considered the weakest and most unlikely hero in the village of Rin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Strange Objects</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/strange_objects_by_gary_crew_isbn_067179759x/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/strange_objects_by_gary_crew_isbn_067179759x/</guid>
      <description>Strange Objects by Gary Crew Title: Strange Objects Author: Gary Crew Review: Strange Objects is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Gary Crew, which tells the story of a young boy named Jack who stumbles upon a mysterious and enchanted world. The book is filled with beautiful illustrations and an engaging narrative that will keep young readers hooked from beginning to end. The target age group for this book is 8-12 years old, as it contains elements of adventure, mystery, and fantasy that are sure to captivate the imagination of young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talking in Whispers</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/talking_in_whispers_by_james_watson_isbn_9780575032729/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/talking_in_whispers_by_james_watson_isbn_9780575032729/</guid>
      <description>Talking in Whispers by James Watson Title: Talking in Whispers Author: James Watson Review: Talking in Whispers is a beautifully written children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young boy named David who learns the importance of trust, friendship, and standing up for what is right. The book is targeted towards children aged 8-12, and it covers important life lessons that are relevant to this age group. The story is set in a small town where David and his family live.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Cloud</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_cloud_by_gudrun_pausewang_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_cloud_by_gudrun_pausewang_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Cloud by Gudrun Pausewang Title: The Cloud Author: Gudrun Pausewang Review: The Cloud is a thought-provoking and captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book by Gudrun Pausewang that takes young readers on a journey through a post-apocalyptic world. This book is suitable for children between the ages of 8 and 12, and it effectively teaches important life lessons through its engaging storyline. The story follows a young girl named Sanna, who lives in a small village with her family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Gathering</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_gathering_by_isobelle_carmody_isbn_059054215x/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_gathering_by_isobelle_carmody_isbn_059054215x/</guid>
      <description>The Gathering by Isobelle Carmody Title: The Gathering Author: Isobelle Carmody The Gathering, written by Isobelle Carmody, is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the adventures of a young boy named Nathanial Delaney. This engaging story is targeted towards children between the ages of 8 to 12 years old. The book is set in a world where the Earth has been ravaged by environmental disasters, and humans have been forced to adapt to a new way of life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Ghost Drum</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_ghost_drum_isbn_571153402/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_ghost_drum_isbn_571153402/</guid>
      <description>The Ghost Drum Title: The Ghost Drum Author: Susan Price The Ghost Drum is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Susan Price, which takes readers on a magical journey through a world filled with mythical creatures and enchanting adventures. This book is an excellent choice for children aged 8 to 12 years old, as it offers a perfect blend of fantasy, mystery, and suspense. The story revolves around a young girl named Siri, who is chosen by the mythical creatures known as the Huldrefolk to become their champion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Neverending Story</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_neverending_story_isbn_9780140076196/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_neverending_story_isbn_9780140076196/</guid>
      <description>The Neverending Story Title: The Neverending Story Author: Michael Ende The Neverending Story is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Michael Ende, which takes the reader on a magical journey through the world of Fantastica. This enchanting tale is perfect for children between the ages of 8 and 12, as it offers a perfect blend of adventure, fantasy, and valuable life lessons. The story revolves around a young boy named Bastian Balthazar Bux, who stumbles upon a mysterious book called &amp;ldquo;The Neverending Story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Ruby in the Smoke</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_ruby_in_the_smoke_isbn_9780394988269/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_ruby_in_the_smoke_isbn_9780394988269/</guid>
      <description>The Ruby in the Smoke Title: The Ruby in the Smoke Author: Philip Pullman Review: The Ruby in the Smoke is a captivating and thrilling mystery novel by Philip Pullman, which is perfect for elementary school students. The story follows the adventures of Sally Lockhart, a sixteen-year-old girl living in Victorian London, as she tries to uncover the truth behind her father&amp;rsquo;s mysterious death and the elusive ruby. This book is targeted towards children aged 9-12 years old, as it contains themes of friendship, bravery, and perseverance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Scarecrows</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_scarecrows_isbn_9798725526912/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_scarecrows_isbn_9798725526912/</guid>
      <description>The Scarecrows Title: The Scarecrows Author: Beth Ferry Illustrator: The Fan Brothers Genre: Children&amp;rsquo;s Picture Book Recommended Age Group: 4-8 years old The Scarecrows is a heartwarming and visually stunning children&amp;rsquo;s picture book that tells the story of a group of scarecrows who come to life when the sun goes down. The story is a beautiful blend of whimsy and friendship, with vibrant illustrations that bring the characters to life. The target age group for this book is 4-8 years old, as the simple yet engaging storyline and vivid illustrations will capture the imagination of young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Sentinels</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_sentinels_by_peter_carter_isbn_9780862671952/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_sentinels_by_peter_carter_isbn_9780862671952/</guid>
      <description>The Sentinels by Peter Carter Title: The Sentinels Author: Peter Carter The Sentinels is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that captures the imagination of young readers and teaches them valuable life lessons. Author Peter Carter has created a world filled with adventure, mystery, and important messages that resonate with readers of all ages. The story follows the journey of a group of young friends who discover a hidden world within their own town.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Westing Game</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_westing_game_isbn_525423206/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_westing_game_isbn_525423206/</guid>
      <description>The Westing Game Title: The Westing Game Author: Ellen Raskin Review: The Westing Game is a captivating mystery novel written by Ellen Raskin, which was first published in 1978. This book is a perfect choice for elementary school children, particularly those between the ages of 8 and 12. The story is filled with intrigue, suspense, and humor, making it an enjoyable read for both children and adults alike. The Westing Game revolves around the mysterious death of Samuel Westing, a wealthy businessman, and the subsequent inheritance game that involves his heirs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thunder and Lightnings</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/thunder_and_lightnings_isbn_1484605667/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/thunder_and_lightnings_isbn_1484605667/</guid>
      <description>Thunder and Lightnings Title: Thunder and Lightnings Review: Thunder and Lightnings is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young boy named Tommy who learns the importance of friendship, bravery, and self-confidence. The book is targeted towards children aged 6-10 years old, as it contains engaging illustrations and a simple yet meaningful storyline. The book&amp;rsquo;s central theme revolves around Tommy, who is fascinated by thunder and lightning. He dreams of becoming a storm chaser, and with the help of his friends, he sets out on an adventure to catch a thunderstorm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thunderwith</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/thunderwith_by_libby_hathorn_isbn_732005566/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/thunderwith_by_libby_hathorn_isbn_732005566/</guid>
      <description>Thunderwith by Libby Hathorn Title: Thunderwith Author: Libby Hathorn Thunderwith is a beautifully written children&amp;rsquo;s book by Libby Hathorn that captures the imagination of young readers with its enchanting storytelling and vivid illustrations. The book is primarily targeted towards children between the ages of 6 and 10 years old, making it an excellent choice for elementary school students. The story follows the adventures of a young boy named Tim, who discovers a magical world filled with talking animals and a powerful storm called Thunderwith.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Titeuf</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/titeuf_isbn_9798671793536/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/titeuf_isbn_9798671793536/</guid>
      <description>Titeuf Title: Titeuf Author: Zep Recommended Age Group: 7-12 years old Titeuf is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the adventures of a young boy named Titeuf, who is always curious about the world around him. The book is filled with colorful illustrations and engaging stories that will capture the attention of young readers. One of the main themes in Titeuf is the importance of friendship. Throughout the book, Titeuf learns valuable lessons about being a good friend, such as sharing, being kind, and supporting one another.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tomorrow, When the War Began</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/tomorrow_when_the_war_began_by_john_marsden_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/tomorrow_when_the_war_began_by_john_marsden_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Tomorrow, When the War Began by John Marsden Title: Tomorrow, When the War Began Author: John Marsden Review: Tomorrow, When the War Began is a gripping novel written by John Marsden, which takes the readers on an adventurous journey through the eyes of a group of teenagers. The book is a perfect blend of action, suspense, and emotional depth, making it an ideal read for young adults. The story revolves around a group of seven friends who embark on a camping trip to a remote area, only to return and find their hometown occupied by a foreign military force.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tulku</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/tulku_isbn_9780140313574/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/tulku_isbn_9780140313574/</guid>
      <description>Tulku Title: Tulku Author: Pearl Zhu Review: &amp;ldquo;Tulku&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that captures the imagination of young readers with its enchanting story and vibrant illustrations. Author Pearl Zhu has crafted a heartwarming tale that follows the adventures of a young boy named Tulku, who embarks on a journey of self-discovery and friendship. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 5 and 10 years old. The language is simple and easy to understand, making it an excellent choice for early readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Kestrel for a Knave</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/a_kestrel_for_a_knave_isbn_1858481465/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/a_kestrel_for_a_knave_isbn_1858481465/</guid>
      <description>A Kestrel for a Knave Title: A Kestrel for a Knave Author: Barry Hines Recommended Age Group: 10-14 years old A Kestrel for a Knave is a captivating and thought-provoking novel by Barry Hines, which tells the story of Billy Casper, a young boy from a working-class family in a small English town. The book is a perfect blend of emotions, struggles, and triumphs, making it an excellent read for children between the ages of 10 and 14.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Wrinkle in Time</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/a_wrinkle_in_time_isbn_1250014107/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/a_wrinkle_in_time_isbn_1250014107/</guid>
      <description>A Wrinkle in Time Title: A Wrinkle in Time Author: Madeleine L&amp;rsquo;Engle Review: A Wrinkle in Time is a captivating and thought-provoking children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes readers on a thrilling adventure through time and space. Written by Madeleine L&amp;rsquo;Engle, this book is perfect for children between the ages of 8 and 12, as it explores themes of bravery, love, and the power of individuality. The story follows Meg Murry, a young girl who embarks on a quest to find her missing father.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chocky</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/chocky_isbn_14_003121_9/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/chocky_isbn_14_003121_9/</guid>
      <description>Chocky Title: Chocky Author: John Wyndham Genre: Science Fiction, Children&amp;rsquo;s Literature Recommended Age Group: 8-12 years old Chocky is a captivating science fiction novel written by John Wyndham, which tells the story of a young boy named Matthew who starts having conversations with an invisible entity named Chocky. The book is a perfect blend of adventure, mystery, and a touch of humor, making it an enjoyable read for children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Friday&#39;s Tunnel</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/fridays_tunnel_by_john_verney_isbn_30563003/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/fridays_tunnel_by_john_verney_isbn_30563003/</guid>
      <description>Friday&amp;rsquo;s Tunnel by John Verney Title: Friday&amp;rsquo;s Tunnel Author: John Verney &amp;ldquo;Friday&amp;rsquo;s Tunnel&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by John Verney, which takes young readers on a thrilling adventure filled with excitement, friendship, and valuable life lessons. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old, making it an excellent choice for elementary school students. The story revolves around Friday, a young boy who embarks on a journey through a magical tunnel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gentle Ben</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/gentle_ben_by_walt_morey_isbn_9781581181197/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/gentle_ben_by_walt_morey_isbn_9781581181197/</guid>
      <description>Gentle Ben by Walt Morey Title: Gentle Ben Author: Walt Morey Gentle Ben is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Walt Morey, which tells the story of a young boy named Mark and his adventures with a large, lovable bear named Ben. The book is suitable for children aged 8-12, as it contains themes of friendship, loyalty, and the importance of preserving nature. The story begins with Mark, a young boy who is grieving the loss of his father and struggling to adjust to his new life in the Alaskan wilderness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;m the King of the Castle</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/im_the_king_of_the_castle_by_susan_hill_isbn_9780141041940/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/im_the_king_of_the_castle_by_susan_hill_isbn_9780141041940/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m the King of the Castle by Susan Hill Title: I&amp;rsquo;m the King of the Castle Author: Susan Hill Review: &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m the King of the Castle&amp;rdquo; is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Susan Hill, which takes readers on a thrilling journey through the lives of two young boys, Joseph Hooper and Edmund Hooper. The story is set in the 1950s and is centered around themes of friendship, power dynamics, and the complexities of human relationships.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Julie &amp; the Wolves</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/julie__the_wolves_isbn_833578316/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/julie__the_wolves_isbn_833578316/</guid>
      <description>Julie &amp;amp; the Wolves Title: Julie &amp;amp; the Wolves Author: Jean Craighead George Recommended Age Group: 8-12 years old Julie &amp;amp; the Wolves is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Jean Craighead George. This beautifully written story is perfect for children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old. The book follows the journey of a young girl named Julie, who finds herself stranded in the Alaskan wilderness after a plane crash.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nobody&#39;s Family Is Going to Change</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/nobodys_family_is_going_to_change_by_louise_fitzhugh_isbn_333294505/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/nobodys_family_is_going_to_change_by_louise_fitzhugh_isbn_333294505/</guid>
      <description>Nobody&amp;rsquo;s Family Is Going to Change by Louise Fitzhugh Title: Nobody&amp;rsquo;s Family Is Going to Change Author: Louise Fitzhugh Review: &amp;ldquo;Nobody&amp;rsquo;s Family Is Going to Change&amp;rdquo; is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Louise Fitzhugh, which tells the story of a young boy named Tommy who is trying to find his place in the world. The book is perfect for children aged 8-12 years old, as it deals with themes of self-discovery, family dynamics, and acceptance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smith</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/smith_by_leon_garfield_isbn_9780844664552/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/smith_by_leon_garfield_isbn_9780844664552/</guid>
      <description>Smith by Leon Garfield Title: Smith Author: Leon Garfield Review: Smith, written by Leon Garfield, is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that captures the essence of adventure and the power of friendship. The story follows the life of a young boy named Smith, who embarks on a thrilling journey through the streets of London in the 18th century. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old, as it features an engaging plot and vivid illustrations that will keep young readers entertained and engaged.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tangara</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/tangara_by_nan_chauncy_isbn_192770942/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/tangara_by_nan_chauncy_isbn_192770942/</guid>
      <description>Tangara by Nan Chauncy Title: Tangara Author: Nan Chauncy Review: Tangara, written by Nan Chauncy, is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes readers on a magical journey through the eyes of a young boy named Tangara. The story is set in the picturesque Tasmanian wilderness and is filled with adventure, friendship, and the power of believing in oneself. The book is primarily targeted at children between the ages of 8 and 12, although readers of all ages can enjoy and appreciate the beautifully crafted story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Dolphin Crossing</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_dolphin_crossing_by_jill_paton_walsh_isbn_140366245/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_dolphin_crossing_by_jill_paton_walsh_isbn_140366245/</guid>
      <description>The Dolphin Crossing by Jill Paton Walsh Title: The Dolphin Crossing Author: Jill Paton Walsh The Dolphin Crossing is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Jill Paton Walsh, which takes the readers on an exciting adventure through the eyes of a young boy named Martin. This book is suitable for children between the ages of 8 to 12 years old, as it contains a perfect blend of adventure, friendship, and moral lessons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Edge of the Cloud</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_edge_of_the_cloud_isbn_9780192720023/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_edge_of_the_cloud_isbn_9780192720023/</guid>
      <description>The Edge of the Cloud Title: The Edge of the Cloud Author: Sarah L. Thomson Illustrator: Rob Dunlavey The Edge of the Cloud is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young girl named Lily, who discovers a magical cloud that transports her to different places and teaches her valuable life lessons. The book is beautifully illustrated by Rob Dunlavey, with vibrant colors and engaging images that capture the reader&amp;rsquo;s attention.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Letter for the King</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_letter_for_the_king_by_tonke_dragt_isbn_1782690263/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_letter_for_the_king_by_tonke_dragt_isbn_1782690263/</guid>
      <description>The Letter for the King by Tonke Dragt Title: The Letter for the King Author: Tonke Dragt Review: The Letter for the King is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Tonke Dragt. This engaging story follows the adventures of a young knight-in-training named Tiuri, who embarks on a perilous journey to deliver an important letter to the king. The book is a perfect blend of action, adventure, and mystery, making it an enjoyable read for children aged 8 to 12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Silver Brumby</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_silver_brumby_isbn_9780006932994/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_silver_brumby_isbn_9780006932994/</guid>
      <description>The Silver Brumby Title: The Silver Brumby Author: Elyne Mitchell The Silver Brumby is a heartwarming and adventurous children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Elyne Mitchell. This beautifully written story takes us on a journey through the Australian high country, following the life of a wild silver stallion named Thowra. The book is primarily targeted at children between the ages of 8 to 12 years old. However, its engaging storyline and captivating themes can be enjoyed by readers of all ages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Twelve and the Genii</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_twelve_and_the_genii_isbn_9780140309164/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_twelve_and_the_genii_isbn_9780140309164/</guid>
      <description>The Twelve and the Genii Title: The Twelve and the Genii Author: Pauline Baynes Genre: Children&amp;rsquo;s Fantasy Adventure Recommended Age Group: 8-12 years old &amp;ldquo;The Twelve and the Genii&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Pauline Baynes, a talented author and illustrator. The story follows the adventures of twelve children who stumble upon a magical world filled with genii, mythical creatures, and exciting challenges. The book is a perfect blend of fantasy, adventure, and humor, making it an enjoyable read for children aged 8-12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Witch of Blackbird Pond</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_witch_of_blackbird_pond_isbn_9780395913673/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_witch_of_blackbird_pond_isbn_9780395913673/</guid>
      <description>The Witch of Blackbird Pond Title: The Witch of Blackbird Pond Author: Elizabeth George Speare Genre: Historical Fiction, Children&amp;rsquo;s Literature Age Group: 8-12 years old &amp;ldquo;The Witch of Blackbird Pond&amp;rdquo; is a captivating historical fiction novel written by Elizabeth George Speare, which tells the story of a young orphan girl named Kit Tyler who moves from the lush Caribbean island of Barbados to the small, strict town of Wethersfield, Connecticut in 1687.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adventures of the Ingenious Alfanhui</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/adventures_of_the_ingenious_alfanhui_by_rafael_sanchez_ferlosio_isbn_1873982593/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/adventures_of_the_ingenious_alfanhui_by_rafael_sanchez_ferlosio_isbn_1873982593/</guid>
      <description>Adventures of the Ingenious Alfanhui by Rafael Sanchez Ferlosio Title: Adventures of the Ingenious Alfanhui Author: Rafael Sanchez Ferlosio Review: Adventures of the Ingenious Alfanhui is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes readers on a whimsical journey through the eyes of its young protagonist, Alfanhui. This book is a perfect choice for children between the ages of 8 and 12, as it is filled with engaging adventures, captivating illustrations, and valuable life lessons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Carry On, Mr. Bowditch</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/carry_on_mr._bowditch_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/carry_on_mr._bowditch_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Carry On, Mr. Bowditch Title: Carry On, Mr. Bowditch Author: Jean Lee Latham Recommended Age Group: 8-12 years old &amp;ldquo;Carry On, Mr. Bowditch&amp;rdquo; is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of Nathaniel Bowditch, a young boy who grew up to become a famous mathematician, astronomer, and navigator. This book is a perfect read for children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old, as it combines elements of adventure, history, and science.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cue for Treason</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/cue_for_treason_by_geoffrey_trease_isbn_014132726x/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/cue_for_treason_by_geoffrey_trease_isbn_014132726x/</guid>
      <description>Cue for Treason by Geoffrey Trease Title: Cue for Treason Author: Geoffrey Trease Review: Cue for Treason is a thrilling adventure story set in the 16th century, which follows the journey of two young boys, Peter and Tom, as they become entangled in a dangerous plot to overthrow Queen Elizabeth I. The book is an excellent choice for elementary school children, particularly those in the 8-12 age range, as it is filled with suspense, action, and historical intrigue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Capture the Castle</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/i_capture_the_castle_by_dodie_smith_isbn_8379430069/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/i_capture_the_castle_by_dodie_smith_isbn_8379430069/</guid>
      <description>I Capture the Castle by Dodie Smith Title: I Capture the Castle Author: Dodie Smith Review: I Capture the Castle is a charming and delightful novel that captures the essence of childhood and the complexities of growing up. The story follows the adventures of Cassandra Mortmain, a young girl living in a crumbling castle with her family. As Cassandra navigates the ups and downs of life, she learns valuable lessons about love, friendship, and the importance of staying true to oneself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jock of the Bushveld</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/jock_of_the_bushveld_isbn_9780548214954/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/jock_of_the_bushveld_isbn_9780548214954/</guid>
      <description>Jock of the Bushveld Title: Jock of the Bushveld Author: Sir Percy Fitzpatrick Jock of the Bushveld is a heartwarming and adventurous story about a young boy named Percy Fitzpatrick and his loyal dog, Jock. The book, written by Sir Percy Fitzpatrick, is based on true events that took place during Fitzpatrick&amp;rsquo;s childhood in the late 1800s in South Africa. The story follows Percy and Jock as they embark on various adventures together in the Bushveld, a region in the northern part of South Africa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jolanda, Daughter of the Black Corsair</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/jolanda_daughter_of_the_black_corsair_by_emilio_salgari_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/jolanda_daughter_of_the_black_corsair_by_emilio_salgari_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Jolanda, Daughter of the Black Corsair by Emilio Salgari Title: Jolanda, Daughter of the Black Corsair Author: Emilio Salgari Review: Jolanda, Daughter of the Black Corsair is a thrilling adventure story that follows the life of a young girl named Jolanda, who is the daughter of the infamous Black Corsair. This book is a perfect fit for children between the ages of 8 and 12, as it is filled with exciting pirate adventures, mysterious islands, and valuable life lessons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Missing From Saint-Agil</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/missing_from_saint-agil_by_pierre_very_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/missing_from_saint-agil_by_pierre_very_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Missing From Saint-Agil by Pierre Very Title: Missing from Saint-Agil Author: Pierre Very Target Age Group: 8-12 years old Review: &amp;ldquo;Missing from Saint-Agil&amp;rdquo; is a captivating mystery novel that will keep young readers on the edge of their seats. Written by Pierre Very, the story is set in the small town of Saint-Agil and follows the adventures of a group of children who come together to solve a perplexing mystery. The book is recommended for children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Friend Flicka</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/my_friend_flicka_isbn_9780812420777/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/my_friend_flicka_isbn_9780812420777/</guid>
      <description>My Friend Flicka Title: My Friend Flicka Author: Mary O&amp;rsquo;Hara Review: My Friend Flicka is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young boy named Ken McLaughlin and his adventures with his horse, Flicka. The book is written by Mary O&amp;rsquo;Hara and is suitable for children between the ages of 8 and 12. The story is set on a ranch in Wyoming and follows Ken as he learns the importance of responsibility, patience, and perseverance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Red Zora</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/red_zora_by_kurt_held_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/red_zora_by_kurt_held_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Red Zora by Kurt Held Title: Red Zora Author: Kurt Held Review: Red Zora is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Kurt Held that takes young readers on an adventurous journey through the life of Zora, a brave and independent girl who lives in a small village. The story is set in the early 20th century and is perfect for children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old. The book&amp;rsquo;s protagonist, Zora, is a strong-willed girl who is not afraid to challenge the norms of her society.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Cave Children</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_cave_children_by_alois_theodor_sonnleitner_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_cave_children_by_alois_theodor_sonnleitner_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Cave Children by Alois Theodor Sonnleitner Title: The Cave Children Author: Alois Theodor Sonnleitner Review: The Cave Children is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes readers on an adventurous journey through a world of imagination. The story follows a group of children who stumble upon a hidden cave and discover a magical new world filled with enchanting creatures and exciting challenges. Author Alois Theodor Sonnleitner has skillfully crafted a tale that is both engaging and educational, making it an ideal read for children between the ages of 7 and 12.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Fortunes of Philippa</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_fortunes_of_philippa_by_angela_brazil_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_fortunes_of_philippa_by_angela_brazil_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Fortunes of Philippa by Angela Brazil Title: The Fortunes of Philippa Author: Angela Brazil The Fortunes of Philippa is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Angela Brazil, which tells the story of a young girl named Philippa. The book is suitable for children between the ages of 8 and 12, and is a delightful read for young readers who enjoy stories with a touch of magic and adventure. The story revolves around Philippa, a young girl who has a special connection with animals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Hound of the Baskervilles</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_hound_of_the_baskervilles_isbn_1539611353/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_hound_of_the_baskervilles_isbn_1539611353/</guid>
      <description>The Hound of the Baskervilles Title: The Hound of the Baskervilles Author: Arthur Conan Doyle Review: The Hound of the Baskervilles is a captivating mystery novel that takes readers on a thrilling adventure through the eerie and treacherous landscape of Dartmoor. Written by Arthur Conan Doyle, this book is a perfect blend of suspense, intrigue, and clever detective work. The story follows the legendary detective, Sherlock Holmes, and his trusted companion, Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Path</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_path_by_miguel_deibes_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_path_by_miguel_deibes_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Path by Miguel Deibes Title: The Path Author: Miguel Deibes Review: The Path, written by Miguel Deibes, is a beautifully crafted children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes readers on a journey through the life of a young boy named Juan. The story is filled with vivid illustrations and thought-provoking messages that will captivate the hearts and minds of young readers. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 6 and 10 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Woods in Windri</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/woods_in_windri_by_violet_needham_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/woods_in_windri_by_violet_needham_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Woods in Windri by Violet Needham Title: Woods in Windri Author: Violet Needham Review: Woods in Windri is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Violet Needham. The story is set in a charming and magical world, filled with enchanting creatures and beautiful landscapes. The book is suitable for children between the ages of 8 and 12, as it offers an engaging and captivating narrative that will keep young readers entertained while also teaching valuable life lessons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cirque De Freak: A Living Nightmare</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/cirque_de_freak_a_living_nightmare_by_darren_shan_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/cirque_de_freak_a_living_nightmare_by_darren_shan_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Cirque De Freak: A Living Nightmare by Darren Shan Title: Cirque De Freak: A Living Nightmare Author: Darren Shan Review: Cirque De Freak: A Living Nightmare is a captivating and thrilling children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Darren Shan. The story follows the life of a young boy named Darren Shan, who becomes entangled in the mysterious world of vampires after attending a freak show with his best friend, Steve. The book is primarily targeted towards children between the ages of 10 to 14 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/harry_potter_and_the_goblet_of_fire_isbn_1413185096/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/harry_potter_and_the_goblet_of_fire_isbn_1413185096/</guid>
      <description>Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire Title: Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire Author: J.K. Rowling Target Age Group: 9-12 years old Review: Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire is the fourth book in the Harry Potter series by J.K. Rowling. This thrilling and magical adventure takes readers on a journey with Harry Potter and his friends, Ron Weasley and Hermione Granger, as they navigate the challenges of their fourth year at Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rupert the Rapper and Aunt Deep Freeze</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/rupert_the_rapper_and_aunt_deep_freeze_by_sinikka_and_tiina_nopola_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/rupert_the_rapper_and_aunt_deep_freeze_by_sinikka_and_tiina_nopola_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Rupert the Rapper and Aunt Deep Freeze by Sinikka and Tiina Nopola Title: Rupert the Rapper and Aunt Deep Freeze Author: Sinikka and Tiina Nopola Review: Rupert the Rapper and Aunt Deep Freeze is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young boy named Rupert who discovers his passion for rapping. The book is filled with engaging illustrations and an entertaining storyline that captures the attention of young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Something&#39;s Fishy, Hazel Green!</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/somethings_fishy_hazel_green_by_odo_hirsch_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/somethings_fishy_hazel_green_by_odo_hirsch_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Something&amp;rsquo;s Fishy, Hazel Green! by Odo Hirsch Title: Something&amp;rsquo;s Fishy, Hazel Green! Author: Odo Hirsch Review: &amp;ldquo;Something&amp;rsquo;s Fishy, Hazel Green!&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Odo Hirsch, which takes readers on a captivating journey through the eyes of its protagonist, Hazel Green. The story follows Hazel as she sets out to uncover the mystery behind a peculiar smell that has been plaguing her school. The book is primarily targeted towards children between the ages of 7 to 10 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Graveyard Book</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_graveyard_book_isbn_9780747598626/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_graveyard_book_isbn_9780747598626/</guid>
      <description>The Graveyard Book Title: The Graveyard Book Author: Neil Gaiman Review: The Graveyard Book is a captivating and enchanting novel written by the renowned author Neil Gaiman. This book is a perfect blend of mystery, adventure, and fantasy, making it an ideal read for children aged 8 to 12 years old. The story revolves around the life of a young boy named Nobody Owens, or Bod for short, who is adopted by the ghostly residents of a graveyard after his family is tragically murdered.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Three Musketeers</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_three_musketeers_by_alexandre_dumas_isbn_9781781399668/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_three_musketeers_by_alexandre_dumas_isbn_9781781399668/</guid>
      <description>The Three Musketeers by Alexandre Dumas Title: The Three Musketeers Author: Alexandre Dumas Review: The Three Musketeers, written by Alexandre Dumas, is a timeless classic that has been enjoyed by readers of all ages. This swashbuckling adventure, set in the 17th century, follows the story of a young man named d&amp;rsquo;Artagnan as he embarks on a journey to join the elite corps of the Musketeers in France. Along the way, he encounters Athos, Porthos, and Aramis, the three musketeers who become his close friends and companions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wolf Brother</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/wolf_brother_isbn_9781842551318/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/wolf_brother_isbn_9781842551318/</guid>
      <description>Wolf Brother Title: Wolf Brother Author: Michelle Paver Review: Wolf Brother is a captivating and thrilling children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes readers on an unforgettable journey through a world filled with magic, adventure, and the power of friendship. Written by Michelle Paver, this book is the first in the Chronicles of Ancient Darkness series and is perfect for children aged 8 to 12 years old. The story follows the life of a young boy named Torak, who lives in a prehistoric world filled with nature and ancient beliefs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Mole Always Turns Up on Its Own</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/a_mole_always_turns_up_on_its_own_by_hanna_johansen_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/a_mole_always_turns_up_on_its_own_by_hanna_johansen_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>A Mole Always Turns Up on Its Own by Hanna Johansen Title: A Mole Always Turns Up on Its Own Author: Hanna Johansen Review: &amp;ldquo;A Mole Always Turns Up on Its Own&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Hanna Johansen, which is perfect for children aged 4-8 years old. The story follows the journey of a mole who gets separated from its family and must find its way back home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Series of Unfortunate Events #1: The Bad Beginning: The Short-Lived</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/a_series_of_unfortunate_events_#1_the_bad_beginning_the_short-lived_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/a_series_of_unfortunate_events_#1_the_bad_beginning_the_short-lived_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>A Series of Unfortunate Events #1: The Bad Beginning: The Short-Lived Title: A Series of Unfortunate Events #1: The Bad Beginning: The Short-Lived Author: Lemony Snicket Review: A Series of Unfortunate Events #1: The Bad Beginning: The Short-Lived is a captivating and engaging children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the story of the Baudelaire siblings, Violet, Klaus, and Sunny, as they navigate through the unfortunate events that befall them after the tragic death of their parents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Thief in the Village</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/a_thief_in_the_village_by_james_berry_isbn_9780582344075/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/a_thief_in_the_village_by_james_berry_isbn_9780582344075/</guid>
      <description>A Thief in the Village by James Berry Title: A Thief in the Village Author: James Berry Review: A Thief in the Village is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by James Berry, which tells the story of a small village that faces the challenge of a thief among them. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 8 to 12 years old. The story follows the journey of the villagers as they try to uncover the identity of the thief, while also learning valuable life lessons along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/harry_potter_and_the_prisoner_of_azkaban_isbn_9780320037795/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/harry_potter_and_the_prisoner_of_azkaban_isbn_9780320037795/</guid>
      <description>Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban Title: Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban Author: J.K. Rowling Review: Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban is the third installment in the widely popular Harry Potter series by J.K. Rowling. This book is an enchanting tale that follows the adventures of Harry Potter, a young wizard, as he navigates the challenges of his third year at Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hayflower and Quiltshoe</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/hayflower_and_quiltshoe_by_sinikka_and_tiina_nopola_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/hayflower_and_quiltshoe_by_sinikka_and_tiina_nopola_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Hayflower and Quiltshoe by Sinikka and Tiina Nopola Title: Hayflower and Quiltshoe Author: Sinikka and Tiina Nopola Review: Hayflower and Quiltshoe is a charming and delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of two sisters, Hayflower and Quiltshoe, who embark on a magical adventure. The story is filled with vivid illustrations that capture the imagination of young readers and bring the characters to life. The book is suitable for children aged 4 to 8 years old, as it contains simple language and engaging storytelling that captivates the young audience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Am Susannah</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/i_am_susannah_by_libby_gleeson_isbn_082340742x/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/i_am_susannah_by_libby_gleeson_isbn_082340742x/</guid>
      <description>I Am Susannah by Libby Gleeson Title: I Am Susannah Author: Libby Gleeson Target Age Group: 6-10 years old Review: &amp;ldquo;I Am Susannah&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young girl named Susannah, who embarks on a journey of self-discovery and learns the importance of embracing her unique qualities. The book, written by Libby Gleeson, is an engaging and heartwarming tale that is perfect for children between the ages of 6 and 10 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manolito Quattrocchi</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/manolito_quattrocchi_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/manolito_quattrocchi_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Manolito Quattrocchi Title: Manolito Quattrocchi Author: Jorge Bucay Manolito Quattrocchi is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Jorge Bucay, which tells the story of a young boy named Manolito who embarks on a journey of self-discovery and learns valuable life lessons along the way. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old and is a perfect read for young readers who are beginning to explore the complexities of life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merryll of the Stones</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/merryll_of_the_stones_by_brian_caswell_isbn_070222250x/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/merryll_of_the_stones_by_brian_caswell_isbn_070222250x/</guid>
      <description>Merryll of the Stones by Brian Caswell Title: Merryll of the Stones Author: Brian Caswell Merryll of the Stones is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Brian Caswell that takes young readers on an exciting adventure filled with magic, mystery, and important life lessons. The book is perfect for children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old, as it is engaging, relatable, and teaches valuable lessons that can be applied to their everyday lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stories to Fernando</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/stories_to_fernando_by_ema_wolf_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/stories_to_fernando_by_ema_wolf_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Stories to Fernando by Ema Wolf Title: Stories to Fernando Author: Ema Wolf Review: Stories to Fernando is a charming collection of stories that are perfect for young readers. The book is filled with delightful tales that are sure to capture the imagination of children aged 5 to 8 years old. The stories are beautifully illustrated, making it a visual treat for the young readers. One of the key strengths of this book is the way it seamlessly incorporates important life lessons into the stories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Composition</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_composition_isbn_9781305633858/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_composition_isbn_9781305633858/</guid>
      <description>The Composition Title: The Composition Author: Antonia Banyard Genre: Children&amp;rsquo;s Picture Book Target Age Group: 4-8 years old Review: &amp;ldquo;The Composition&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s picture book that tells the story of a young boy named Sam who is tasked with creating a picture for his school&amp;rsquo;s art competition. The book takes readers on a journey as Sam struggles to find inspiration for his artwork, eventually discovering that the beauty of nature can be found in the most unexpected places.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The View From Saturday</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_view_from_saturday_isbn_068980993x/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_view_from_saturday_isbn_068980993x/</guid>
      <description>The View From Saturday Title: The View from Saturday Author: E.L. Konigsburg Recommended Age Group: 8-12 years old &amp;ldquo;The View from Saturday&amp;rdquo; is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book by E.L. Konigsburg that tells the story of four sixth-grade students - Noah, Nadia, Ethan, and Julian - who come together to form an academic team. The book is a perfect blend of humor, heart, and adventure, making it an enjoyable read for children aged 8-12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Whipping Boy</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_whipping_boy_isbn_416088120/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_whipping_boy_isbn_416088120/</guid>
      <description>The Whipping Boy Title: The Whipping Boy Author: Sid Fleischman The Whipping Boy is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young prince named Horace and his whipping boy, Jemmy. The whipping boy, Jemmy, is a commoner who receives the punishments for the prince&amp;rsquo;s misbehavior, as it was believed that it would help the prince learn from his mistakes. The book is set in a medieval kingdom and follows the adventures of Horace and Jemmy as they escape from the castle and embark on a thrilling journey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Watch Out for the Cat</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/watch_out_for_the_cat_by_silvana_gandolfi_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/watch_out_for_the_cat_by_silvana_gandolfi_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Watch Out for the Cat by Silvana Gandolfi Title: Watch Out for the Cat Author: Silvana Gandolfi Review: &amp;ldquo;Watch Out for the Cat&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Silvana Gandolfi, which takes the reader on a thrilling adventure through the eyes of a young protagonist, Martino. The story is set in a small village where the villagers are constantly plagued by a mischievous and cunning cat. Martino, a curious and brave boy, decides to take matters into his own hands and find a way to outsmart the cat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gargling With Jelly</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/gargling_with_jelly_by_brian_patten_isbn_9780573050923/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/gargling_with_jelly_by_brian_patten_isbn_9780573050923/</guid>
      <description>Gargling With Jelly by Brian Patten Title: Gargling with Jelly Author: Brian Patten &amp;ldquo;Gargling with Jelly&amp;rdquo; is a whimsical and delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book by Brian Patten, a well-known poet and author. This book is perfect for young readers aged 6-10, as it captures their imaginations with its fantastical tales and engaging illustrations. The book is a collection of short stories, each one more captivating than the last. The stories range from the amusing tale of a boy who tries to catch the wind to the touching story of a lonely man who finds friendship in a magical fish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Max and Sally</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/max_and_sally_by_milos_macourek_isbn_9788000007007/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/max_and_sally_by_milos_macourek_isbn_9788000007007/</guid>
      <description>Max and Sally by Milos Macourek Title: Max and Sally Author: Milos Macourek Max and Sally is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Milos Macourek. This book is a perfect choice for children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old. The story revolves around two young siblings, Max and Sally, who embark on an adventure together. The illustrations are vibrant and engaging, making it a visually appealing book for young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Redwall</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/redwall_isbn_9780091767297/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/redwall_isbn_9780091767297/</guid>
      <description>Redwall Title: Redwall Author: Brian Jacques Redwall is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes readers on an adventurous journey through the world of anthropomorphic animals. The story is set in the abbey of Redwall, where the kind and peaceful inhabitants live in harmony with nature. The main character, Matthias, is a young mouse who dreams of becoming a warrior like the legendary Martin the Warrior. The target age group for this book is 8-12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ronia the Robber&#39;s Daughter</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/ronia_the_robbers_daughter_isbn_812437233/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/ronia_the_robbers_daughter_isbn_812437233/</guid>
      <description>Ronia the Robber&amp;rsquo;s Daughter Title: Ronia the Robber&amp;rsquo;s Daughter Author: Astrid Lindgren Ronia the Robber&amp;rsquo;s Daughter is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the talented Astrid Lindgren. This story is a perfect blend of adventure, friendship, and fantasy, making it an enjoyable read for children aged 8-12 years old. The book follows the life of Ronia, the daughter of a robber chieftain, who lives in a castle in the forest. She is a curious and fearless girl who loves to explore the woods and spend time with her best friend, Birk, the son of a rival robber chieftain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sarah, Plain and Tall</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/sarah_plain_and_tall_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/sarah_plain_and_tall_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Sarah, Plain and Tall Title: Sarah, Plain and Tall Author: Patricia MacLachlan Review: &amp;ldquo;Sarah, Plain and Tall&amp;rdquo; is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Patricia MacLachlan. The story revolves around a widowed father, Jacob Witting, and his two children, Anna and Caleb, who live on a farm in the Midwest. Jacob places an advertisement for a mail-order bride, and Sarah, a woman from Maine, responds to the ad. The book targets children aged 6 to 10 years old and is a perfect blend of emotions, family values, and life lessons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Haunting</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_haunting_by_margaret_mahy_isbn_9780440404088/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_haunting_by_margaret_mahy_isbn_9780440404088/</guid>
      <description>The Haunting by Margaret Mahy Title: The Haunting Author: Margaret Mahy Review: The Haunting, written by Margaret Mahy, is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book that is sure to enthrall young readers with its spooky yet heartwarming story. The book is primarily targeted at children between the ages of 8 and 12, making it a perfect addition to any elementary school library or classroom. The story follows the adventures of a young girl named Barbara, who is determined to save her family&amp;rsquo;s home from being haunted by a mischievous ghost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When the Wind Blows</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/when_the_wind_blows_isbn_747292876/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/when_the_wind_blows_isbn_747292876/</guid>
      <description>When the Wind Blows Title: When the Wind Blows Author: Linda Booth Sweeney Illustrator: Jana Christy Recommended Age Group: 4-8 years old &amp;ldquo;When the Wind Blows&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that captures the essence of nature and the power of imagination. The story follows a young girl named Maya, who loves to play and explore in her backyard. One day, she notices the wind blowing, and she starts to imagine all the different things that the wind might be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why the Whales Came</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/why_the_whales_came_by_michael_morpurgo_isbn_1405255889/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/why_the_whales_came_by_michael_morpurgo_isbn_1405255889/</guid>
      <description>Why the Whales Came by Michael Morpurgo Title: Why the Whales Came Author: Michael Morpurgo Review: Why the Whales Came is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the talented author Michael Morpurgo. This book is an excellent choice for young readers, particularly those in the 8-12 age range. The story is set in a small island village during World War I and follows the adventures of two young boys, Ben and Gracie, who befriend a mysterious man called Birdman.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Charmed Life</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/charmed_life_isbn_688155464/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/charmed_life_isbn_688155464/</guid>
      <description>Charmed Life Title: Charmed Life Author: Lisa Schroeder Charmed Life is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Lisa Schroeder, which tells the story of two sisters, Caitlin and Abby, who embark on a magical adventure in a small coastal town. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 8 and 12, and is a perfect blend of fantasy, adventure, and heartwarming moments. The story revolves around Caitlin and Abby, who move to a new town with their family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goodnight Mister Tom</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/goodnight_mister_tom_isbn_9780141332253/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/goodnight_mister_tom_isbn_9780141332253/</guid>
      <description>Goodnight Mister Tom Title: Goodnight Mister Tom Author: Michelle Magorian Genre: Children&amp;rsquo;s Literature, Historical Fiction Recommended Age Group: 8-12 years old &amp;ldquo;Goodnight Mister Tom&amp;rdquo; is a heartwarming and poignant story set in the midst of World War II. The book is suitable for children aged 8-12 years old and serves as an excellent introduction to the historical context of the time period. The story follows the life of a young boy named William Beech, who is evacuated from London to the countryside to escape the dangers of the war.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Turbulent Term of Tyke Tiler</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_turbulent_term_of_tyke_tiler_isbn_198312695/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_turbulent_term_of_tyke_tiler_isbn_198312695/</guid>
      <description>The Turbulent Term of Tyke Tiler Title: The Turbulent Term of Tyke Tiler Author: Gene Kemp The Turbulent Term of Tyke Tiler is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Gene Kemp. The story follows the adventures of Tyke Tiler, a young boy who is struggling to fit in at his new school. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 8 and 12, and is an engaging read that teaches valuable life lessons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Pair of Jesus Boots</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/a_pair_of_jesus_boots_by_sylvia_sherry_isbn_224615769/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/a_pair_of_jesus_boots_by_sylvia_sherry_isbn_224615769/</guid>
      <description>A Pair of Jesus Boots by Sylvia Sherry Title: A Pair of Jesus Boots Author: Sylvia Sherry Review: A Pair of Jesus Boots is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Sylvia Sherry. The story follows a young boy named Timmy, who desperately wants a pair of Jesus Boots - boots that can walk on water just like Jesus did. The book is targeted towards children aged 4-8 years old and is a perfect blend of adventure, imagination, and heartwarming lessons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are You There God? It&#39;s Me, Margaret</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/are_you_there_god_its_me_margaret_by_new_jersey_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/are_you_there_god_its_me_margaret_by_new_jersey_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Are You There God? It&amp;rsquo;s Me, Margaret by New Jersey Title: Are You There God? It&amp;rsquo;s Me, Margaret Author: New Jersey Review: Are You There God? It&amp;rsquo;s Me, Margaret is a heartwarming and relatable story that follows the life of a young girl named Margaret as she navigates the challenges of adolescence. The book, written by New Jersey, is an excellent choice for children between the ages of 8 and 12.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bridge to Terabithia</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/bridge_to_terabithia_isbn_9786051732077/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/bridge_to_terabithia_isbn_9786051732077/</guid>
      <description>Bridge to Terabithia Title: Bridge to Terabithia Author: Katherine Paterson Review: Bridge to Terabithia is a captivating and heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s novel written by Katherine Paterson. The story follows the lives of two young protagonists, Jess Aarons and Leslie Burke, as they embark on a journey of friendship, imagination, and self-discovery. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old. The themes and life lessons presented in the story are relatable and relevant to this age group, making it an excellent choice for young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crusade in Jeans</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/crusade_in_jeans_isbn_9781935954071/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/crusade_in_jeans_isbn_9781935954071/</guid>
      <description>Crusade in Jeans Title: Crusade in Jeans Author: Thea Beckman Review: Crusade in Jeans is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young boy named Dolf, who is unexpectedly transported back in time to the Middle Ages. The book, written by Thea Beckman, is an engaging and thought-provoking adventure that is perfect for children aged 10-14. The story is filled with historical details, and it provides an exciting and immersive way for young readers to learn about the past.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Sweet-Orange Tree</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/my_sweet-orange_tree_by_jose_mauro_de_vasconcelos_isbn_9780718108779/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/my_sweet-orange_tree_by_jose_mauro_de_vasconcelos_isbn_9780718108779/</guid>
      <description>My Sweet-Orange Tree by Jose Mauro De Vasconcelos Title: My Sweet-Orange Tree Author: Jose Mauro De Vasconcelos &amp;ldquo;My Sweet-Orange Tree&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Jose Mauro De Vasconcelos, which takes readers on a heartwarming journey through the life of a young boy named Zezé. The story is set in a small Brazilian town and beautifully portrays the innocence and joy of childhood, as well as the importance of friendship, love, and imagination.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Carpet People</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_carpet_people_isbn_9780754050674/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_carpet_people_isbn_9780754050674/</guid>
      <description>The Carpet People Title: The Carpet People Author: Terry Pratchett Review: The Carpet People is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Terry Pratchett, which takes readers on a fantastical journey through the world of tiny people living in the carpet. The story follows the adventures of the Carpet People as they face various challenges and learn important life lessons. The book is suitable for children between the ages of 7 and 12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Cucumber King</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_cucumber_king_by_christine_nostlinger_isbn_093026701x/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_cucumber_king_by_christine_nostlinger_isbn_093026701x/</guid>
      <description>The Cucumber King by Christine Nostlinger Title: The Cucumber King Author: Christine Nostlinger Review: The Cucumber King is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Christine Nostlinger. This charming story follows the adventures of a young boy named Peter, who lives in a small village and has a unique talent for growing cucumbers. The story takes the reader on a journey through Peter&amp;rsquo;s life, as he learns valuable life lessons about perseverance, friendship, and the importance of embracing one&amp;rsquo;s unique abilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Shrinking of Treehorn</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_shrinking_of_treehorn_by_florence_parry_heide_isbn_9780823401895/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_shrinking_of_treehorn_by_florence_parry_heide_isbn_9780823401895/</guid>
      <description>The Shrinking of Treehorn by Florence Parry Heide Title: The Shrinking of Treehorn Author: Florence Parry Heide The Shrinking of Treehorn is a whimsical and thought-provoking children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Florence Parry Heide. The story follows the adventures of Treehorn, a young boy who starts shrinking inexplicably. As he gets smaller and smaller, Treehorn&amp;rsquo;s family and friends fail to notice his predicament, leading to a series of humorous and sometimes perilous situations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chitty Chitty Bang Bang</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/chitty_chitty_bang_bang_isbn_394819489/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/chitty_chitty_bang_bang_isbn_394819489/</guid>
      <description>Chitty Chitty Bang Bang Title: Chitty Chitty Bang Bang Author: Ian Fleming Review: Chitty Chitty Bang Bang is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Ian Fleming, the creator of the famous James Bond series. The story revolves around the adventures of the Pott family, who stumble upon an old, magical car with the ability to fly and float on water. As the family embarks on various thrilling escapades, they encounter a series of challenges and obstacles that they must overcome together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From the Mixed-Up Files of Mrs. Basil E. Frankweiler</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/from_the_mixed-up_files_of_mrs._basil_e._frankweiler_isbn_9781557360922/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/from_the_mixed-up_files_of_mrs._basil_e._frankweiler_isbn_9781557360922/</guid>
      <description>From the Mixed-Up Files of Mrs. Basil E. Frankweiler Title: From the Mixed-Up Files of Mrs. Basil E. Frankweiler Author: E.L. Konigsburg Review: From the Mixed-Up Files of Mrs. Basil E. Frankweiler is a delightful and engaging children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes young readers on a thrilling adventure. The story follows the lives of two siblings, Claudia and Jamie, who decide to run away from home and end up living in the Metropolitan Museum of Art in New York City.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gaston</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/gaston_isbn_9782800126074/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/gaston_isbn_9782800126074/</guid>
      <description>Gaston Title: Gaston Author: Kelly DiPucchio Illustrator: Christian Robinson Recommended Age Group: 4-8 years old Gaston is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a charming little bulldog who finds himself in a family of poodles. The book is beautifully illustrated by Christian Robinson, and the story is written by Kelly DiPucchio, who is known for her engaging and heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s books. The story follows Gaston, a little bulldog who is raised by a family of poodles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mort and Phil</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/mort_and_phil_by_francisco_ibanez_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/mort_and_phil_by_francisco_ibanez_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Mort and Phil by Francisco Ibanez Title: Mort and Phil Author: Francisco Ibanez Review: Mort and Phil is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of two young friends, Mort and Phil, who embark on a series of adventures together. The book is filled with colorful illustrations and engaging dialogue that will captivate young readers. Target Age Group: Mort and Phil is perfect for children between the ages of 6 and 10.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Six Companions</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/six_companions_by_paul-jacques_bonzon_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/six_companions_by_paul-jacques_bonzon_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Six Companions by Paul-Jacques Bonzon Title: Six Companions Author: Paul-Jacques Bonzon Review: Six Companions by Paul-Jacques Bonzon is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes young readers on an exciting adventure filled with friendship, teamwork, and self-discovery. The story follows six unique characters, each with their own distinct personality and background, as they embark on a journey to find a missing treasure. Target Age Group: The book is suitable for children between the ages of 8 and 12.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Hundred and One Dalmatians</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_hundred_and_one_dalmatians_isbn_9780760704066/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_hundred_and_one_dalmatians_isbn_9780760704066/</guid>
      <description>The Hundred and One Dalmatians Title: The Hundred and One Dalmatians Author: Dodie Smith Review: The Hundred and One Dalmatians is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Dodie Smith, first published in 1956. The story revolves around the lives of 101 Dalmatian puppies, their parents Pongo and Missis, and their human family, the Dearlys. The book is filled with adventure, suspense, and heartwarming moments that make it a delightful read for children of all ages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_lion_the_witch_and_the_wardrobe_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_lion_the_witch_and_the_wardrobe_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe Title: The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe Author: C.S. Lewis The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by C.S. Lewis, which takes the reader on a magical journey through the enchanted land of Narnia. The story is set during World War II and follows the adventures of four siblings, Peter, Susan, Edmund, and Lucy, who stumble upon a magical wardrobe that leads them to Narnia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Betsy-Tacy Books</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/betsy-tacy_books_isbn_9780064401272/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/betsy-tacy_books_isbn_9780064401272/</guid>
      <description>Betsy-Tacy Books Title: Betsy-Tacy Books Review: The Betsy-Tacy Books, written by Maud Hart Lovelace, is a delightful series that captures the essence of childhood friendships, imagination, and the innocence of a bygone era. This heartwarming collection of stories is perfect for young readers between the ages of 7 and 12, and it is an ideal choice for parents and teachers looking to instill important life lessons in their children. Set in the early 20th century, the Betsy-Tacy Books follow the adventures of two best friends, Betsy and Tacy, as they grow up together in the charming town of Deep Valley.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lassie Come Home</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/lassie_come_home_isbn_9781627792943/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/lassie_come_home_isbn_9781627792943/</guid>
      <description>Lassie Come Home Title: Lassie Come Home Author: Eric Knight Illustrator: Marguerite Kirmse Publisher: Little, Brown Books for Young Readers (1940) Lassie Come Home is a heartwarming tale about the bond between a boy named Joe and his beloved collie, Lassie. Set in the Yorkshire Dales, the story follows Lassie&amp;rsquo;s incredible journey to reunite with Joe after being sold to a wealthy duke. The book is suitable for children aged 8-12, as it is a relatively short novel with simple language and engaging illustrations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Night on the Galactic Railroad</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/night_on_the_galactic_railroad_by_kenji_miyazawa_isbn_9781935548997/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/night_on_the_galactic_railroad_by_kenji_miyazawa_isbn_9781935548997/</guid>
      <description>Night on the Galactic Railroad by Kenji Miyazawa Title: Night on the Galactic Railroad Author: Kenji Miyazawa Review: Night on the Galactic Railroad is a beautifully written children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes readers on a magical journey through the cosmos. Author Kenji Miyazawa has crafted a captivating story that is perfect for young readers between the ages of 8 and 12. The book follows the adventures of two young boys, Giovanni and Campanella, as they embark on a fantastical train ride through the stars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Platero and I</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/platero_and_i_isbn_9780292733282/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/platero_and_i_isbn_9780292733282/</guid>
      <description>Platero and I Title: Platero and I Author: Juan Ramón Jiménez Recommended Age Group: 8-12 years old Platero and I is a beautifully written and illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book that captures the essence of a young boy&amp;rsquo;s adventures with his loyal donkey, Platero, in a small Andalusian village. The book is filled with heartwarming stories that touch upon various life lessons, making it an excellent choice for children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Far-Distant Oxus</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_far-distant_oxus_by_k_hull_and_p_whitlock_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_far-distant_oxus_by_k_hull_and_p_whitlock_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Far-Distant Oxus by K Hull and P Whitlock Title: The Far-Distant Oxus Author: K. Hull and P. Whitlock Review: The Far-Distant Oxus is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes young readers on an exciting adventure filled with unexpected twists and turns. Written by K. Hull and P. Whitlock, this book is a perfect blend of fantasy and reality, making it an enjoyable read for children aged 8 to 12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Red U: A Story for Lads</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_red_u_a_story_for_lads_by_wilhelm_matthiessen_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_red_u_a_story_for_lads_by_wilhelm_matthiessen_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Red U: A Story for Lads by Wilhelm Matthiessen Title: The Red U: A Story for Lads Author: Wilhelm Matthiessen The Red U: A Story for Lads is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Wilhelm Matthiessen. The book is a perfect blend of adventure, friendship, and self-discovery, making it an ideal read for children between the ages of 8 and 12. The story revolves around a group of young lads who embark on a thrilling journey to find a hidden treasure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Secret of the Old Clock</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_secret_of_the_old_clock_isbn_9780765117281/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_secret_of_the_old_clock_isbn_9780765117281/</guid>
      <description>The Secret of the Old Clock Title: The Secret of the Old Clock Author: Carolyn Keene Recommended Age Group: 8-12 years old The Secret of the Old Clock is a delightful and engaging children&amp;rsquo;s mystery novel that follows the adventures of the young and curious Nancy Drew. This book is perfect for young readers between the ages of 8 and 12 years old who enjoy mysteries and adventure stories. The story revolves around Nancy Drew, an intelligent and resourceful teenage girl, who stumbles upon a mystery while helping her father with a case.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Celia Says</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/what_celia_says_by_elena_fortun_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/what_celia_says_by_elena_fortun_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>What Celia Says by Elena Fortun Title: What Celia Says Author: Elena Fortun &amp;ldquo;What Celia Says&amp;rdquo; is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Elena Fortun, which tells the story of a young girl named Celia who has a unique way of looking at the world. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 5 to 10 years old, and it is an excellent choice for parents and teachers looking for a book that teaches valuable life lessons in a fun and engaging manner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arsene Lupin Gentleman Thief</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/arsene_lupin_gentleman_thief_isbn_1538707462/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/arsene_lupin_gentleman_thief_isbn_1538707462/</guid>
      <description>Arsene Lupin Gentleman Thief Title: Arsene Lupin, Gentleman Thief Author: Maurice Leblanc Genre: Children&amp;rsquo;s Adventure Target Age Group: 8-12 years old &amp;ldquo;Arsene Lupin, Gentleman Thief&amp;rdquo; is a thrilling adventure story that follows the cunning exploits of the master thief, Arsene Lupin. Written by Maurice Leblanc, this book is a delightful read for children between the ages of 8 and 12. The story is filled with mystery, suspense, and humor, making it an engaging read for young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moonfleet</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/moonfleet_isbn_9798655516502/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/moonfleet_isbn_9798655516502/</guid>
      <description>Moonfleet Title: Moonfleet Author: J. Meade Falkner Genre: Adventure, Historical Fiction Target Age Group: 9-12 years old Review: Moonfleet is a thrilling adventure novel set in the 18th century, following the story of a young orphan boy named John Trenchard. The book takes the reader on a journey through the mysterious world of smugglers and treasure hunters, as John uncovers the secrets of the small village of Moonfleet. The story is filled with exciting twists and turns, making it a captivating read for children aged 9-12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess and the Goblin / Princess and Curdie</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/princess_and_the_goblin__princess_and_curdie_isbn_984698655/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/princess_and_the_goblin__princess_and_curdie_isbn_984698655/</guid>
      <description>Princess and the Goblin / Princess and Curdie Title: The Princess and the Goblin / Princess and Curdie Author: George MacDonald Recommended Age Group: 8-12 years old The Princess and the Goblin / Princess and Curdie is a classic children&amp;rsquo;s book written by George MacDonald, originally published in 1872. This timeless story is a perfect read for children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old, as it contains captivating themes and valuable life lessons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Black Corsair</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_black_corsair_by_emilio_salgari_isbn_6077200069/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_black_corsair_by_emilio_salgari_isbn_6077200069/</guid>
      <description>The Black Corsair by Emilio Salgari Title: The Black Corsair Author: Emilio Salgari Review: The Black Corsair, written by Emilio Salgari, is a thrilling adventure story that is perfect for elementary school-aged children. The book is filled with action, excitement, and valuable life lessons that will captivate young readers. The story follows the adventures of Emilio, a young boy who is captured by pirates and forced to join their crew. As Emilio becomes part of the pirate world, he learns about courage, friendship, and the importance of standing up for what is right.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Bobbsey Twins at the Seashore</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_bobbsey_twins_at_the_seashore_by_laura_lee_hope_isbn_1421812703/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_bobbsey_twins_at_the_seashore_by_laura_lee_hope_isbn_1421812703/</guid>
      <description>The Bobbsey Twins at the Seashore by Laura Lee Hope Title: The Bobbsey Twins at the Seashore Author: Laura Lee Hope Review: The Bobbsey Twins at the Seashore is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Laura Lee Hope, which takes young readers on an exciting adventure with the Bobbsey Twins. This book is part of a series that follows the adventures of the Bobbsey Twins, Bert and Nan, and their younger siblings, Flossie and Freddie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Through the Looking Glass</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/through_the_looking_glass_isbn_9626344202/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/through_the_looking_glass_isbn_9626344202/</guid>
      <description>Through the Looking Glass Title: Through the Looking Glass Author: Lewis Carroll Review: Through the Looking Glass is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Lewis Carroll, originally published in 1871. This novel is a sequel to the well-known Alice&amp;rsquo;s Adventures in Wonderland, and it continues the story of Alice, who finds herself in a magical world on the other side of a mirror. The book is targeted at children between the ages of 8 and 12, as it contains elements of fantasy, adventure, and humor that will captivate young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tom Sawyer</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/tom_sawyer_isbn_9798417467929/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/tom_sawyer_isbn_9798417467929/</guid>
      <description>Tom Sawyer Title: The Adventures of Tom Sawyer Author: Mark Twain Review: The Adventures of Tom Sawyer is a timeless classic written by Mark Twain, which takes the reader on a thrilling journey through the eyes of a young boy named Tom Sawyer. The story is set in the small town of St. Petersburg, Missouri, and follows Tom&amp;rsquo;s adventures with his friends, particularly Huckleberry Finn. The book is suitable for children between the ages of 8 and 12, as it contains elements of fun, mischief, and learning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Treasure Island</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/treasure_island_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/treasure_island_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Treasure Island Title: Treasure Island Author: Robert Louis Stevenson Genre: Adventure/Children&amp;rsquo;s Literature Recommended Age Group: 8-12 years old Treasure Island is a classic adventure story written by Robert Louis Stevenson, first published in 1883. The book follows the thrilling journey of young Jim Hawkins as he sets sail on a pirate ship in search of buried treasure. Along the way, Jim encounters a variety of colorful characters, including the infamous Long John Silver, and learns valuable life lessons about trust, friendship, and the importance of staying true to oneself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aesop&#39;s Fables</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/aesops_fables_by_aesop_isbn_787115851/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/aesops_fables_by_aesop_isbn_787115851/</guid>
      <description>Aesop&amp;rsquo;s Fables by Aesop Title: Aesop&amp;rsquo;s Fables Author: Aesop Aesop&amp;rsquo;s Fables is a timeless collection of stories that has been passed down through generations, teaching valuable life lessons to children and adults alike. The book is a compilation of tales that are credited to the ancient Greek storyteller, Aesop. Target Age Group: Aesop&amp;rsquo;s Fables is suitable for children between the ages of 6 and 12 years old. However, the stories can be enjoyed by readers of all ages, as they contain universal truths and morals that are applicable to everyone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flotsam</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/flotsam_isbn_9780548284308/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/flotsam_isbn_9780548284308/</guid>
      <description>Flotsam Title: Flotsam Author: David Wiesner Flotsam is a visually stunning and imaginative children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young boy who discovers an underwater world through a mysterious camera washed up on the beach. Author and illustrator David Wiesner uses a combination of captivating illustrations and minimal text to create a captivating and immersive experience for young readers. Targeted towards children aged 4-8, Flotsam is a wonderful book that not only encourages a love for reading but also sparks curiosity and imagination.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Llama Llama Red Pajama</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/llama_llama_red_pajama_isbn_606400931/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/llama_llama_red_pajama_isbn_606400931/</guid>
      <description>Llama Llama Red Pajama Title: Llama Llama Red Pajama Author: Anna Dewdney Review: Llama Llama Red Pajama is a charming and delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Anna Dewdney. The story follows a young llama named Baby Llama who becomes anxious and worried when his mother, Mama Llama, goes out for the evening. As Baby Llama struggles with separation anxiety, he learns valuable lessons about patience, trust, and the importance of a loving and supportive family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Morality Tales</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/morality_tales_by_rafael_pombo_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/morality_tales_by_rafael_pombo_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Morality Tales by Rafael Pombo Title: Morality Tales Author: Rafael Pombo Review: Morality Tales by Rafael Pombo is a delightful collection of short stories that teach valuable life lessons to young readers. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 6 and 12 years old, making it an excellent choice for elementary school students. The stories in Morality Tales are engaging and thought-provoking, covering a wide range of topics such as honesty, kindness, and perseverance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Nutcracker and Other Tales</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_nutcracker_and_other_tales_by_eta_hoffman_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_nutcracker_and_other_tales_by_eta_hoffman_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Nutcracker and Other Tales by ETA Hoffman Title: The Nutcracker and Other Tales Author: ETA Hoffman Review: The Nutcracker and Other Tales is a delightful collection of stories that is perfect for children between the ages of 8 and 12. The book is filled with enchanting tales that are sure to captivate young readers and spark their imagination. The first story, &amp;ldquo;The Nutcracker,&amp;rdquo; is a classic tale that has been adapted into a popular ballet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Water-Babies</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_water-babies_isbn_9798485198176/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_water-babies_isbn_9798485198176/</guid>
      <description>The Water-Babies Title: The Water-Babies Author: Charles Kingsley Genre: Children&amp;rsquo;s Fantasy/Adventure Age Group: 8-12 years old &amp;ldquo;The Water-Babies&amp;rdquo; is a delightful and imaginative children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes readers on an enchanting journey through the world of water-babies. Written by Charles Kingsley, this book was first published in 1863 and has since become a classic in children&amp;rsquo;s literature. The story revolves around Tom, a young chimney sweeper, who is transformed into a water-baby after his death.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Kingdom for a Horse</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/my_kingdom_for_a_horse_by_ana_m_machado_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/my_kingdom_for_a_horse_by_ana_m_machado_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>My Kingdom for a Horse by Ana M Machado Title: My Kingdom for a Horse Author: Ana M Machado Review: My Kingdom for a Horse is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Ana M Machado. The story revolves around a young boy named Tim who dreams of owning a horse. Tim&amp;rsquo;s determination and perseverance to achieve his goal teaches valuable life lessons to young readers. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 6 to 10 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Biggest Kiss in the World</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_biggest_kiss_in_the_world_by_r_chavez_castaneda_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_biggest_kiss_in_the_world_by_r_chavez_castaneda_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Biggest Kiss in the World by R Chavez Castaneda Title: The Biggest Kiss in the World Author: R. Chavez Castaneda Review: The Biggest Kiss in the World is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes young readers on a heartwarming journey through the world of animals. The story follows a mother elephant who, upon hearing about the biggest kiss in the world, sets out on a quest to find it. Along the way, she encounters various animals, each with their own unique interpretation of what the biggest kiss could be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lon Po Po</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/lon_po_po_isbn_9780399216190/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/lon_po_po_isbn_9780399216190/</guid>
      <description>Lon Po Po Title: Lon Po Po: A Red-Riding Hood Story from China Author: Ed Young Lon Po Po is a beautifully illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young girl named Little Red Riding Hood, but with a Chinese twist. The story is set in a Chinese village, and the characters and setting are infused with traditional Chinese elements, making it a unique and culturally rich experience for young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stellaluna</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/stellaluna_by_janell_cannon_isbn_1859028667/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/stellaluna_by_janell_cannon_isbn_1859028667/</guid>
      <description>Stellaluna by Janell Cannon Title: Stellaluna Author: Janell Cannon Review: Stellaluna is a beautifully illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Janell Cannon. The story follows a young fruit bat named Stellaluna who becomes separated from her mother and is adopted by a family of birds. As Stellaluna grows up, she learns about the differences between bats and birds, ultimately discovering her true identity and reuniting with her mother. The book is targeted towards children aged 4 to 8 years old, as it teaches valuable life lessons in a simple and engaging manner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tar Beach</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/tar_beach_isbn_590463810/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/tar_beach_isbn_590463810/</guid>
      <description>Tar Beach Title: Tar Beach Author: Faith Ringgold Target Age Group: 5-10 years old Tar Beach is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Faith Ringgold, which takes readers on a magical journey through the eyes of a young girl named Cassie. The story is set in the 1930s and is based on the author&amp;rsquo;s own experiences growing up in Harlem. The book is beautifully illustrated with Faith Ringgold&amp;rsquo;s quilt-like artwork, which adds to the charm and uniqueness of the story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John Brown, Rose and the Midnight Cat</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/john_brown_rose_and_the_midnight_cat_by_jenny_wagner_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/john_brown_rose_and_the_midnight_cat_by_jenny_wagner_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>John Brown, Rose and the Midnight Cat by Jenny Wagner Title: John Brown, Rose and the Midnight Cat Author: Jenny Wagner Review: &amp;ldquo;John Brown, Rose and the Midnight Cat&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Jenny Wagner. The story follows the adventures of John Brown, a young boy who lives with his family in a small cottage, and his friend Rose, a curious and imaginative girl. The two friends come across a mysterious midnight cat, which leads them on an exciting journey through the woods.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mr Fox</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/mr_fox_by_gavin_bishop_isbn_9780330292450/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/mr_fox_by_gavin_bishop_isbn_9780330292450/</guid>
      <description>Mr Fox by Gavin Bishop Title: Mr. Fox Author: Gavin Bishop Mr. Fox is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written and illustrated by Gavin Bishop. The story follows a fox who, after being chased by a group of farmers, finds himself in a magical world where he can talk to animals and learn their languages. Through his adventures, Mr. Fox learns valuable life lessons and makes new friends along the way. Target Age Group: Mr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Cat That Lived a Million Times</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_cat_that_lived_a_million_times_by_yoko_sano_isbn_9780824820985/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_cat_that_lived_a_million_times_by_yoko_sano_isbn_9780824820985/</guid>
      <description>The Cat That Lived a Million Times by Yoko Sano Title: The Cat That Lived a Million Times Author: Yoko Sano Review: The Cat That Lived a Million Times is a heartwarming and enchanting children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a cat with an extraordinary ability to reincarnate and live multiple lives. The book is a perfect read for children aged 6-10 years old, as it features beautiful illustrations and a captivating narrative that will keep young readers engaged.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Hound of Mound and the Frog of the Bog</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_hound_of_mound_and_the_frog_of_the_bog_by_ana_maria_machado_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_hound_of_mound_and_the_frog_of_the_bog_by_ana_maria_machado_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Hound of Mound and the Frog of the Bog by Ana Maria Machado Title: The Hound of Mound and the Frog of the Bog Author: Ana Maria Machado The Hound of Mound and the Frog of the Bog is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young hound named Mound and a curious frog named Bog. The book is written by Ana Maria Machado, who has a knack for creating engaging stories that captivate young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Polar Express</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_polar_express_isbn_9781783446827/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_polar_express_isbn_9781783446827/</guid>
      <description>The Polar Express Title: The Polar Express Author: Chris Van Allsburg Review: The Polar Express is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Chris Van Allsburg, which tells the story of a young boy who embarks on a magical journey to the North Pole on Christmas Eve. The story is beautifully illustrated with captivating images that bring the enchanting world of the Polar Express to life. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Real Thief</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_real_thief_by_william_steig_isbn_1782691456/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_real_thief_by_william_steig_isbn_1782691456/</guid>
      <description>The Real Thief by William Steig Title: The Real Thief Author: William Steig Target Age Group: 5-10 years old The Real Thief is a beautifully illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book by William Steig, which tells the story of a young mouse named Pearl who is accused of stealing a cherished diamond ring. The book explores themes of friendship, trust, and honesty, making it a perfect read for children between the ages of 5 and 10 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Lion in the Meadow</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/a_lion_in_the_meadow_by_margaret_mahy_isbn_9780460061742/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/a_lion_in_the_meadow_by_margaret_mahy_isbn_9780460061742/</guid>
      <description>A Lion in the Meadow by Margaret Mahy Title: A Lion in the Meadow Author: Margaret Mahy Review: A Lion in the Meadow is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Margaret Mahy, which tells the story of a young boy named Timothy who has a vivid imagination. The book is perfect for children aged 4 to 8 years old, as it teaches valuable life lessons through a captivating and engaging narrative.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Captain Pugwash</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/captain_pugwash_by_john_ryan_isbn_859680169/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/captain_pugwash_by_john_ryan_isbn_859680169/</guid>
      <description>Captain Pugwash by John Ryan Title: Captain Pugwash Author: John Ryan Review: Captain Pugwash is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes readers on a thrilling adventure with its lovable characters and engaging storyline. The book, written by John Ryan, is an ideal read for children between the ages of 5 and 10 years old. The story revolves around the charming Captain Pugwash, a pirate captain, and his trusty crew as they embark on a treasure hunt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chanticleer and the Fox</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/chanticleer_and_the_fox_isbn_690185618/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/chanticleer_and_the_fox_isbn_690185618/</guid>
      <description>Chanticleer and the Fox Title: Chanticleer and the Fox Author: Barbara Cooney Age Group: 4-8 years old &amp;ldquo;Chanticleer and the Fox&amp;rdquo; is a beautifully illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a proud rooster named Chanticleer. The book is based on the classic tale from &amp;ldquo;The Canterbury Tales&amp;rdquo; by Geoffrey Chaucer. The story follows Chanticleer, who lives in a farmyard with other animals. He is known for his beautiful singing voice, which he believes makes him the most important animal on the farm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ramona the Pest</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/ramona_the_pest_isbn_62253123/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/ramona_the_pest_isbn_62253123/</guid>
      <description>Ramona the Pest Title: Ramona the Pest Author: Beverly Cleary Review: Ramona the Pest is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Beverly Cleary, which tells the story of a young girl named Ramona Quimby, who is eager to start kindergarten and make new friends. The book is an engaging and heartwarming read that will captivate the hearts of young readers. Target Age Group: Ramona the Pest is best suited for children between the ages of 6 and 10 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Swimmy</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/swimmy_isbn_2211024882/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/swimmy_isbn_2211024882/</guid>
      <description>Swimmy Title: Swimmy Author: Leo Lionni Swimmy is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Leo Lionni, which tells the story of a small black fish named Swimmy who sets out on a journey to find a new home for himself and his friends. The book is beautifully illustrated with colorful and vibrant images that capture the essence of the story. The target age group for this book is 4 to 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Bears on Hemlock Mountain</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_bears_on_hemlock_mountain_by_alice_dalgliesh_isbn_9780684191690/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_bears_on_hemlock_mountain_by_alice_dalgliesh_isbn_9780684191690/</guid>
      <description>The Bears on Hemlock Mountain by Alice Dalgliesh Title: The Bears on Hemlock Mountain Author: Alice Dalgliesh Illustrator: Helen Sewell The Bears on Hemlock Mountain is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Alice Dalgliesh and illustrated by Helen Sewell. This story, first published in 1952, has been a favorite of many young readers for generations. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old. The story follows Jonathan, a young boy who lives near Hemlock Mountain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Biggest Bear</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_biggest_bear_isbn_9780440842026/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_biggest_bear_isbn_9780440842026/</guid>
      <description>The Biggest Bear Title: The Biggest Bear Author: Lynd Ward Review: The Biggest Bear is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young boy named Johnny who encounters a massive, friendly bear in the woods. The story is set in a small village surrounded by beautiful forests, where Johnny and his family live. The illustrations in this book are simply breathtaking, as they were created by the talented Lynd Ward, who uses intricate wood engravings to bring the story to life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Dreams of the Toad</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_dreams_of_the_toad_by_javier_villafane_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_dreams_of_the_toad_by_javier_villafane_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Dreams of the Toad by Javier Villafane Title: The Dreams of the Toad Author: Javier Villafane Review: The Dreams of the Toad is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Javier Villafane that tells the story of a toad named Tito who dreams of doing something extraordinary. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 4 to 8 years old and is filled with beautiful illustrations that will captivate the young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elsie Piddock Skips in Her Sleep</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/elsie_piddock_skips_in_her_sleep_by_eleanor_farjeon_isbn_9780763601331/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/elsie_piddock_skips_in_her_sleep_by_eleanor_farjeon_isbn_9780763601331/</guid>
      <description>Elsie Piddock Skips in Her Sleep by Eleanor Farjeon Title: Elsie Piddock Skips in Her Sleep Author: Eleanor Farjeon Review: Elsie Piddock Skips in Her Sleep is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Eleanor Farjeon. The story follows Elsie Piddock, a young girl with an extraordinary talent for skipping. She lives in a small village where everyone knows her as the best skipper around. One day, a mischievous fairy named Willy Skilly comes to town and challenges Elsie to a skipping contest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Morning in Maine</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/one_morning_in_maine_isbn_9780808536338/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/one_morning_in_maine_isbn_9780808536338/</guid>
      <description>One Morning in Maine Title: One Morning in Maine Author: Robert McCloskey One Morning in Maine is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written and illustrated by Robert McCloskey. The story follows the adventures of a young girl named Sal and her little sister, Jane, as they spend a day exploring the coast of Maine with their mother. The book is filled with beautiful illustrations that capture the essence of the Maine coastline and the charm of a small fishing village.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Adventures of Maya the Bee</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_adventures_of_maya_the_bee_by_waldemar_bonsels_isbn_1627937587/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_adventures_of_maya_the_bee_by_waldemar_bonsels_isbn_1627937587/</guid>
      <description>The Adventures of Maya the Bee by Waldemar Bonsels Title: The Adventures of Maya the Bee Author: Waldemar Bonsels Review: The Adventures of Maya the Bee, written by Waldemar Bonsels, is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the journey of Maya, a young bee who embarks on an adventure to explore the world outside her hive. The story is filled with colorful characters, exciting adventures, and valuable life lessons that make it an enjoyable read for children aged 6 to 10 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Doll&#39;s House</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_dolls_house_by_rumer_godden_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_dolls_house_by_rumer_godden_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Doll&amp;rsquo;s House by Rumer Godden Title: The Doll&amp;rsquo;s House Author: Rumer Godden The Doll&amp;rsquo;s House, written by Rumer Godden, is a charming and enchanting children&amp;rsquo;s book that captures the essence of childhood imagination and the importance of friendship. The story revolves around two young sisters, Tottie and Emily, who receive a beautiful dollhouse as a gift. The dollhouse becomes a magical world where the dolls come to life and experience their own adventures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Squirrel, the Hare, and the Little Grey Rabbit</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_squirrel_the_hare_and_the_little_grey_rabbit_by_alison_uttley/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_squirrel_the_hare_and_the_little_grey_rabbit_by_alison_uttley/</guid>
      <description>The Squirrel, the Hare, and the Little Grey Rabbit by Alison Uttley Title: The Squirrel, the Hare, and the Little Grey Rabbit Author: Alison Uttley Illustrator: Margaret Tempest Recommended Age Group: 4-8 years old The Squirrel, the Hare, and the Little Grey Rabbit is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Alison Uttley, which has been beautifully illustrated by Margaret Tempest. The story revolves around three friends, a squirrel, a hare, and a little grey rabbit, who live in a forest and enjoy their adventures together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tweet Tweet</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/tweet_tweet_by_ludmila_podjavorinska_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/tweet_tweet_by_ludmila_podjavorinska_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Tweet Tweet by Ludmila Podjavorinska Title: Tweet Tweet Author: Ludmila Podjavorinska Review: Tweet Tweet is a charming and engaging children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Ludmila Podjavorinska. The story follows the adventures of a young bird named Tweet who embarks on a journey to find a new home. Along the way, Tweet encounters various challenges and meets new friends who help her on her quest. The book is beautifully illustrated, with vibrant colors and detailed drawings that capture the reader&amp;rsquo;s attention.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Visit From St. Nicholas</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/a_visit_from_st._nicholas_by_the_night_before_christmas_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/a_visit_from_st._nicholas_by_the_night_before_christmas_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>A Visit From St. Nicholas by The Night Before Christmas Title: A Visit from St. Nicholas (The Night Before Christmas) Author: Clement C. Moore Illustrator: Jessie Willcox Smith A Visit from St. Nicholas, also known as The Night Before Christmas, is a timeless classic that has been cherished by children and adults alike for generations. Written by Clement C. Moore and beautifully illustrated by Jessie Willcox Smith, this book brings to life the enchanting story of a visit from the jolly old elf, Santa Claus, on Christmas Eve.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Madlenka</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/madlenka_by_peter_sis_isbn_9780439233132/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/madlenka_by_peter_sis_isbn_9780439233132/</guid>
      <description>Madlenka by Peter Sis Title: Madlenka Author: Peter Sis Madlenka is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the adventures of a young girl named Madlenka, who lives in a charming city apartment building. The story takes the reader on a journey through Madlenka&amp;rsquo;s day, as she interacts with her neighbors and friends, each with their own unique story to tell. The book is beautifully illustrated by the author, Peter Sis, who uses vibrant colors and intricate details to bring the city and its inhabitants to life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marc Just Couldn&#39;t Sleep</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/marc_just_couldnt_sleep_by_gabriela_keselman_isbn_9781929132911/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/marc_just_couldnt_sleep_by_gabriela_keselman_isbn_9781929132911/</guid>
      <description>Marc Just Couldn&amp;rsquo;t Sleep by Gabriela Keselman Title: Marc Just Couldn&amp;rsquo;t Sleep Author: Gabriela Keselman Review: Marc Just Couldn&amp;rsquo;t Sleep is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young boy named Marc who struggles to fall asleep at night. Through vivid illustrations and engaging storytelling, author Gabriela Keselman takes readers on a journey with Marc as he tries various methods to overcome his sleeplessness. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 4 and 8, making it an ideal bedtime story for parents to read with their young ones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Max</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/max_by_bob_graham_isbn_613565177/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/max_by_bob_graham_isbn_613565177/</guid>
      <description>Max by Bob Graham Title: Max Author: Bob Graham Max is a heartwarming and thought-provoking children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the talented author and illustrator, Bob Graham. This beautifully illustrated story follows the adventures of a young boy named Max, who finds a homeless dog and takes it upon himself to care for and protect the animal. Targeted Age Group: Max is most suitable for children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Max and Moritz</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/max_and_moritz_by_heinrich_christian_wilhelm_busch_isbn_9781095977651/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/max_and_moritz_by_heinrich_christian_wilhelm_busch_isbn_9781095977651/</guid>
      <description>Max and Moritz by Heinrich Christian Wilhelm Busch Title: Max and Moritz Author: Heinrich Christian Wilhelm Busch Max and Moritz is a classic children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Heinrich Christian Wilhelm Busch, first published in 1865. The book tells the story of two mischievous boys, Max and Moritz, who engage in a series of pranks that lead to disastrous consequences. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 6 and 12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Gruffalo</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_gruffalo_isbn_999214212x/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_gruffalo_isbn_999214212x/</guid>
      <description>The Gruffalo Title: The Gruffalo Author: Julia Donaldson Illustrator: Axel Scheffler The Gruffalo is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Julia Donaldson and illustrated by Axel Scheffler. The story revolves around a clever mouse who uses his wits to escape the clutches of predators in the deep, dark wood. The mouse invents a fictional creature called the Gruffalo to scare off the predators, only to discover that the Gruffalo is not so fictional after all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pumpkin Soup</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/pumpkin_soup_by_helen_cooper_isbn_374460310/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/pumpkin_soup_by_helen_cooper_isbn_374460310/</guid>
      <description>Pumpkin Soup by Helen Cooper Title: Pumpkin Soup Author: Helen Cooper &amp;ldquo;Pumpkin Soup&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Helen Cooper, which tells the story of three friends - a cat, a squirrel, and a duck - who live in a cozy cottage and work together to make delicious pumpkin soup. The book is filled with beautiful illustrations and captivating storytelling, making it a perfect read for young children. Target Age Group: The book is suitable for children between the ages of 3 and 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frog in Winter</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/frog_in_winter_by_max_velthuijs_isbn_9781842704479/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/frog_in_winter_by_max_velthuijs_isbn_9781842704479/</guid>
      <description>Frog in Winter by Max Velthuijs Title: Frog in Winter Author: Max Velthuijs Frog in Winter is a charming and delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book by Max Velthuijs, which tells the story of a frog who experiences the beauty and challenges of winter for the first time. The book is suitable for children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old, and it teaches valuable life lessons about friendship, overcoming fears, and embracing new experiences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Owl Moon</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/owl_moon_isbn_9780590420440/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/owl_moon_isbn_9780590420440/</guid>
      <description>Owl Moon Title: Owl Moon Author: Jane Yolen Illustrator: John Schoenherr Recommended Age Group: 4-8 years old &amp;ldquo;Owl Moon&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Jane Yolen and illustrated by John Schoenherr. This story is a perfect blend of adventure, family bonding, and the beauty of nature. The book is recommended for children aged 4-8 years old and is a perfect read-aloud story for bedtime or anytime. The story follows a young girl and her father as they venture into the snowy woods in search of an owl.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alfie Gets in First</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/alfie_gets_in_first_by_shirley_hughes_isbn_688008496/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/alfie_gets_in_first_by_shirley_hughes_isbn_688008496/</guid>
      <description>Alfie Gets in First by Shirley Hughes Title: Alfie Gets in First Author: Shirley Hughes Review: Alfie Gets in First is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the talented Shirley Hughes. The story revolves around a young boy named Alfie, who is eager to show his independence and curiosity. Alfie&amp;rsquo;s adventures in the book teach young readers valuable life lessons while also entertaining them with its charming illustrations and engaging storyline.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry the Dirty Dog</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/harry_the_dirty_dog_by_gene_zion_isbn_9780099978701/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/harry_the_dirty_dog_by_gene_zion_isbn_9780099978701/</guid>
      <description>Harry the Dirty Dog by Gene Zion Title: Harry the Dirty Dog Author: Gene Zion Illustrator: Margaret Bloy Graham Harry the Dirty Dog is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Gene Zion and illustrated by Margaret Bloy Graham. This delightful story is about a white dog with black spots named Harry, who hates taking baths. One day, Harry decides to run away from home to avoid a bath. In his adventures, Harry gets so dirty that his family doesn&amp;rsquo;t recognize him, and he almost loses his home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little I Am I</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/little_i_am_i_by_mira_lobe_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/little_i_am_i_by_mira_lobe_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Little I Am I by Mira Lobe Title: Little I Am I Author: Mira Lobe Review: Little I Am I is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Mira Lobe, which is perfect for young readers between the ages of 4 and 8. The book follows the story of a little girl who is trying to find her place in the world and learn about the importance of self-worth. The illustrations in the book are vibrant and eye-catching, which helps to keep the young readers engaged.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lotta&#39;s Bike</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/lottas_bike_by_astrid_lindgren_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/lottas_bike_by_astrid_lindgren_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Lotta&amp;rsquo;s Bike by Astrid Lindgren Title: Lotta&amp;rsquo;s Bike Author: Astrid Lindgren &amp;ldquo;Lotta&amp;rsquo;s Bike&amp;rdquo; is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the talented Astrid Lindgren. This heartwarming story follows the adventures of Lotta, a young girl who dreams of owning a bicycle. The book is beautifully illustrated and is perfect for children aged 4-8 years old. The story is filled with valuable life lessons that children can learn and appreciate. It teaches the importance of perseverance, hard work, and determination.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pancakes for Findus</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/pancakes_for_findus_by_sven_nordqvist_isbn_1912480441/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/pancakes_for_findus_by_sven_nordqvist_isbn_1912480441/</guid>
      <description>Pancakes for Findus by Sven Nordqvist Title: Pancakes for Findus Author: Sven Nordqvist &amp;ldquo;Pancakes for Findus&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Sven Nordqvist, which tells the story of an old man named Farmer Pettson and his curious cat, Findus. The book is a part of a series that revolves around the adventures of Pettson and Findus, and this particular story focuses on the duo&amp;rsquo;s attempt to make pancakes together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Cat in the Hat</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_cat_in_the_hat_by_dr._seuss_isbn_000820151x/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_cat_in_the_hat_by_dr._seuss_isbn_000820151x/</guid>
      <description>The Cat in the Hat by Dr. Seuss Title: The Cat in the Hat Author: Dr. Seuss Review: The Cat in the Hat is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the renowned author Dr. Seuss. The story follows the adventures of a mischievous cat who visits two children, Sally and her brother, on a rainy day. The Cat in the Hat teaches valuable life lessons while keeping the reader entertained with its whimsical rhymes and colorful illustrations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bedtime for Frances</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/bedtime_for_frances_by_russell_hoban_isbn_9780571052745/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/bedtime_for_frances_by_russell_hoban_isbn_9780571052745/</guid>
      <description>Bedtime for Frances by Russell Hoban Title: Bedtime for Frances Author: Russell Hoban Review: Bedtime for Frances is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Russell Hoban. The story follows a young badger named Frances who is reluctant to go to bed, as she is afraid of the dark and monsters under her bed. With the help of her loving and patient parents, Frances learns to overcome her fears and embrace bedtime.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fly, Little Bird</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/fly_little_bird_by_francesco_tullio_altan_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/fly_little_bird_by_francesco_tullio_altan_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Fly, Little Bird by Francesco Tullio Altan Title: Fly, Little Bird Author: Francesco Tullio Altan Fly, Little Bird is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book by Francesco Tullio Altan that tells the story of a young bird who dreams of flying high and exploring the world. The book is perfect for children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old, as it is filled with colorful illustrations and simple, yet engaging language.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maisy Goes to Playschool</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/maisy_goes_to_playschool_by_lucy_cousins_isbn_1406306924/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/maisy_goes_to_playschool_by_lucy_cousins_isbn_1406306924/</guid>
      <description>Maisy Goes to Playschool by Lucy Cousins Title: Maisy Goes to Playschool Author: Lucy Cousins Review: Maisy Goes to Playschool is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the adventures of Maisy, a lovable mouse, as she experiences her first day at playschool. The book is targeted towards children aged 3 to 6 years old, making it a perfect read for preschoolers and kindergarteners. Author Lucy Cousins has done an excellent job of creating a relatable and engaging story that captures the essence of a child&amp;rsquo;s first day at school.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mike Mulligan</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/mike_mulligan_by_virginia_lee_burton_isbn_9789995250270/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/mike_mulligan_by_virginia_lee_burton_isbn_9789995250270/</guid>
      <description>Mike Mulligan by Virginia Lee Burton Title: Mike Mulligan and His Steam Shovel Author: Virginia Lee Burton Review: Mike Mulligan and His Steam Shovel is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of Mike Mulligan, a hardworking and dedicated steam shovel operator, and his trusty steam shovel, Mary Anne. The book is perfect for children aged 4 to 8 years old and teaches valuable life lessons about perseverance, friendship, and adapting to change.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Owl Babies</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/owl_babies_by_martin_waddell_isbn_1854303449/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/owl_babies_by_martin_waddell_isbn_1854303449/</guid>
      <description>Owl Babies by Martin Waddell Title: Owl Babies Author: Martin Waddell Owl Babies is a heartwarming and engaging children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Martin Waddell. The story follows the adventures of three young owlets who wake up one night to find their mother missing from their nest. The three siblings, Sarah, Percy, and Bill, are filled with worry and concern as they wait for their mother&amp;rsquo;s return. The book is beautifully illustrated by Patrick Benson, with soft and warm images that perfectly capture the emotions of the young owlets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Bear Went Over the Mountain</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_bear_went_over_the_mountain_by_john_prater_isbn_9780370323688/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_bear_went_over_the_mountain_by_john_prater_isbn_9780370323688/</guid>
      <description>The Bear Went Over the Mountain by John Prater Title: The Bear Went Over the Mountain Author: John Prater Review: The Bear Went Over the Mountain is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a curious bear who decides to explore the world beyond his familiar mountain home. With vibrant illustrations and engaging storytelling, author John Prater captures the imagination of young readers and takes them on a journey of discovery and adventure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Story of Ping</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_story_of_ping_by_marjorie_flack_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_story_of_ping_by_marjorie_flack_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Story of Ping by Marjorie Flack Title: The Story of Ping Author: Marjorie Flack Review: The Story of Ping is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Marjorie Flack and illustrated by Kurt Wiese. This timeless classic tells the story of a young duck named Ping, who lives with his family on a boat in the Yangtze River in China. The book, first published in 1933, has been enjoyed by generations of children and continues to be a popular choice for parents and educators alike.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Tale of Jemima Puddle Duck</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_tale_of_jemima_puddle_duck_isbn_723247781/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_tale_of_jemima_puddle_duck_isbn_723247781/</guid>
      <description>The Tale of Jemima Puddle Duck Title: The Tale of Jemima Puddle Duck Author: Beatrix Potter The Tale of Jemima Puddle Duck is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Beatrix Potter. The story follows Jemima Puddle Duck, a lovely duck who is looking for a quiet place to lay her eggs. Along the way, she encounters a sly fox who tries to trick her into his clutches. However, with the help of some friendly animals, Jemima Puddle Duck outwits the fox and finds a safe place to lay her eggs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Tale of Mr Jeremy Fisher</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_tale_of_mr_jeremy_fisher_by_beatrix_potter_isbn_9780723244257/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_tale_of_mr_jeremy_fisher_by_beatrix_potter_isbn_9780723244257/</guid>
      <description>The Tale of Mr Jeremy Fisher by Beatrix Potter Title: The Tale of Mr. Jeremy Fisher Author: Beatrix Potter Review: The Tale of Mr. Jeremy Fisher is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Beatrix Potter, a renowned author and illustrator. The story revolves around Mr. Jeremy Fisher, a frog who lives in a beautiful pond and is on a quest to find a tasty meal. Throughout the book, readers are taken on a journey with Mr.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
