<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Childrens Books that talk about &#39;Persevere&#39; on Monsty The Monster Truck</title>
    <link>https://www.monsty.co/tags/childrens-books-that-talk-about-persevere/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Childrens Books that talk about &#39;Persevere&#39; on Monsty The Monster Truck</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.monsty.co/tags/childrens-books-that-talk-about-persevere/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Pig-Heart Boy</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/pig-heart_boy_by_malorie_blackman_isbn_9780552528412/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/pig-heart_boy_by_malorie_blackman_isbn_9780552528412/</guid>
      <description>Pig-Heart Boy by Malorie Blackman Title: Pig-Heart Boy Author: Malorie Blackman Review: Pig-Heart Boy is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Malorie Blackman, which explores the life of a young boy named Cameron. The story follows Cameron&amp;rsquo;s journey as he faces a life-threatening heart condition and the challenges that come with receiving a heart transplant from a pig. This book is targeted towards children aged 8-12 years old and covers important life lessons such as empathy, acceptance, and overcoming adversity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Devil&#39;s Arithmetic</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_devils_arithmetic_by_jane_yolen_isbn_9781664495296/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_devils_arithmetic_by_jane_yolen_isbn_9781664495296/</guid>
      <description>The Devil&amp;rsquo;s Arithmetic by Jane Yolen Title: The Devil&amp;rsquo;s Arithmetic Author: Jane Yolen Review: The Devil&amp;rsquo;s Arithmetic, written by Jane Yolen, is a poignant and thought-provoking children&amp;rsquo;s book that delves into the harsh realities of the Holocaust. The story follows a young girl named Hannah, who is transported back in time to a concentration camp during the Holocaust. Through her experiences, she learns the importance of remembering and honoring the past, as well as the value of courage and resilience in the face of adversity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>There Will Be Wolves</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/there_will_be_wolves_by_karleen_bradford_isbn_9780525675396/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/there_will_be_wolves_by_karleen_bradford_isbn_9780525675396/</guid>
      <description>There Will Be Wolves by Karleen Bradford Title: There Will Be Wolves Author: Karleen Bradford Review: There Will Be Wolves is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Karleen Bradford, which tells the story of a young boy named Connor who is forced to confront his fears and overcome challenges in a thrilling adventure. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 8 and 12, and it teaches valuable life lessons about courage, resilience, and the importance of family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Last Giants</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_last_giants_by_francois_place_isbn_9781862052895/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_last_giants_by_francois_place_isbn_9781862052895/</guid>
      <description>The Last Giants by Francois Place Title: The Last Giants Author: Francois Place The Last Giants, written by Francois Place, is a beautifully illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes readers on a magical journey through a world of giants. The story is perfect for children aged 7-10 years old, as it contains a captivating plot and vivid imagery that will engage young readers. The book follows the adventures of two young giants, Leo and his sister, as they embark on a quest to save their family and their world from the evil clutches of the Dark Giant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Turbulent Term of Tyke Tiler</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_turbulent_term_of_tyke_tiler_isbn_198312695/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_turbulent_term_of_tyke_tiler_isbn_198312695/</guid>
      <description>The Turbulent Term of Tyke Tiler Title: The Turbulent Term of Tyke Tiler Author: Gene Kemp The Turbulent Term of Tyke Tiler is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Gene Kemp. The story follows the adventures of Tyke Tiler, a young boy who is struggling to fit in at his new school. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 8 and 12, and is an engaging read that teaches valuable life lessons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uncle</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/uncle_by_j.p._martin_isbn_9780099294504/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/uncle_by_j.p._martin_isbn_9780099294504/</guid>
      <description>Uncle by J.P. Martin Title: Uncle Author: J.P. Martin Review: &amp;ldquo;Uncle&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by J.P. Martin, which takes the readers on an exciting adventure in the world of fantasy. The story follows the life of a wealthy, kind-hearted man named Uncle, who lives in a huge, magical house called &amp;ldquo;The Manor.&amp;rdquo; Uncle&amp;rsquo;s house is filled with talking animals, who are his loyal friends and helpers. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 6 and 12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Little Bookroom</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_little_bookroom_isbn_9780192719478/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_little_bookroom_isbn_9780192719478/</guid>
      <description>The Little Bookroom Title: The Little Bookroom Author: Eleanor Farjeon Illustrator: Edward Ardizzone The Little Bookroom is a charming and delightful collection of short stories that will captivate the hearts of young readers. Eleanor Farjeon, the author, has skillfully woven a tapestry of tales that transport the reader to a world of enchantment and adventure. The book is accompanied by beautiful illustrations by Edward Ardizzone, which add to the overall charm of the stories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tar Beach</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/tar_beach_isbn_590463810/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/tar_beach_isbn_590463810/</guid>
      <description>Tar Beach Title: Tar Beach Author: Faith Ringgold Target Age Group: 5-10 years old Tar Beach is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Faith Ringgold, which takes readers on a magical journey through the eyes of a young girl named Cassie. The story is set in the 1930s and is based on the author&amp;rsquo;s own experiences growing up in Harlem. The book is beautifully illustrated with Faith Ringgold&amp;rsquo;s quilt-like artwork, which adds to the charm and uniqueness of the story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Doll&#39;s House</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_dolls_house_by_rumer_godden_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_dolls_house_by_rumer_godden_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Doll&amp;rsquo;s House by Rumer Godden Title: The Doll&amp;rsquo;s House Author: Rumer Godden The Doll&amp;rsquo;s House, written by Rumer Godden, is a charming and enchanting children&amp;rsquo;s book that captures the essence of childhood imagination and the importance of friendship. The story revolves around two young sisters, Tottie and Emily, who receive a beautiful dollhouse as a gift. The dollhouse becomes a magical world where the dolls come to life and experience their own adventures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Little Red Engine Gets a Name</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_little_red_engine_gets_a_name_by_diana_ross_isbn_571064396/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_little_red_engine_gets_a_name_by_diana_ross_isbn_571064396/</guid>
      <description>The Little Red Engine Gets a Name by Diana Ross Title: The Little Red Engine Gets a Name Author: Diana Ross Review: The Little Red Engine Gets a Name is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Diana Ross. This delightful story follows the adventures of a little red engine who doesn&amp;rsquo;t have a name. The little red engine embarks on a journey to find a name that truly represents who they are.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Little Wooden Horse</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_little_wooden_horse_by_ursula_m_williams_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_little_wooden_horse_by_ursula_m_williams_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Little Wooden Horse by Ursula M Williams Title: The Little Wooden Horse Author: Ursula M. Williams The Little Wooden Horse is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Ursula M. Williams. This heartwarming story is perfect for children aged 5-8 years old, as it contains simple language and engaging illustrations that will capture their attention. The story revolves around a little wooden horse named Timothy, who dreams of becoming a real horse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Bear Called Paddington</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/a_bear_called_paddington_isbn_9780440404835/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/a_bear_called_paddington_isbn_9780440404835/</guid>
      <description>A Bear Called Paddington Title: A Bear Called Paddington Author: Michael Bond A Bear Called Paddington is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Michael Bond, first published in 1958. The story follows the adventures of a lovable bear named Paddington, who arrives in London from Peru and is taken in by the Brown family. Target Age Group: A Bear Called Paddington is suitable for children aged 6 to 10 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little I Am I</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/little_i_am_i_by_mira_lobe_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/little_i_am_i_by_mira_lobe_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Little I Am I by Mira Lobe Title: Little I Am I Author: Mira Lobe Review: Little I Am I is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Mira Lobe, which is perfect for young readers between the ages of 4 and 8. The book follows the story of a little girl who is trying to find her place in the world and learn about the importance of self-worth. The illustrations in the book are vibrant and eye-catching, which helps to keep the young readers engaged.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mr. Tickle</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/mr._tickle_by_roger_hargreaves_isbn_749800003/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/mr._tickle_by_roger_hargreaves_isbn_749800003/</guid>
      <description>Mr. Tickle by Roger Hargreaves Title: Mr. Tickle Author: Roger Hargreaves Review: Mr. Tickle is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Roger Hargreaves, and it is part of the popular &amp;ldquo;Mr. Men and Little Miss&amp;rdquo; series. This book is perfect for young readers between the ages of 4 and 8 years old. The story revolves around the character Mr. Tickle, who has extraordinarily long arms that allow him to reach far and wide.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who&#39;s Seen the Scissors?</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/whos_seen_the_scissors_by_fernando_krahn_isbn_525427104/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/whos_seen_the_scissors_by_fernando_krahn_isbn_525427104/</guid>
      <description>Who&amp;rsquo;s Seen the Scissors? by Fernando Krahn Title: &amp;ldquo;Who&amp;rsquo;s Seen the Scissors?&amp;quot; Author: Fernando Krahn Review: &amp;ldquo;Who&amp;rsquo;s Seen the Scissors?&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book by Fernando Krahn that follows the adventures of a group of friendly animals living in a peaceful forest. The story is engaging and filled with colorful illustrations that capture the imagination of young readers. The book targets children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old, making it an excellent choice for parents, teachers, and caregivers looking for a fun and educational read.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
