<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Childrens Books that talk about &#39;Risk&#39; on Monsty The Monster Truck</title>
    <link>https://www.monsty.co/tags/childrens-books-that-talk-about-risk/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Childrens Books that talk about &#39;Risk&#39; on Monsty The Monster Truck</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.monsty.co/tags/childrens-books-that-talk-about-risk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Crispin</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/crispin_isbn_9780606305556/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/crispin_isbn_9780606305556/</guid>
      <description>Crispin Title: Crispin Author: Avi Review: Crispin is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Avi, which tells the story of a young boy named Crispin, who embarks on a thrilling adventure in medieval England. The book is targeted towards children aged 8-12, as it features themes of friendship, bravery, and perseverance. The story follows Crispin, a 13-year-old boy who is falsely accused of a crime and forced to flee his village.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finding Violet Park</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/finding_violet_park_by_jenny_valentine_isbn_7291248/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/finding_violet_park_by_jenny_valentine_isbn_7291248/</guid>
      <description>Finding Violet Park by Jenny Valentine Title: Finding Violet Park Author: Jenny Valentine Review: Finding Violet Park is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Jenny Valentine, which tells the story of a young boy named Lucas who embarks on a journey to find the mysterious Violet Park. The book is suitable for children aged 8-12 years old, as it contains elements of adventure, mystery, and self-discovery. The story follows Lucas as he navigates through various challenges and obstacles in his quest to find Violet Park.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heart&#39;s Delight</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/hearts_delight_by_per_nilsson_isbn_9781886910928/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/hearts_delight_by_per_nilsson_isbn_9781886910928/</guid>
      <description>Heart&amp;rsquo;s Delight by Per Nilsson Title: Heart&amp;rsquo;s Delight Author: Per Nilsson Review: Heart&amp;rsquo;s Delight is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that captures the hearts of young readers with its charming story and beautiful illustrations. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 4 and 8, and it teaches valuable life lessons through its engaging narrative. The story revolves around a young girl named Elsa, who is given a special heart-shaped box by her grandmother.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Devil&#39;s Arithmetic</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_devils_arithmetic_by_jane_yolen_isbn_9781664495296/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_devils_arithmetic_by_jane_yolen_isbn_9781664495296/</guid>
      <description>The Devil&amp;rsquo;s Arithmetic by Jane Yolen Title: The Devil&amp;rsquo;s Arithmetic Author: Jane Yolen Review: The Devil&amp;rsquo;s Arithmetic, written by Jane Yolen, is a poignant and thought-provoking children&amp;rsquo;s book that delves into the harsh realities of the Holocaust. The story follows a young girl named Hannah, who is transported back in time to a concentration camp during the Holocaust. Through her experiences, she learns the importance of remembering and honoring the past, as well as the value of courage and resilience in the face of adversity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Long Way From Verona</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/a_long_way_from_verona_by_jane_gardam_isbn_349114056/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/a_long_way_from_verona_by_jane_gardam_isbn_349114056/</guid>
      <description>A Long Way From Verona by Jane Gardam Title: A Long Way From Verona Author: Jane Gardam Review: A Long Way From Verona is a delightful and thought-provoking children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Jane Gardam. The story follows the life of a young girl named Betty Carpenter, who is growing up in a small village during World War II. The book is an engaging read for children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old, as it covers themes such as friendship, family, and resilience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Island on Bird Street</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_island_on_bird_street_by_uri_orlev_isbn_9780091595807/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_island_on_bird_street_by_uri_orlev_isbn_9780091595807/</guid>
      <description>The Island on Bird Street by Uri Orlev Title: The Island on Bird Street Author: Uri Orlev Review: The Island on Bird Street is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Uri Orlev, which takes readers on a heartwarming journey through the eyes of a young boy named Alex. The story is set during World War II, where Alex and his family are forced to live in a ghetto due to their Jewish heritage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Lark and the Laurel</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_lark_and_the_laurel_by_barbara_willard_isbn_356131696/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_lark_and_the_laurel_by_barbara_willard_isbn_356131696/</guid>
      <description>The Lark and the Laurel by Barbara Willard Title: The Lark and the Laurel Author: Barbara Willard Review: The Lark and the Laurel is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Barbara Willard. The story revolves around the adventures of a young lark and a laurel tree, both of whom face various challenges and learn valuable life lessons along the way. The book is targeted towards children aged 6 to 10 years old, as it contains beautiful illustrations and a simple yet engaging narrative that captures the imagination of young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Am David</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/i_am_david_isbn_416233406/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/i_am_david_isbn_416233406/</guid>
      <description>I Am David Title: I Am David Author: Anne Holm Review: I Am David is a heartwarming and adventurous children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young boy named David, who escapes from a Bulgarian labor camp and embarks on a journey to find freedom and a new life. The book is beautifully written by Anne Holm, and it captures the essence of hope, resilience, and the human spirit. The story is suitable for children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old, as it contains themes of friendship, courage, and self-discovery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Capture the Castle</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/i_capture_the_castle_by_dodie_smith_isbn_8379430069/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/i_capture_the_castle_by_dodie_smith_isbn_8379430069/</guid>
      <description>I Capture the Castle by Dodie Smith Title: I Capture the Castle Author: Dodie Smith Review: I Capture the Castle is a charming and delightful novel that captures the essence of childhood and the complexities of growing up. The story follows the adventures of Cassandra Mortmain, a young girl living in a crumbling castle with her family. As Cassandra navigates the ups and downs of life, she learns valuable lessons about love, friendship, and the importance of staying true to oneself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time of Trial</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/time_of_trial_isbn_9780192720429/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/time_of_trial_isbn_9780192720429/</guid>
      <description>Time of Trial Title: Time of Trial Author: C.S. Lakin Target Age Group: 8-12 years old Time of Trial is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by C.S. Lakin. The story follows the adventures of a young boy named Jadiel, who finds himself in a world where time is a valuable commodity. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 8 and 12, as it contains elements of adventure, mystery, and fantasy that are sure to engage young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Cat: Or, How I Lost Eternity</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_cat_or_how_i_lost_eternity_by_jutta_richter_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_cat_or_how_i_lost_eternity_by_jutta_richter_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Cat: Or, How I Lost Eternity by Jutta Richter Title: The Cat: Or, How I Lost Eternity Author: Jutta Richter Review: The Cat: Or, How I Lost Eternity is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Jutta Richter. This story is an excellent choice for young readers between the ages of 8 and 12 years old. The book&amp;rsquo;s engaging narrative and beautiful illustrations make it an enjoyable read for both children and adults.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Friend the Painter</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/my_friend_the_painter_by_lygia_bojunga_isbn_9780152563400/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/my_friend_the_painter_by_lygia_bojunga_isbn_9780152563400/</guid>
      <description>My Friend the Painter by Lygia Bojunga Title: My Friend the Painter Author: Lygia Bojunga Target Age Group: 8-12 years old &amp;ldquo;My Friend the Painter&amp;rdquo; is a beautifully written and illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book by Lygia Bojunga. The story revolves around a young boy named Tim, who befriends a talented painter named Pablo. Through their friendship, Tim learns about the importance of following one&amp;rsquo;s passion, the power of imagination, and the beauty of art.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Pair of Jesus Boots</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/a_pair_of_jesus_boots_by_sylvia_sherry_isbn_224615769/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/a_pair_of_jesus_boots_by_sylvia_sherry_isbn_224615769/</guid>
      <description>A Pair of Jesus Boots by Sylvia Sherry Title: A Pair of Jesus Boots Author: Sylvia Sherry Review: A Pair of Jesus Boots is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Sylvia Sherry. The story follows a young boy named Timmy, who desperately wants a pair of Jesus Boots - boots that can walk on water just like Jesus did. The book is targeted towards children aged 4-8 years old and is a perfect blend of adventure, imagination, and heartwarming lessons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Platero and I</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/platero_and_i_isbn_9780292733282/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/platero_and_i_isbn_9780292733282/</guid>
      <description>Platero and I Title: Platero and I Author: Juan Ramón Jiménez Recommended Age Group: 8-12 years old Platero and I is a beautifully written and illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book that captures the essence of a young boy&amp;rsquo;s adventures with his loyal donkey, Platero, in a small Andalusian village. The book is filled with heartwarming stories that touch upon various life lessons, making it an excellent choice for children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Black Corsair</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_black_corsair_by_emilio_salgari_isbn_6077200069/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_black_corsair_by_emilio_salgari_isbn_6077200069/</guid>
      <description>The Black Corsair by Emilio Salgari Title: The Black Corsair Author: Emilio Salgari Review: The Black Corsair, written by Emilio Salgari, is a thrilling adventure story that is perfect for elementary school-aged children. The book is filled with action, excitement, and valuable life lessons that will captivate young readers. The story follows the adventures of Emilio, a young boy who is captured by pirates and forced to join their crew. As Emilio becomes part of the pirate world, he learns about courage, friendship, and the importance of standing up for what is right.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>George MacDonald at the Back of the North Wind</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/george_macdonald_at_the_back_of_the_north_wind_isbn_9798519978361/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/george_macdonald_at_the_back_of_the_north_wind_isbn_9798519978361/</guid>
      <description>George MacDonald at the Back of the North Wind Title: George MacDonald at the Back of the North Wind Author: George MacDonald Age Group: 8-12 years old The children&amp;rsquo;s book &amp;lsquo;George MacDonald at the Back of the North Wind&amp;rsquo; is a beautifully written and enchanting story that captures the hearts of young readers. Author George MacDonald weaves a tale that is both magical and thought-provoking, making it an excellent choice for children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Hate School</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/i_hate_school_by_jeanne_willis_isbn_9786077352655/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/i_hate_school_by_jeanne_willis_isbn_9786077352655/</guid>
      <description>I Hate School by Jeanne Willis Title: I Hate School Author: Jeanne Willis Review: &amp;ldquo;I Hate School&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Jeanne Willis, which is perfect for young readers between the ages of 4 to 8 years old. The story revolves around a young boy named Charlie, who is not very fond of going to school. The book explores the various reasons behind Charlie&amp;rsquo;s dislike for school and how his perspective changes over time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Friends From the Other Side</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/friends_from_the_other_side_by_gloria_anzaldua_isbn_9780892391134/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/friends_from_the_other_side_by_gloria_anzaldua_isbn_9780892391134/</guid>
      <description>Friends From the Other Side by Gloria Anzaldua Title: Friends From the Other Side Author: Gloria Anzaldua Review: &amp;ldquo;Friends From the Other Side&amp;rdquo; is a beautifully written and illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young girl named Marisol, who lives near the U.S.-Mexico border. The book explores themes of friendship, empathy, and understanding, as Marisol befriends a group of children from the other side of the border. The story is engaging and age-appropriate for children between the ages of 6 and 10 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Keeping Quilt</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_keeping_quilt_by_patricia_polacco_isbn_9780440831709/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_keeping_quilt_by_patricia_polacco_isbn_9780440831709/</guid>
      <description>The Keeping Quilt by Patricia Polacco Title: The Keeping Quilt Author: Patricia Polacco The Keeping Quilt, written by Patricia Polacco, is a heartwarming and beautifully illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a family&amp;rsquo;s cherished quilt and the traditions that it represents. This book is a perfect choice for children aged 5 to 10 years old, as it touches upon themes of family, love, and the importance of preserving cultural heritage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Felix and Alexander</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/felix_and_alexander_by_terry_denton_isbn_019554658x/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/felix_and_alexander_by_terry_denton_isbn_019554658x/</guid>
      <description>Felix and Alexander by Terry Denton Title: Felix and Alexander Author: Terry Denton Target Age Group: 5-8 years old Felix and Alexander is a heartwarming and entertaining children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Terry Denton. The story revolves around two best friends, Felix the cat and Alexander the dog, who live together in a small house. Throughout the book, they go on adventures, learn new things, and support each other in times of need.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Freight Train</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/freight_train_isbn_9789573212409/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/freight_train_isbn_9789573212409/</guid>
      <description>Freight Train Title: Freight Train Author: Donald Crews Freight Train is a charming and vibrant children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes young readers on a journey through the world of trains. With its simple yet engaging story and colorful illustrations, this book is perfect for children aged 2 to 5 years old. The story follows a freight train as it travels through different landscapes, passing by cities, mountains, and tunnels. The book teaches children about colors, shapes, and the concept of a train&amp;rsquo;s journey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make Way for Ducklings</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/make_way_for_ducklings_isbn_874996589/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/make_way_for_ducklings_isbn_874996589/</guid>
      <description>Make Way for Ducklings Title: Make Way for Ducklings Author: Robert McCloskey Target Age Group: 4-8 years old &amp;ldquo;Make Way for Ducklings&amp;rdquo; is a timeless classic written by Robert McCloskey, which has been capturing the hearts of young readers since its publication in 1941. The story revolves around a family of ducks who are searching for a safe place to raise their ducklings in Boston&amp;rsquo;s Public Garden. The book is beautifully illustrated, with detailed drawings that bring the characters to life.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
