<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Childrens Books that talk about &#39;Open&#39; on Monsty The Monster Truck</title>
    <link>https://www.monsty.co/tags/childrens-books-that-talk-about-open/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Childrens Books that talk about &#39;Open&#39; on Monsty The Monster Truck</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.monsty.co/tags/childrens-books-that-talk-about-open/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A Jump Into the Other World</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/a_jump_into_the_other_world_by_bruno_tognolini_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/a_jump_into_the_other_world_by_bruno_tognolini_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>A Jump Into the Other World by Bruno Tognolini Title: A Jump Into the Other World Author: Bruno Tognolini Review: A Jump Into the Other World is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that transports young readers on an exciting adventure filled with fantasy and valuable life lessons. Author Bruno Tognolini has crafted a story that captivates the imagination while teaching important morals. The book is suitable for children between the ages of 7 and 12.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>By the River</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/by_the_river_by_steven_herrick_isbn_9781741143577/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/by_the_river_by_steven_herrick_isbn_9781741143577/</guid>
      <description>By the River by Steven Herrick Title: By the River Author: Steven Herrick Review: By the River is a beautifully written children&amp;rsquo;s book by Steven Herrick that captures the essence of childhood innocence and the importance of friendship. The book is perfect for children aged 8-12, as it is both engaging and thought-provoking. The story follows the life of Ben, a young boy who spends his days by the river, observing the world around him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Am Not Esther</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/i_am_not_esther_by_fleur_beale_isbn_9781864470598/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/i_am_not_esther_by_fleur_beale_isbn_9781864470598/</guid>
      <description>I Am Not Esther by Fleur Beale Title: I Am Not Esther Author: Fleur Beale Review: I Am Not Esther is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Fleur Beale, which tells the story of a young girl named Kirby who is forced to live with her estranged relatives after her mother&amp;rsquo;s sudden death. The book primarily targets children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old, as it explores themes of family, friendship, and self-discovery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Molly Goes Shopping</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/molly_goes_shopping_by_eva_eriksson_isbn_9129658195/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/molly_goes_shopping_by_eva_eriksson_isbn_9129658195/</guid>
      <description>Molly Goes Shopping by Eva Eriksson Title: Molly Goes Shopping Author: Eva Eriksson Molly Goes Shopping is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Eva Eriksson, aimed at children between the ages of 4 to 8 years old. The story follows the adventures of a young girl named Molly, who goes shopping with her mother and learns important life lessons along the way. The illustrations in the book are vibrant and engaging, capturing the attention of young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peeling the Onion</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/peeling_the_onion_by_wendy_orr_isbn_9781741149333/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/peeling_the_onion_by_wendy_orr_isbn_9781741149333/</guid>
      <description>Peeling the Onion by Wendy Orr Title: Peeling the Onion Author: Wendy Orr Review: Peeling the Onion is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Wendy Orr, which takes the reader on a journey of self-discovery and friendship. The story revolves around a young girl named Mia, who struggles with the challenges of growing up and finding her place in the world. Target Age Group: The book is suitable for children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rosa Goes to Daycare</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/rosa_goes_to_daycare_by_barbro_lindgren_isbn_9780888993915/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/rosa_goes_to_daycare_by_barbro_lindgren_isbn_9780888993915/</guid>
      <description>Rosa Goes to Daycare by Barbro Lindgren Title: Rosa Goes to Daycare Author: Barbro Lindgren Review: Rosa Goes to Daycare is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the story of Rosa, a young girl who is nervous about attending daycare for the first time. Throughout the book, Rosa learns to adjust to her new environment and make friends, ultimately overcoming her fears and enjoying her time at daycare. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 3-6 years old, as it deals with themes such as overcoming anxiety, making friends, and adjusting to new situations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Curious Incident of the Dog in the Night-Time – Mark Haddon</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_curious_incident_of_the_dog_in_the_night-time__mark_haddon_isbn_521613795/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_curious_incident_of_the_dog_in_the_night-time__mark_haddon_isbn_521613795/</guid>
      <description>The Curious Incident of the Dog in the Night-Time – Mark Haddon Title: The Curious Incident of the Dog in the Night-Time Author: Mark Haddon Age Group: 12 years and above &amp;ldquo;The Curious Incident of the Dog in the Night-Time&amp;rdquo; is a captivating and thought-provoking novel that tells the story of Christopher Boone, a 15-year-old boy with Asperger&amp;rsquo;s Syndrome. The book takes the reader on a journey through Christopher&amp;rsquo;s unique perspective as he navigates the complexities of everyday life and solves the mystery of a murdered dog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Illustrated Mum</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_illustrated_mum_isbn_9780385902632/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_illustrated_mum_isbn_9780385902632/</guid>
      <description>The Illustrated Mum Title: The Illustrated Mum Author: Jacqueline Wilson Review: The Illustrated Mum is a heartwarming and poignant children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of two sisters, Dolphin and Star, who navigate the challenges of growing up with a mother suffering from mental illness. The book is beautifully illustrated and the artwork complements the emotional depth of the story. The target age group for this book is children between the ages of 8 and 12.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Walk Two Moons</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/walk_two_moons_isbn_9780590649438/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/walk_two_moons_isbn_9780590649438/</guid>
      <description>Walk Two Moons Title: Walk Two Moons Author: Sharon Creech Review: Walk Two Moons is a beautifully written children&amp;rsquo;s novel by Sharon Creech, which tells the story of a young girl named Salamanca Tree Hiddle, who embarks on a journey to find her missing mother. The book is an engaging and thought-provoking read that explores themes of family, friendship, and the power of storytelling. Target Age Group: The book is suitable for children aged 9-12 years old, as it contains relatable themes and characters that resonate well with this age group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Pack of Lies</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/a_pack_of_lies_isbn_019271788x/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/a_pack_of_lies_isbn_019271788x/</guid>
      <description>A Pack of Lies Title: A Pack of Lies Author: Laurel Remington Genre: Children&amp;rsquo;s Fiction, Mystery A Pack of Lies is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes readers on a thrilling adventure filled with mystery and intrigue. Laurel Remington has done an excellent job of creating a story that captures the imagination of young readers and keeps them engaged from beginning to end. The book is targeted towards children aged 8-12 years old, making it an ideal choice for elementary school students.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dear Nobody</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/dear_nobody_isbn_531086119/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/dear_nobody_isbn_531086119/</guid>
      <description>Dear Nobody Title: Dear Nobody Author: Berlie Doherty Recommended Age Group: 8-12 years old Dear Nobody is a heartwarming and thought-provoking children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Berlie Doherty. The story revolves around two main characters, Helen and Chris, who are both dealing with the challenges of growing up and navigating their emotions. The book is written in a diary format, with Helen and Chris taking turns to share their thoughts and feelings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flour Babies</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/flour_babies_isbn_9780316283199/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/flour_babies_isbn_9780316283199/</guid>
      <description>Flour Babies Title: Flour Babies Author: Anne Fine Flour Babies is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Anne Fine, which was first published in 1992. The story revolves around a group of elementary school students who are given flour sacks as their &amp;lsquo;babies&amp;rsquo; to take care of, as part of a school project. The project aims to teach the students about the responsibilities and challenges of parenthood. The book is suitable for children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hey, Dollface</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/hey_dollface_by_deborah_hautzig_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/hey_dollface_by_deborah_hautzig_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Hey, Dollface by Deborah Hautzig Title: Hey, Dollface Author: Deborah Hautzig Review: Hey, Dollface is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Deborah Hautzig. The story revolves around a young girl named Dollface, who is struggling to find her identity and place in the world. Throughout the book, Dollface encounters various challenges and experiences that help her grow and learn valuable life lessons. Target Age Group: Hey, Dollface is primarily targeted towards children between the ages of 8 and 12.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>See Ya, Simon</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/see_ya_simon_by_david_hill_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/see_ya_simon_by_david_hill_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>See Ya, Simon by David Hill Title: See Ya, Simon Author: David Hill Target Age Group: 8-12 years old &amp;ldquo;See Ya, Simon&amp;rdquo; is a heartwarming and engaging children&amp;rsquo;s book by David Hill that captures the attention of young readers with its relatable characters and themes. The story revolves around a young boy named Simon, who struggles with the challenges of growing up and navigating the complexities of friendships and relationships. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 8 and 12, as it addresses issues that are relevant to this age group, such as bullying, self-esteem, and the importance of communication.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some of the Kinder Planets</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/some_of_the_kinder_planets_by_tim_wynne-jones_isbn_531087514/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/some_of_the_kinder_planets_by_tim_wynne-jones_isbn_531087514/</guid>
      <description>Some of the Kinder Planets by Tim Wynne-Jones Title: Some of the Kinder Planets Author: Tim Wynne-Jones Review: Some of the Kinder Planets is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes young readers on a whimsical journey through the solar system. Written by Tim Wynne-Jones, this book is perfect for children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old. The story follows a young boy named Leo who, after being scolded by his mother for not cleaning his room, decides to run away to the kinder planets in the solar system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Island on Bird Street</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_island_on_bird_street_by_uri_orlev_isbn_9780091595807/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_island_on_bird_street_by_uri_orlev_isbn_9780091595807/</guid>
      <description>The Island on Bird Street by Uri Orlev Title: The Island on Bird Street Author: Uri Orlev Review: The Island on Bird Street is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Uri Orlev, which takes readers on a heartwarming journey through the eyes of a young boy named Alex. The story is set during World War II, where Alex and his family are forced to live in a ghetto due to their Jewish heritage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Sentinels</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_sentinels_by_peter_carter_isbn_9780862671952/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_sentinels_by_peter_carter_isbn_9780862671952/</guid>
      <description>The Sentinels by Peter Carter Title: The Sentinels Author: Peter Carter The Sentinels is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that captures the imagination of young readers and teaches them valuable life lessons. Author Peter Carter has created a world filled with adventure, mystery, and important messages that resonate with readers of all ages. The story follows the journey of a group of young friends who discover a hidden world within their own town.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thunderwith</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/thunderwith_by_libby_hathorn_isbn_732005566/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/thunderwith_by_libby_hathorn_isbn_732005566/</guid>
      <description>Thunderwith by Libby Hathorn Title: Thunderwith Author: Libby Hathorn Thunderwith is a beautifully written children&amp;rsquo;s book by Libby Hathorn that captures the imagination of young readers with its enchanting storytelling and vivid illustrations. The book is primarily targeted towards children between the ages of 6 and 10 years old, making it an excellent choice for elementary school students. The story follows the adventures of a young boy named Tim, who discovers a magical world filled with talking animals and a powerful storm called Thunderwith.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chocky</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/chocky_isbn_14_003121_9/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/chocky_isbn_14_003121_9/</guid>
      <description>Chocky Title: Chocky Author: John Wyndham Genre: Science Fiction, Children&amp;rsquo;s Literature Recommended Age Group: 8-12 years old Chocky is a captivating science fiction novel written by John Wyndham, which tells the story of a young boy named Matthew who starts having conversations with an invisible entity named Chocky. The book is a perfect blend of adventure, mystery, and a touch of humor, making it an enjoyable read for children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nobody&#39;s Family Is Going to Change</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/nobodys_family_is_going_to_change_by_louise_fitzhugh_isbn_333294505/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/nobodys_family_is_going_to_change_by_louise_fitzhugh_isbn_333294505/</guid>
      <description>Nobody&amp;rsquo;s Family Is Going to Change by Louise Fitzhugh Title: Nobody&amp;rsquo;s Family Is Going to Change Author: Louise Fitzhugh Review: &amp;ldquo;Nobody&amp;rsquo;s Family Is Going to Change&amp;rdquo; is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Louise Fitzhugh, which tells the story of a young boy named Tommy who is trying to find his place in the world. The book is perfect for children aged 8-12 years old, as it deals with themes of self-discovery, family dynamics, and acceptance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twopence a Tub</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/twopence_a_tub_by_susan_price_isbn_9780571106240/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/twopence_a_tub_by_susan_price_isbn_9780571106240/</guid>
      <description>Twopence a Tub by Susan Price Title: Twopence a Tub Author: Susan Price Review: Twopence a Tub is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Susan Price, which takes readers on a captivating journey through the life of a young boy named Joe. The story is set in the early 1900s and revolves around Joe&amp;rsquo;s family, who work as washerwomen, washing clothes for wealthy people. The book targets children between the ages of 8 to 12 years old, as it contains a perfect blend of adventure, emotion, and historical context.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Girl of the Limberlost</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/a_girl_of_the_limberlost_by_gene_stratton-porter_isbn_9780517072356/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/a_girl_of_the_limberlost_by_gene_stratton-porter_isbn_9780517072356/</guid>
      <description>A Girl of the Limberlost by Gene Stratton-Porter Title: A Girl of the Limberlost Author: Gene Stratton-Porter A Girl of the Limberlost is a beautifully written classic children&amp;rsquo;s book by Gene Stratton-Porter. The story follows the life of a young girl named Elnora Comstock, who lives in the swamps of the Limberlost forest in Indiana. Elnora&amp;rsquo;s mother has passed away, and her father is cold and distant, leaving her to navigate the challenges of life on her own.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Capture the Castle</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/i_capture_the_castle_by_dodie_smith_isbn_8379430069/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/i_capture_the_castle_by_dodie_smith_isbn_8379430069/</guid>
      <description>I Capture the Castle by Dodie Smith Title: I Capture the Castle Author: Dodie Smith Review: I Capture the Castle is a charming and delightful novel that captures the essence of childhood and the complexities of growing up. The story follows the adventures of Cassandra Mortmain, a young girl living in a crumbling castle with her family. As Cassandra navigates the ups and downs of life, she learns valuable lessons about love, friendship, and the importance of staying true to oneself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Children From Number 67</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_children_from_number_67_by_lisa_tetzner_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_children_from_number_67_by_lisa_tetzner_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Children From Number 67 by Lisa Tetzner Title: The Children from Number 67 Author: Lisa Tetzner The Children from Number 67 is a heartwarming and adventurous children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Lisa Tetzner. This book is a perfect read for children aged 8-12 years old. The story revolves around a group of children who live in a boarding house at Number 67. These children come from different backgrounds and face various challenges in their lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Around the World in Eighty Days</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/around_the_world_in_eighty_days_isbn_9780756784652/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/around_the_world_in_eighty_days_isbn_9780756784652/</guid>
      <description>Around the World in Eighty Days Title: Around the World in Eighty Days Author: Jules Verne Age Group: 8-12 years old &amp;ldquo;Around the World in Eighty Days&amp;rdquo; is a thrilling adventure novel written by Jules Verne, which takes readers on a whirlwind journey around the globe. The story follows the determined and punctual Phileas Fogg, who accepts a wager to circumnavigate the world in just 80 days. Accompanied by his loyal French valet, Passepartout, Fogg encounters numerous obstacles and challenges throughout his journey, making for an exciting and engaging read.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Journey to the River Sea</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/journey_to_the_river_sea_by_eva_ibbotson_isbn_9780525467397/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/journey_to_the_river_sea_by_eva_ibbotson_isbn_9780525467397/</guid>
      <description>Journey to the River Sea by Eva Ibbotson Title: Journey to the River Sea Author: Eva Ibbotson Review: Journey to the River Sea is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book by Eva Ibbotson, which takes the reader on a thrilling adventure through the Amazon rainforest. The story follows the life of Maia, an orphan who is sent to live with distant relatives in Brazil. The book is targeted towards children aged 9-12 years old, as it features relatable themes and engaging storytelling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rupert the Rapper and Aunt Deep Freeze</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/rupert_the_rapper_and_aunt_deep_freeze_by_sinikka_and_tiina_nopola_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/rupert_the_rapper_and_aunt_deep_freeze_by_sinikka_and_tiina_nopola_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Rupert the Rapper and Aunt Deep Freeze by Sinikka and Tiina Nopola Title: Rupert the Rapper and Aunt Deep Freeze Author: Sinikka and Tiina Nopola Review: Rupert the Rapper and Aunt Deep Freeze is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young boy named Rupert who discovers his passion for rapping. The book is filled with engaging illustrations and an entertaining storyline that captures the attention of young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Something&#39;s Fishy, Hazel Green!</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/somethings_fishy_hazel_green_by_odo_hirsch_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/somethings_fishy_hazel_green_by_odo_hirsch_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Something&amp;rsquo;s Fishy, Hazel Green! by Odo Hirsch Title: Something&amp;rsquo;s Fishy, Hazel Green! Author: Odo Hirsch Review: &amp;ldquo;Something&amp;rsquo;s Fishy, Hazel Green!&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Odo Hirsch, which takes readers on a captivating journey through the eyes of its protagonist, Hazel Green. The story follows Hazel as she sets out to uncover the mystery behind a peculiar smell that has been plaguing her school. The book is primarily targeted towards children between the ages of 7 to 10 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Graveyard Book</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_graveyard_book_isbn_9780747598626/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_graveyard_book_isbn_9780747598626/</guid>
      <description>The Graveyard Book Title: The Graveyard Book Author: Neil Gaiman Review: The Graveyard Book is a captivating and enchanting novel written by the renowned author Neil Gaiman. This book is a perfect blend of mystery, adventure, and fantasy, making it an ideal read for children aged 8 to 12 years old. The story revolves around the life of a young boy named Nobody Owens, or Bod for short, who is adopted by the ghostly residents of a graveyard after his family is tragically murdered.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Katy Did</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/what_katy_did_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/what_katy_did_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>What Katy Did Title: What Katy Did Author: Susan Coolidge Target Age Group: 8-12 years old &amp;ldquo;What Katy Did&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Susan Coolidge, originally published in 1872. The story revolves around the life of a young girl named Katy Carr and her family. The book has been cherished by generations of readers and continues to be a favorite among children today. The story is set in the 19th century and follows Katy, a lively and adventurous girl who loves to play with her siblings and friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>45 &amp; 47 Stella Street and Everything That Happened</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/45__47_stella_street_and_everything_that_happened_by_elizabeth_honey_isbn_1863738584/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/45__47_stella_street_and_everything_that_happened_by_elizabeth_honey_isbn_1863738584/</guid>
      <description>45 &amp;amp; 47 Stella Street and Everything That Happened by Elizabeth Honey Title: &amp;ldquo;45 &amp;amp; 47 Stella Street and Everything That Happened&amp;rdquo; Author: Elizabeth Honey Review: &amp;ldquo;45 &amp;amp; 47 Stella Street and Everything That Happened&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that captures the essence of childhood friendships, adventures, and the lessons we learn along the way. Elizabeth Honey has crafted a heartwarming story that is sure to resonate with readers of all ages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Am Susannah</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/i_am_susannah_by_libby_gleeson_isbn_082340742x/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/i_am_susannah_by_libby_gleeson_isbn_082340742x/</guid>
      <description>I Am Susannah by Libby Gleeson Title: I Am Susannah Author: Libby Gleeson Target Age Group: 6-10 years old Review: &amp;ldquo;I Am Susannah&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young girl named Susannah, who embarks on a journey of self-discovery and learns the importance of embracing her unique qualities. The book, written by Libby Gleeson, is an engaging and heartwarming tale that is perfect for children between the ages of 6 and 10 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kensuke&#39;s Kingdom</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/kensukes_kingdom_by_michael_morpurgo_isbn_1405267372/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/kensukes_kingdom_by_michael_morpurgo_isbn_1405267372/</guid>
      <description>Kensuke&amp;rsquo;s Kingdom by Michael Morpurgo Title: Kensuke&amp;rsquo;s Kingdom Author: Michael Morpurgo Review: Kensuke&amp;rsquo;s Kingdom is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Michael Morpurgo. The story revolves around a young boy named Michael who embarks on a thrilling adventure with his family. The book is targeted towards children aged 8-12 years old and is a perfect blend of adventure, friendship, and self-discovery. The story begins with Michael and his family setting sail on a yacht to fulfill their dream of exploring the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Only You Can Save Mankind</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/only_you_can_save_mankind_isbn_61376817/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/only_you_can_save_mankind_isbn_61376817/</guid>
      <description>Only You Can Save Mankind Title: Only You Can Save Mankind Author: Terry Pratchett Review: Only You Can Save Mankind is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Terry Pratchett, which takes the reader on a thrilling adventure into the world of virtual reality gaming. The story follows the life of a young boy named Johnny Maxwell, who becomes the leader of a group of aliens known as &amp;ldquo;ScreeWee.&amp;rdquo; As the story unfolds, Johnny and his friends must navigate the complexities of their new virtual world while learning valuable life lessons along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Sterkarm Handshake</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_sterkarm_handshake_by_susan_price_isbn_9781504020992/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_sterkarm_handshake_by_susan_price_isbn_9781504020992/</guid>
      <description>The Sterkarm Handshake by Susan Price Title: The Sterkarm Handshake Author: Susan Price Review: The Sterkarm Handshake is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Susan Price, which takes the readers on an adventurous journey through time. The story revolves around a teenage girl named Allie, who gets transported to the 16th century after touching a mysterious handshake carved on a stone. The book is targeted towards children aged 8-12 years old, as it contains elements of history, fantasy, and adventure that would appeal to this age group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mouth Open, Story Jump Out</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/mouth_open_story_jump_out_by_grace_hallworth_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/mouth_open_story_jump_out_by_grace_hallworth_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Mouth Open, Story Jump Out by Grace Hallworth Title: Mouth Open, Story Jump Out Author: Grace Hallworth &amp;ldquo;Mouth Open, Story Jump Out&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Grace Hallworth, which is perfect for young readers between the ages of 5 and 8. The book is filled with charming illustrations and engaging stories that capture the imagination of its young audience. The book is divided into several short stories, each one featuring a unique character and a valuable life lesson.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ronia the Robber&#39;s Daughter</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/ronia_the_robbers_daughter_isbn_812437233/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/ronia_the_robbers_daughter_isbn_812437233/</guid>
      <description>Ronia the Robber&amp;rsquo;s Daughter Title: Ronia the Robber&amp;rsquo;s Daughter Author: Astrid Lindgren Ronia the Robber&amp;rsquo;s Daughter is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the talented Astrid Lindgren. This story is a perfect blend of adventure, friendship, and fantasy, making it an enjoyable read for children aged 8-12 years old. The book follows the life of Ronia, the daughter of a robber chieftain, who lives in a castle in the forest. She is a curious and fearless girl who loves to explore the woods and spend time with her best friend, Birk, the son of a rival robber chieftain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schoolboy Jia Li</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/schoolboy_jia_li_by_qin_wenjun_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/schoolboy_jia_li_by_qin_wenjun_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Schoolboy Jia Li by Qin Wenjun Title: Schoolboy Jia Li Author: Qin Wenjun Schoolboy Jia Li is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Qin Wenjun, which follows the story of a young boy named Jia Li as he navigates through the ups and downs of school life. This heartwarming tale is perfect for children between the ages of 6 and 10, as it addresses various life lessons and challenges that young readers can relate to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Little Man Dressed in Gray</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_little_man_dressed_in_gray_by_fernando_alonso_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_little_man_dressed_in_gray_by_fernando_alonso_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Little Man Dressed in Gray by Fernando Alonso Title: The Little Man Dressed in Gray Author: Fernando Alonso Review: The Little Man Dressed in Gray is a charming and delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that captures the hearts of young readers with its beautiful illustrations and engaging story. Written by Fernando Alonso, this book is perfect for children aged 4 to 8 years old. The story revolves around a little man dressed in gray who lives in a world of color.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crusade in Jeans</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/crusade_in_jeans_isbn_9781935954071/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/crusade_in_jeans_isbn_9781935954071/</guid>
      <description>Crusade in Jeans Title: Crusade in Jeans Author: Thea Beckman Review: Crusade in Jeans is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young boy named Dolf, who is unexpectedly transported back in time to the Middle Ages. The book, written by Thea Beckman, is an engaging and thought-provoking adventure that is perfect for children aged 10-14. The story is filled with historical details, and it provides an exciting and immersive way for young readers to learn about the past.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Shrinking of Treehorn</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_shrinking_of_treehorn_by_florence_parry_heide_isbn_9780823401895/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_shrinking_of_treehorn_by_florence_parry_heide_isbn_9780823401895/</guid>
      <description>The Shrinking of Treehorn by Florence Parry Heide Title: The Shrinking of Treehorn Author: Florence Parry Heide The Shrinking of Treehorn is a whimsical and thought-provoking children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Florence Parry Heide. The story follows the adventures of Treehorn, a young boy who starts shrinking inexplicably. As he gets smaller and smaller, Treehorn&amp;rsquo;s family and friends fail to notice his predicament, leading to a series of humorous and sometimes perilous situations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fantomette</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/fantomette_by_georges_chaulet_isbn_2010177886/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/fantomette_by_georges_chaulet_isbn_2010177886/</guid>
      <description>Fantomette by Georges Chaulet Title: Fantomette Author: Georges Chaulet Review: Fantomette is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Georges Chaulet that tells the story of a young girl named Fantomette, who is a mysterious superheroine. This book is a perfect read for children between the ages of 7 to 12 years old. The story revolves around Fantomette, who uses her superpowers to help people in need and fight against injustice. Throughout the book, the readers are taken on an exciting adventure filled with action, suspense, and mystery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Graveyard Kitaro</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/graveyard_kitaro_by_shigeru_mizuki_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/graveyard_kitaro_by_shigeru_mizuki_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Graveyard Kitaro by Shigeru Mizuki Title: Graveyard Kitaro Author: Shigeru Mizuki Graveyard Kitaro is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Shigeru Mizuki, which takes the readers on a thrilling adventure filled with supernatural creatures and valuable life lessons. This book is suitable for children between the ages of 8 to 12 years old. The story revolves around Kitaro, a young boy who lives in a graveyard with his ghostly friends. Together, they embark on various adventures, encountering monsters, spirits, and other supernatural beings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stig of the Dump</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/stig_of_the_dump_isbn_754065766/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/stig_of_the_dump_isbn_754065766/</guid>
      <description>Stig of the Dump Title: Stig of the Dump Author: Clive King Target Age Group: 7-12 years old Stig of the Dump is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Clive King, which tells the story of a young boy named Barney who discovers a caveman named Stig living in a nearby dump. The book takes readers on a delightful adventure as Barney and Stig form a unique friendship, teaching valuable life lessons along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Hundred and One Dalmatians</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_hundred_and_one_dalmatians_isbn_9780760704066/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_hundred_and_one_dalmatians_isbn_9780760704066/</guid>
      <description>The Hundred and One Dalmatians Title: The Hundred and One Dalmatians Author: Dodie Smith Review: The Hundred and One Dalmatians is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Dodie Smith, first published in 1956. The story revolves around the lives of 101 Dalmatian puppies, their parents Pongo and Missis, and their human family, the Dearlys. The book is filled with adventure, suspense, and heartwarming moments that make it a delightful read for children of all ages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Little Pot Boiler</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_little_pot_boiler_by_spike_milligan_isbn_9780234777558/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_little_pot_boiler_by_spike_milligan_isbn_9780234777558/</guid>
      <description>The Little Pot Boiler by Spike Milligan Title: The Little Pot Boiler Author: Spike Milligan Review: The Little Pot Boiler is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the talented Spike Milligan. This delightful story is a perfect fit for children between the ages of 5 and 8 years old. The book&amp;rsquo;s engaging illustrations and simple language make it an enjoyable read for young readers. The story revolves around a little pot that dreams of becoming a boiler, just like the big, shiny ones in the factory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Seasons in the City</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_seasons_in_the_city_by_italo_calvino_isbn_151570817/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_seasons_in_the_city_by_italo_calvino_isbn_151570817/</guid>
      <description>The Seasons in the City by Italo Calvino Title: The Seasons in the City Author: Italo Calvino The Seasons in the City is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Italo Calvino. The book is a collection of short stories that take place in a city, each story representing a different season. The stories are beautifully written and engaging, making it a perfect read for children aged 6 to 10 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uncle</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/uncle_by_j.p._martin_isbn_9780099294504/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/uncle_by_j.p._martin_isbn_9780099294504/</guid>
      <description>Uncle by J.P. Martin Title: Uncle Author: J.P. Martin Review: &amp;ldquo;Uncle&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by J.P. Martin, which takes the readers on an exciting adventure in the world of fantasy. The story follows the life of a wealthy, kind-hearted man named Uncle, who lives in a huge, magical house called &amp;ldquo;The Manor.&amp;rdquo; Uncle&amp;rsquo;s house is filled with talking animals, who are his loyal friends and helpers. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 6 and 12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where the Red Fern Grows</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/where_the_red_fern_grows_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/where_the_red_fern_grows_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Where the Red Fern Grows Title: Where the Red Fern Grows Author: Phyllis Reynolds Naylor Review: Where the Red Fern Grows is a heartwarming and adventurous story that follows the life of a young boy named Billy Colman, who dreams of owning two redbone coonhounds to hunt with in the Ozark Mountains. The story is set in the 1930s and beautifully captures the essence of life in a small rural community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Down With Skool</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/down_with_skool_by_geoffrey_willans_isbn_9780141191683/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/down_with_skool_by_geoffrey_willans_isbn_9780141191683/</guid>
      <description>Down With Skool by Geoffrey Willans Title: Down With Skool Author: Geoffrey Willans Review: Down With Skool is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Geoffrey Willans, which takes readers on a humorous journey through the eyes of a young boy named Nigel Molesworth. The book is a collection of short stories and illustrations that capture the essence of life in a British boarding school. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 8 and 12, and is perfect for those who enjoy a good laugh and relatable situations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Little Bookroom</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_little_bookroom_isbn_9780192719478/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_little_bookroom_isbn_9780192719478/</guid>
      <description>The Little Bookroom Title: The Little Bookroom Author: Eleanor Farjeon Illustrator: Edward Ardizzone The Little Bookroom is a charming and delightful collection of short stories that will captivate the hearts of young readers. Eleanor Farjeon, the author, has skillfully woven a tapestry of tales that transport the reader to a world of enchantment and adventure. The book is accompanied by beautiful illustrations by Edward Ardizzone, which add to the overall charm of the stories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Twenty-One Balloons</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_twenty-one_balloons_isbn_670734411/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_twenty-one_balloons_isbn_670734411/</guid>
      <description>The Twenty-One Balloons Title: The Twenty-One Balloons Author: William Pène du Bois The Twenty-One Balloons is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of Professor William Waterman Sherman, who embarks on a journey in a hot air balloon. The book, written by William Pène du Bois, is an exciting adventure that takes readers on a thrilling ride through the skies and to the mysterious and fantastical land of Krakatoa. The story is suitable for children aged 8 to 12 years old, as it contains elements of adventure, humor, and suspense.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Incredible Adventures of Professor Branestawm</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_incredible_adventures_of_professor_branestawm_by_norman_hunter_isbn_9780140351385/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_incredible_adventures_of_professor_branestawm_by_norman_hunter_isbn_9780140351385/</guid>
      <description>The Incredible Adventures of Professor Branestawm by Norman Hunter Title: The Incredible Adventures of Professor Branestawm Author: Norman Hunter Review: The Incredible Adventures of Professor Branestawm is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the hilarious and entertaining adventures of the eccentric inventor, Professor Branestawm. The book is perfect for children aged 7-12, as it contains engaging illustrations and a captivating storyline that will keep young readers entertained for hours. The book covers important life lessons such as the importance of teamwork, perseverance, and creativity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The School at the Chalet</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_school_at_the_chalet_by_elinor_m._brent-dyer_isbn_6903347/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_school_at_the_chalet_by_elinor_m._brent-dyer_isbn_6903347/</guid>
      <description>The School at the Chalet by Elinor M. Brent-Dyer Title: The School at the Chalet Author: Elinor M. Brent-Dyer Review: The School at the Chalet is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Elinor M. Brent-Dyer. The story follows the adventures of Jo Bettany, a young girl who finds herself at a new boarding school in the Swiss Alps called the Chalet School. The book is filled with heartwarming friendships, exciting adventures, and valuable life lessons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Story of Doctor Dolittle</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_story_of_doctor_dolittle_isbn_9798720754471/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_story_of_doctor_dolittle_isbn_9798720754471/</guid>
      <description>The Story of Doctor Dolittle Title: The Story of Doctor Dolittle Author: Hugh Lofting Review: The Story of Doctor Dolittle is a charming and imaginative children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the adventures of a kind-hearted doctor who possesses the extraordinary ability to communicate with animals. This delightful tale, written by Hugh Lofting, is filled with enchanting characters, whimsical situations, and important life lessons that are sure to captivate young readers. The book is targeted at children aged 7 to 10 years old, although readers of all ages can enjoy and appreciate the story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Wind on the Moon</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_wind_on_the_moon_isbn_1590171004/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_wind_on_the_moon_isbn_1590171004/</guid>
      <description>The Wind on the Moon Title: The Wind on the Moon Author: Eric Linklater Recommended Age Group: 8-12 years old The Wind on the Moon is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Eric Linklater, which tells the story of two young sisters, Dinah and Dorinda, who embark on a magical adventure. The book, first published in 1944, has aged remarkably well and continues to captivate young readers with its whimsical tale and valuable life lessons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peter Pan in Kensington Gardens</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/peter_pan_in_kensington_gardens_isbn_9781653813407/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/peter_pan_in_kensington_gardens_isbn_9781653813407/</guid>
      <description>Peter Pan in Kensington Gardens Title: Peter Pan in Kensington Gardens Author: J.M. Barrie Review: Peter Pan in Kensington Gardens is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that captures the essence of childhood innocence and imagination. Written by J.M. Barrie, the author of the classic tale of Peter Pan, this book takes readers on a magical journey through the eyes of Peter Pan as a young boy. The story follows Peter Pan as he explores the enchanted Kensington Gardens, where he encounters various fairies, animals, and other magical creatures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Morality Tales</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/morality_tales_by_rafael_pombo_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/morality_tales_by_rafael_pombo_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Morality Tales by Rafael Pombo Title: Morality Tales Author: Rafael Pombo Review: Morality Tales by Rafael Pombo is a delightful collection of short stories that teach valuable life lessons to young readers. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 6 and 12 years old, making it an excellent choice for elementary school students. The stories in Morality Tales are engaging and thought-provoking, covering a wide range of topics such as honesty, kindness, and perseverance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zen Shorts</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/zen_shorts_isbn_9780545040877/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/zen_shorts_isbn_9780545040877/</guid>
      <description>Zen Shorts Title: Zen Shorts Author: Jon J. Muth Target Age Group: 5-10 years old &amp;ldquo;Zen Shorts&amp;rdquo; is a beautifully illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book that captures the essence of mindfulness and the importance of finding inner peace. Author Jon J. Muth has skillfully crafted a story that is both engaging and educational for young readers. The book follows the story of three siblings, Michael, Karl, and Addy, who meet a wise and mysterious panda named Stillwater.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are We There Yet?</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/are_we_there_yet_by_alison_lester_isbn_670880671/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/are_we_there_yet_by_alison_lester_isbn_670880671/</guid>
      <description>Are We There Yet? by Alison Lester Title: Are We There Yet? Author: Alison Lester Review: Are We There Yet? is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Alison Lester, which takes young readers on an exciting journey across Australia. The story follows Grace and her family as they embark on a road trip from their home in Melbourne to visit relatives in far-off Western Australia. The book is filled with vibrant illustrations and engaging storytelling, making it a perfect choice for children between the ages of 4 and 8.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beegu</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/beegu_by_alexis_deacon_isbn_9780091768294/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/beegu_by_alexis_deacon_isbn_9780091768294/</guid>
      <description>Beegu by Alexis Deacon Title: Beegu Author: Alexis Deacon Beegu is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written and illustrated by Alexis Deacon. The story follows the adventures of Beegu, an adorable, lovable, and friendly alien who becomes stranded on Earth. As Beegu encounters various animals and people, she struggles to find a way back to her home planet. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 4 to 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Will Not Ever Never Eat a Tomato</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/i_will_not_ever_never_eat_a_tomato_by_lauren_child_isbn_9780763611880/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/i_will_not_ever_never_eat_a_tomato_by_lauren_child_isbn_9780763611880/</guid>
      <description>I Will Not Ever Never Eat a Tomato by Lauren Child Title: I Will Not Ever Never Eat a Tomato Author: Lauren Child Review: &amp;ldquo;I Will Not Ever Never Eat a Tomato&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Lauren Child, targeting young readers between the ages of 4 to 8 years old. The story revolves around a young girl named Lola, who is very particular about her food choices and refuses to eat anything that is not her favorite.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>That Pesky Rat</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/that_pesky_rat_by_lauren_child_isbn_1484423003/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/that_pesky_rat_by_lauren_child_isbn_1484423003/</guid>
      <description>That Pesky Rat by Lauren Child Title: &amp;ldquo;That Pesky Rat&amp;rdquo; Author: Lauren Child Review: &amp;ldquo;That Pesky Rat&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the talented Lauren Child. The story follows the adventures of a pesky rat who finds himself in a variety of amusing situations. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old, as it contains simple yet engaging language and colorful illustrations that will capture the young readers&amp;rsquo; attention.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Biggest Kiss in the World</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_biggest_kiss_in_the_world_by_r_chavez_castaneda_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_biggest_kiss_in_the_world_by_r_chavez_castaneda_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Biggest Kiss in the World by R Chavez Castaneda Title: The Biggest Kiss in the World Author: R. Chavez Castaneda Review: The Biggest Kiss in the World is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes young readers on a heartwarming journey through the world of animals. The story follows a mother elephant who, upon hearing about the biggest kiss in the world, sets out on a quest to find it. Along the way, she encounters various animals, each with their own unique interpretation of what the biggest kiss could be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Day the Babies Crawled Away</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_day_the_babies_crawled_away_by_peggy_rathman_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_day_the_babies_crawled_away_by_peggy_rathman_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Day the Babies Crawled Away by Peggy Rathman Title: The Day the Babies Crawled Away Author: Peggy Rathman Genre: Children&amp;rsquo;s Fiction, Picture Book Recommended Age Group: 4-8 years old The Day the Babies Crawled Away is a delightful and engaging children&amp;rsquo;s book written and illustrated by Peggy Rathman. This book tells the story of a group of babies who decide to crawl away from their families and embark on a grand adventure together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Death Book</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_death_book_by_pernilla_stalfelt_isbn_888994826/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_death_book_by_pernilla_stalfelt_isbn_888994826/</guid>
      <description>The Death Book by Pernilla Stalfelt Title: The Death Book Author: Pernilla Stalfelt The Death Book, written by Pernilla Stalfelt, is a beautifully illustrated and thoughtfully written children&amp;rsquo;s book that addresses the sensitive topic of death in a manner that is both age-appropriate and comforting. The book targets children between the ages of 4 and 8, making it an excellent choice for parents, educators, and caregivers looking to initiate conversations about this important subject with young children.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Love Book</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_love_book_by_pernilla_stalfelt_isbn_888994559/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_love_book_by_pernilla_stalfelt_isbn_888994559/</guid>
      <description>The Love Book by Pernilla Stalfelt Title: The Love Book Author: Pernilla Stalfelt Review: The Love Book by Pernilla Stalfelt is a heartwarming and visually stunning children&amp;rsquo;s book that beautifully captures the essence of love and kindness. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 4 to 8 years old and is a perfect addition to any child&amp;rsquo;s library. The Love Book is a vibrant and imaginative exploration of love, showcasing the many ways love can be expressed and experienced.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Three Pigs</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_three_pigs_isbn_9780844208732/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_three_pigs_isbn_9780844208732/</guid>
      <description>The Three Pigs Title: The Three Pigs Age Group: 4-8 years old The Three Pigs is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that retells the classic story of three pigs and their encounters with the big, bad wolf. This timeless tale is perfect for children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old, as it teaches valuable life lessons while being entertaining and engaging. The book features beautiful illustrations that bring the story to life, making it an enjoyable read for both children and parents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You&#39;re All My Favourites</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/youre_all_my_favourites_by_sam_mcbratney_isbn_744570298/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/youre_all_my_favourites_by_sam_mcbratney_isbn_744570298/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;re All My Favourites by Sam McBratney Title: You&amp;rsquo;re All My Favourites Author: Sam McBratney Illustrator: Anita Jeram Age Group: 4-8 years old &amp;ldquo;You&amp;rsquo;re All My Favourites&amp;rdquo; is a heartwarming and beautifully illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a family of bears - Mama Bear, Papa Bear, and their three little bear cubs. The book is written by Sam McBratney, who is known for his engaging and touching stories, and is brought to life by the charming illustrations of Anita Jeram.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Friends From the Other Side</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/friends_from_the_other_side_by_gloria_anzaldua_isbn_9780892391134/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/friends_from_the_other_side_by_gloria_anzaldua_isbn_9780892391134/</guid>
      <description>Friends From the Other Side by Gloria Anzaldua Title: Friends From the Other Side Author: Gloria Anzaldua Review: &amp;ldquo;Friends From the Other Side&amp;rdquo; is a beautifully written and illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young girl named Marisol, who lives near the U.S.-Mexico border. The book explores themes of friendship, empathy, and understanding, as Marisol befriends a group of children from the other side of the border. The story is engaging and age-appropriate for children between the ages of 6 and 10 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jennifer Jones Won&#39;t Leave Me Alone</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/jennifer_jones_wont_leave_me_alone_by_frieda_wishinsky_isbn_9780876149218/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/jennifer_jones_wont_leave_me_alone_by_frieda_wishinsky_isbn_9780876149218/</guid>
      <description>Jennifer Jones Won&amp;rsquo;t Leave Me Alone by Frieda Wishinsky Title: Jennifer Jones Won&amp;rsquo;t Leave Me Alone Author: Frieda Wishinsky Review: &amp;ldquo;Jennifer Jones Won&amp;rsquo;t Leave Me Alone&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tackles the relatable theme of dealing with a bothersome classmate. Author Frieda Wishinsky has created a story that will resonate with young readers, as they follow the protagonist&amp;rsquo;s journey to find a solution to his problem. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 8 and 12.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lon Po Po</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/lon_po_po_isbn_9780399216190/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/lon_po_po_isbn_9780399216190/</guid>
      <description>Lon Po Po Title: Lon Po Po: A Red-Riding Hood Story from China Author: Ed Young Lon Po Po is a beautifully illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young girl named Little Red Riding Hood, but with a Chinese twist. The story is set in a Chinese village, and the characters and setting are infused with traditional Chinese elements, making it a unique and culturally rich experience for young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Place</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/my_place_by_nadia_wheatley_isbn_9780916291426/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/my_place_by_nadia_wheatley_isbn_9780916291426/</guid>
      <description>My Place by Nadia Wheatley Title: My Place Author: Nadia Wheatley Review: &amp;ldquo;My Place&amp;rdquo; is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Nadia Wheatley, which takes readers on a journey through time and place. The story follows the lives of various children who live in the same location but at different points in history, starting from 1888 and ending in 1988. The book is targeted towards children aged 8-12 years old, as it provides an engaging and educational experience for young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oh, the Places You&#39;ll Go</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/oh_the_places_youll_go_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/oh_the_places_youll_go_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Oh, the Places You&amp;rsquo;ll Go Title: Oh, the Places You&amp;rsquo;ll Go Author: Dr. Seuss Review: Oh, the Places You&amp;rsquo;ll Go is a delightful and inspiring children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the beloved author Dr. Seuss. This book is perfect for children aged 4 to 8 years old, as it captures their imagination and teaches valuable life lessons in a fun and engaging way. The story follows the journey of a young character as they navigate through the ups and downs of life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Little Bird</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_little_bird_by_paro_anand_isbn_817223077x/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_little_bird_by_paro_anand_isbn_817223077x/</guid>
      <description>The Little Bird by Paro Anand Title: The Little Bird Author: Paro Anand The Little Bird is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Paro Anand, which tells the story of a young bird who embarks on a journey of self-discovery and learns valuable life lessons along the way. This beautifully illustrated book is perfect for children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old. The story revolves around a little bird who is curious about the world around her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Stinky Cheese Man and Other Fairly Stupid Tales</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_stinky_cheese_man_and_other_fairly_stupid_tales_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_stinky_cheese_man_and_other_fairly_stupid_tales_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Stinky Cheese Man and Other Fairly Stupid Tales Title: The Stinky Cheese Man and Other Fairly Stupid Tales Author: Jon Scieszka and Lane Smith Genre: Children&amp;rsquo;s Humor Recommended Age Group: 7-12 years old The Stinky Cheese Man and Other Fairly Stupid Tales is a hilarious and cleverly written children&amp;rsquo;s book that offers a fresh twist on classic fairy tales. The book is filled with witty humor and captivating illustrations that will keep young readers engaged from start to finish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alexander and the Terrible, Horrible, No Good, Very Bad Day</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/alexander_and_the_terrible_horrible_no_good_very_bad_day_by_judith_viorst/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/alexander_and_the_terrible_horrible_no_good_very_bad_day_by_judith_viorst/</guid>
      <description>Alexander and the Terrible, Horrible, No Good, Very Bad Day by Judith Viorst Title: Alexander and the Terrible, Horrible, No Good, Very Bad Day Author: Judith Viorst Illustrator: Ray Cruz Target Age Group: 4-8 years old Alexander and the Terrible, Horrible, No Good, Very Bad Day is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young boy named Alexander who is having the worst day ever. The book, written by Judith Viorst and illustrated by Ray Cruz, is a perfect read for children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Figgie Hobbin</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/figgie_hobbin_by_charles_causley_isbn_9780330400008/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/figgie_hobbin_by_charles_causley_isbn_9780330400008/</guid>
      <description>Figgie Hobbin by Charles Causley Title: Figgie Hobbin Author: Charles Causley Review: Figgie Hobbin is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the talented Charles Causley. This book is perfect for children between the ages of 6 and 10 years old, as it contains engaging and imaginative stories that will capture their attention and spark their curiosity. The book follows the adventures of Figgie Hobbin, a young boy who embarks on various exciting journeys and encounters interesting characters along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fungus the Bogeyman</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/fungus_the_bogeyman_by_raymond_briggs_isbn_9780394738208/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/fungus_the_bogeyman_by_raymond_briggs_isbn_9780394738208/</guid>
      <description>Fungus the Bogeyman by Raymond Briggs Title: Fungus the Bogeyman Author: Raymond Briggs &amp;ldquo;Fungus the Bogeyman&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the talented author and illustrator, Raymond Briggs. This book is perfect for children aged 7-10 years old and provides an engaging and humorous insight into the life of a bogeyman. The story follows Fungus, a bogeyman who lives underground with his family, and their daily lives filled with slime, mud, and other unmentionable things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not Now, Bernard</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/not_now_bernard_by_david_mckee_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/not_now_bernard_by_david_mckee_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Not Now, Bernard by David McKee Title: Not Now, Bernard Author: David McKee &amp;ldquo;Not Now, Bernard&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written and illustrated by David McKee. This book is a perfect read for children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old. The story follows a young boy named Bernard who is constantly ignored by his parents, and one day, he encounters a monster in his backyard. The book tackles themes such as family relationships, the importance of listening, and the consequences of neglect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Jolly Postman</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_jolly_postman_by_allan_ahlberg_isbn_9788423332328/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_jolly_postman_by_allan_ahlberg_isbn_9788423332328/</guid>
      <description>The Jolly Postman by Allan Ahlberg Title: The Jolly Postman Author: Allan Ahlberg Review: The Jolly Postman is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Allan Ahlberg and beautifully illustrated by Janet Ahlberg. This interactive story follows the adventures of a cheerful postman as he delivers letters to various classic fairy tale characters. The book is designed for children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old, and it offers a unique reading experience that combines storytelling with interactive elements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The New Kid on the Block</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_new_kid_on_the_block_by_jack_prelutsky_isbn_807201154/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_new_kid_on_the_block_by_jack_prelutsky_isbn_807201154/</guid>
      <description>The New Kid on the Block by Jack Prelutsky Title: The New Kid on the Block Author: Jack Prelutsky The New Kid on the Block is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Jack Prelutsky, which tells the story of a young boy who moves to a new neighborhood and struggles to make friends. This book is perfect for children aged 6 to 10 years old, as it teaches valuable life lessons about friendship, acceptance, and overcoming shyness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two Little Bears</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/two_little_bears_by_hanna_muschg_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/two_little_bears_by_hanna_muschg_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Two Little Bears by Hanna Muschg Title: Two Little Bears Author: Hanna Muschg Review: Two Little Bears is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Hanna Muschg, which tells the story of two young bears, Tina and Tom, who embark on a series of adventures in the forest. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 4 to 8 years old and is a perfect blend of fun, adventure, and valuable life lessons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Lion in the Meadow</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/a_lion_in_the_meadow_by_margaret_mahy_isbn_9780460061742/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/a_lion_in_the_meadow_by_margaret_mahy_isbn_9780460061742/</guid>
      <description>A Lion in the Meadow by Margaret Mahy Title: A Lion in the Meadow Author: Margaret Mahy Review: A Lion in the Meadow is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Margaret Mahy, which tells the story of a young boy named Timothy who has a vivid imagination. The book is perfect for children aged 4 to 8 years old, as it teaches valuable life lessons through a captivating and engaging narrative.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Nest</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/best_nest_by_pd_eastman_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/best_nest_by_pd_eastman_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Best Nest by PD Eastman Title: Best Nest Author: P.D. Eastman &amp;ldquo;Best Nest&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by P.D. Eastman, which follows the story of a bird named Peter who is on a quest to find the perfect nest. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 3 to 7 years old, as it features simple and engaging illustrations, as well as easy-to-understand language. The story begins with Peter&amp;rsquo;s dissatisfaction with his current nest, which he deems too small and uncomfortable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Captain Pugwash</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/captain_pugwash_by_john_ryan_isbn_859680169/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/captain_pugwash_by_john_ryan_isbn_859680169/</guid>
      <description>Captain Pugwash by John Ryan Title: Captain Pugwash Author: John Ryan Review: Captain Pugwash is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes readers on a thrilling adventure with its lovable characters and engaging storyline. The book, written by John Ryan, is an ideal read for children between the ages of 5 and 10 years old. The story revolves around the charming Captain Pugwash, a pirate captain, and his trusty crew as they embark on a treasure hunt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crictor</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/crictor_by_tomi_ungerer_isbn_2211071295/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/crictor_by_tomi_ungerer_isbn_2211071295/</guid>
      <description>Crictor by Tomi Ungerer Title: Crictor Author: Tomi Ungerer Crictor is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Tomi Ungerer, which tells the story of a charming and friendly boa constrictor named Crictor. This book is a perfect read for children between the ages of 4 to 8 years old, as it contains beautiful illustrations and a simple yet engaging storyline. The story revolves around Crictor, who lives in a small village and is loved by everyone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gumdrop</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/gumdrop_by_val_biro_isbn_340714492/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/gumdrop_by_val_biro_isbn_340714492/</guid>
      <description>Gumdrop by Val Biro Title: Gumdrop Author: Val Biro Gumdrop, written by Val Biro, is a charming and engaging children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the adventures of a little car named Gumdrop. The story is perfect for children between the ages of 4 and 8, as it is filled with colorful illustrations and simple language that young readers can easily understand and enjoy. The book&amp;rsquo;s main character, Gumdrop, is a friendly and curious little car who loves to explore the world around him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Italian Folktales</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/italian_folktales_isbn_9780814317907/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/italian_folktales_isbn_9780814317907/</guid>
      <description>Italian Folktales Title: Italian Folktales Author: Italo Calvino Review: Italian Folktales is a delightful collection of stories by Italo Calvino, an Italian journalist and writer, who has beautifully captured the essence of traditional Italian folklore. The book is a perfect blend of enchanting tales, colorful illustrations, and timeless life lessons, making it an ideal choice for children between the ages of 6 to 12 years. The book consists of 200 stories, each one more fascinating than the other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little Nicholas</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/little_nicholas_by_rene_goscinny_isbn_9780374312756/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/little_nicholas_by_rene_goscinny_isbn_9780374312756/</guid>
      <description>Little Nicholas by Rene Goscinny Title: Little Nicholas Author: Rene Goscinny Review: Little Nicholas is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the adventures of a young boy named Nicholas and his friends. The book is written by Rene Goscinny, who is well-known for his engaging storytelling and humor. The story is relatable and entertaining for children, making it a perfect read for elementary school students. The book targets children between the ages of 6 and 12, as it explores themes of friendship, honesty, and teamwork.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Bears on Hemlock Mountain</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_bears_on_hemlock_mountain_by_alice_dalgliesh_isbn_9780684191690/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_bears_on_hemlock_mountain_by_alice_dalgliesh_isbn_9780684191690/</guid>
      <description>The Bears on Hemlock Mountain by Alice Dalgliesh Title: The Bears on Hemlock Mountain Author: Alice Dalgliesh Illustrator: Helen Sewell The Bears on Hemlock Mountain is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Alice Dalgliesh and illustrated by Helen Sewell. This story, first published in 1952, has been a favorite of many young readers for generations. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old. The story follows Jonathan, a young boy who lives near Hemlock Mountain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ameliaranne and the Green Umbrella</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/ameliaranne_and_the_green_umbrella_by_constance_heward_isbn_245551042/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/ameliaranne_and_the_green_umbrella_by_constance_heward_isbn_245551042/</guid>
      <description>Ameliaranne and the Green Umbrella by Constance Heward Title: Ameliaranne and the Green Umbrella Author: Constance Heward Ameliaranne and the Green Umbrella is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the adventures of a young girl named Ameliaranne and her magical green umbrella. The story takes place in a whimsical world where anything is possible, and Ameliaranne learns valuable life lessons along the way. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 6 and 10 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Doll&#39;s House</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_dolls_house_by_rumer_godden_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_dolls_house_by_rumer_godden_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Doll&amp;rsquo;s House by Rumer Godden Title: The Doll&amp;rsquo;s House Author: Rumer Godden The Doll&amp;rsquo;s House, written by Rumer Godden, is a charming and enchanting children&amp;rsquo;s book that captures the essence of childhood imagination and the importance of friendship. The story revolves around two young sisters, Tottie and Emily, who receive a beautiful dollhouse as a gift. The dollhouse becomes a magical world where the dolls come to life and experience their own adventures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crispin</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/crispin_by_ted_dewan_isbn_9780606305556/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/crispin_by_ted_dewan_isbn_9780606305556/</guid>
      <description>Crispin by Ted Dewan Title: Crispin Author: Ted Dewan Crispin is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Ted Dewan, which tells the story of a young boy named Crispin and his adventures in a magical world. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 5 and 8 years old, and it beautifully covers essential life lessons that are crucial for young readers. The story revolves around Crispin, a curious and imaginative boy who embarks on a journey to find his missing toy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t Let the Pigeon Drive the Bus!</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/dont_let_the_pigeon_drive_the_bus_isbn_9780439686174/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/dont_let_the_pigeon_drive_the_bus_isbn_9780439686174/</guid>
      <description>Don&amp;rsquo;t Let the Pigeon Drive the Bus! Title: Don&amp;rsquo;t Let the Pigeon Drive the Bus! Author: Mo Willems Review: Don&amp;rsquo;t Let the Pigeon Drive the Bus! is a delightful and entertaining children&amp;rsquo;s book that is perfect for young readers between the ages of 3 and 8. The story follows a mischievous pigeon who is desperate to drive a bus, but the reader is tasked with preventing this from happening. The book is filled with vibrant and engaging illustrations that will capture the attention of young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lost and Found</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/lost_and_found_by_oliver_jeffers_isbn_7240376/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/lost_and_found_by_oliver_jeffers_isbn_7240376/</guid>
      <description>Lost and Found by Oliver Jeffers Title: Lost and Found Author: Oliver Jeffers Review: Lost and Found, written and illustrated by Oliver Jeffers, is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young boy who finds a lost penguin at his doorstep. The boy embarks on a journey to return the penguin to its home in the South Pole. This beautifully illustrated book is suitable for children aged 4-8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Max and Moritz</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/max_and_moritz_by_heinrich_christian_wilhelm_busch_isbn_9781095977651/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/max_and_moritz_by_heinrich_christian_wilhelm_busch_isbn_9781095977651/</guid>
      <description>Max and Moritz by Heinrich Christian Wilhelm Busch Title: Max and Moritz Author: Heinrich Christian Wilhelm Busch Max and Moritz is a classic children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Heinrich Christian Wilhelm Busch, first published in 1865. The book tells the story of two mischievous boys, Max and Moritz, who engage in a series of pranks that lead to disastrous consequences. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 6 and 12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tatu and Patu in Helsinki</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/tatu_and_patu_in_helsinki_by_aino_havukainen_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/tatu_and_patu_in_helsinki_by_aino_havukainen_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Tatu and Patu in Helsinki by Aino Havukainen Title: Tatu and Patu in Helsinki Author: Aino Havukainen Review: Tatu and Patu in Helsinki is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes readers on a fun-filled adventure through the city of Helsinki with two lovable characters, Tatu and Patu. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 4 and 8, and is perfect for sparking their curiosity and interest in exploring new places.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Garden of Little Creatures</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/garden_of_little_creatures_by_antoon_krings_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/garden_of_little_creatures_by_antoon_krings_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Garden of Little Creatures by Antoon Krings Title: Garden of Little Creatures Author: Antoon Krings Review: Garden of Little Creatures is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes readers on a whimsical journey through a magical garden filled with enchanting creatures. Author Antoon Krings has beautifully crafted a story that not only entertains but also teaches valuable life lessons to young readers. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crocodile Beat</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/crocodile_beat_by_gail_jorgensen_isbn_689718810/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/crocodile_beat_by_gail_jorgensen_isbn_689718810/</guid>
      <description>Crocodile Beat by Gail Jorgensen Title: Crocodile Beat Author: Gail Jorgensen Crocodile Beat is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Gail Jorgensen, which takes the reader on an adventurous journey into the world of a young crocodile named Croc. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 4 to 8 years old and is filled with vibrant illustrations that capture the imagination of young readers. The story follows Croc as he learns to play the drums and eventually forms a band with his animal friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fire-Engine Lil</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/fire-engine_lil_by_janet_mclean_andrew_mclean_isbn_9780048200358/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/fire-engine_lil_by_janet_mclean_andrew_mclean_isbn_9780048200358/</guid>
      <description>Fire-Engine Lil by Janet McLean, Andrew McLean Title: Fire-Engine Lil Author: Janet McLean, Andrew McLean Review: Fire-Engine Lil is a charming and delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young girl named Lil, who dreams of becoming a firefighter. The book is beautifully illustrated with vibrant colors and engaging images that capture the imagination of young readers. The target age group for this book is 4 to 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slinky Malinki</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/slinky_malinki_by_lynley_dodd_isbn_9780907349747/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/slinky_malinki_by_lynley_dodd_isbn_9780907349747/</guid>
      <description>Slinky Malinki by Lynley Dodd Title: Slinky Malinki Author: Lynley Dodd Review: Slinky Malinki is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Lynley Dodd, which follows the adventures of a mischievous cat named Slinky Malinki. The story is engaging and fun, making it a perfect read for children between the ages of 3 to 7 years old. The book&amp;rsquo;s illustrations are vibrant and captivating, which adds to the overall charm of the story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Felix and Alexander</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/felix_and_alexander_by_terry_denton_isbn_019554658x/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/felix_and_alexander_by_terry_denton_isbn_019554658x/</guid>
      <description>Felix and Alexander by Terry Denton Title: Felix and Alexander Author: Terry Denton Target Age Group: 5-8 years old Felix and Alexander is a heartwarming and entertaining children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Terry Denton. The story revolves around two best friends, Felix the cat and Alexander the dog, who live together in a small house. Throughout the book, they go on adventures, learn new things, and support each other in times of need.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Green Eggs and Ham</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/green_eggs_and_ham_isbn_1717952/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/green_eggs_and_ham_isbn_1717952/</guid>
      <description>Green Eggs and Ham Title: Green Eggs and Ham Author: Dr. Seuss Review: Green Eggs and Ham is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the renowned author Dr. Seuss. This book is a classic and has been enjoyed by children for generations. The story follows the adventures of Sam-I-Am, who tries to convince an unnamed character to try green eggs and ham. The unnamed character is initially hesitant, but eventually gives in and ends up enjoying the dish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little Blue and Little Yellow</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/little_blue_and_little_yellow_by_leo_lionni_isbn_9780340035764/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/little_blue_and_little_yellow_by_leo_lionni_isbn_9780340035764/</guid>
      <description>Little Blue and Little Yellow by Leo Lionni Title: Little Blue and Little Yellow Author: Leo Lionni Review: Little Blue and Little Yellow is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written and illustrated by Leo Lionni. The story follows the adventures of two friends, Little Blue and Little Yellow, who are both colors. Throughout the book, they learn about the importance of friendship, acceptance, and embracing change. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 4 to 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lyle, Lyle Crocodile</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/lyle_lyle_crocodile_by_bernard_waber_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/lyle_lyle_crocodile_by_bernard_waber_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Lyle, Lyle Crocodile by Bernard Waber Title: Lyle, Lyle Crocodile Author: Bernard Waber Review: Lyle, Lyle Crocodile is a charming and delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Bernard Waber. The story revolves around a friendly crocodile named Lyle, who lives in a house on East 88th Street in New York City with the Primm family. Lyle loves to sing and perform, and he becomes a beloved member of the community. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Cat in the Hat</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_cat_in_the_hat_by_dr._seuss_isbn_000820151x/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_cat_in_the_hat_by_dr._seuss_isbn_000820151x/</guid>
      <description>The Cat in the Hat by Dr. Seuss Title: The Cat in the Hat Author: Dr. Seuss Review: The Cat in the Hat is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the renowned author Dr. Seuss. The story follows the adventures of a mischievous cat who visits two children, Sally and her brother, on a rainy day. The Cat in the Hat teaches valuable life lessons while keeping the reader entertained with its whimsical rhymes and colorful illustrations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fly, Little Bird</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/fly_little_bird_by_francesco_tullio_altan_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/fly_little_bird_by_francesco_tullio_altan_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Fly, Little Bird by Francesco Tullio Altan Title: Fly, Little Bird Author: Francesco Tullio Altan Fly, Little Bird is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book by Francesco Tullio Altan that tells the story of a young bird who dreams of flying high and exploring the world. The book is perfect for children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old, as it is filled with colorful illustrations and simple, yet engaging language.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kipper</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/kipper_by_mick_inkpen_isbn_152022945/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/kipper_by_mick_inkpen_isbn_152022945/</guid>
      <description>Kipper by Mick Inkpen Title: Kipper Author: Mick Inkpen Review: Kipper, written by Mick Inkpen, is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the adventures of a lovable and curious dog named Kipper. The book is filled with vibrant illustrations that capture the attention of young readers and engage their imagination. The story is suitable for children aged 4 to 8 years old, as it teaches important life lessons in a fun and engaging manner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little Brown Bear</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/little_brown_bear_by_claude_lebrun_isbn_9780516078205/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/little_brown_bear_by_claude_lebrun_isbn_9780516078205/</guid>
      <description>Little Brown Bear by Claude Lebrun Title: Little Brown Bear Author: Claude Lebrun Little Brown Bear is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Claude Lebrun, which tells the story of a young bear who goes on an adventure to find a new home. This book is perfect for children aged 4 to 8 years old, as it is filled with colorful illustrations and simple yet engaging language. The story follows Little Brown Bear as he leaves his familiar forest to explore the world around him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Madeline</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/madeline_isbn_9863380156/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/madeline_isbn_9863380156/</guid>
      <description>Madeline Title: Madeline Author: Ludwig Bemelmans Madeline is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the adventures of a young girl named Madeline, who lives in a boarding school in Paris. The story, written by Ludwig Bemelmans, is a timeless classic that has been cherished by generations of children and adults alike. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 4 and 8, making it an excellent choice for early readers or as a bedtime story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Quangle Wangle&#39;s Hat</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_quangle_wangles_hat_by_edward_lear_isbn_9780749713362/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_quangle_wangles_hat_by_edward_lear_isbn_9780749713362/</guid>
      <description>The Quangle Wangle&amp;rsquo;s Hat by Edward Lear Title: The Quangle Wangle&amp;rsquo;s Hat Author: Edward Lear &amp;ldquo;The Quangle Wangle&amp;rsquo;s Hat&amp;rdquo; is a whimsical and imaginative children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Edward Lear, an English artist, illustrator, and writer. This book is a delightful read for children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old. The story follows the adventures of the Quangle Wangle, a curious and friendly creature, who wears a tall, elaborate hat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Story of Babar</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_story_of_babar_by_jean_de_brunhoff_isbn_590757482/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_story_of_babar_by_jean_de_brunhoff_isbn_590757482/</guid>
      <description>The Story of Babar by Jean De Brunhoff Title: The Story of Babar Author: Jean De Brunhoff Review: The Story of Babar, written and illustrated by Jean De Brunhoff, is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that has captured the hearts of readers for generations. Originally published in 1931, this timeless classic tells the story of a young elephant named Babar who embarks on a series of adventures after losing his mother to hunters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tickle, Tickle</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/tickle_tickle_by_helen_oxenbury_isbn_9789991112909/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/tickle_tickle_by_helen_oxenbury_isbn_9789991112909/</guid>
      <description>Tickle, Tickle by Helen Oxenbury Title: Tickle, Tickle Author: Helen Oxenbury Review: Tickle, Tickle is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written and illustrated by the talented Helen Oxenbury. The book is designed for young readers between the ages of 2 to 5 years old. The story follows a group of adorable animals as they play and explore their world. The illustrations in Tickle, Tickle are vibrant and engaging, capturing the attention of young readers with their bright colors and playful designs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We&#39;re Going on a Bear Hunt</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/were_going_on_a_bear_hunt_isbn_9781844280841/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/were_going_on_a_bear_hunt_isbn_9781844280841/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re Going on a Bear Hunt Title: We&amp;rsquo;re Going on a Bear Hunt Author: Michael Rosen Illustrator: Helen Oxenbury Recommended Age Group: 3-8 years old We&amp;rsquo;re Going on a Bear Hunt is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Michael Rosen and illustrated by Helen Oxenbury. The story follows a family on a thrilling adventure as they go on a bear hunt. The book is a perfect blend of engaging illustrations and a captivating narrative that captures the attention of young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
