<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Childrens Books that talk about &#39;Focus&#39; on Monsty The Monster Truck</title>
    <link>https://www.monsty.co/tags/childrens-books-that-talk-about-focus/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Childrens Books that talk about &#39;Focus&#39; on Monsty The Monster Truck</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.monsty.co/tags/childrens-books-that-talk-about-focus/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Arthur</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/arthur_by_kevin_crossley-holland_isbn_1842551558/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/arthur_by_kevin_crossley-holland_isbn_1842551558/</guid>
      <description>Arthur by Kevin Crossley-Holland Title: Arthur Author: Kevin Crossley-Holland Review: Arthur is a charming and engaging children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Kevin Crossley-Holland. The story follows a young boy named Arthur who embarks on a thrilling adventure to save his village from a fire-breathing dragon. The book is beautifully illustrated and has a captivating narrative that keeps the readers engaged from start to finish. The target age group for this book is 5 to 9 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finding Violet Park</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/finding_violet_park_by_jenny_valentine_isbn_7291248/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/finding_violet_park_by_jenny_valentine_isbn_7291248/</guid>
      <description>Finding Violet Park by Jenny Valentine Title: Finding Violet Park Author: Jenny Valentine Review: Finding Violet Park is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Jenny Valentine, which tells the story of a young boy named Lucas who embarks on a journey to find the mysterious Violet Park. The book is suitable for children aged 8-12 years old, as it contains elements of adventure, mystery, and self-discovery. The story follows Lucas as he navigates through various challenges and obstacles in his quest to find Violet Park.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Private Peaceful</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/private_peaceful_isbn_786289465/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/private_peaceful_isbn_786289465/</guid>
      <description>Private Peaceful Title: Private Peaceful Author: Michael Morpurgo Age Group: 9-12 years old Private Peaceful is a heart-warming and poignant children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Michael Morpurgo. The story follows the life of a young boy named Thomas &amp;ldquo;Tommo&amp;rdquo; Peaceful, who grows up in a loving family in a small village during the early 1900s. As the narrative unfolds, we witness the challenges and experiences that shape Tommo&amp;rsquo;s life, including the tragic events of World War I.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stony Heart Country</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/stony_heart_country_by_david_metzenthen_isbn_140279083/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/stony_heart_country_by_david_metzenthen_isbn_140279083/</guid>
      <description>Stony Heart Country by David Metzenthen Title: Stony Heart Country Author: David Metzenthen Review: Stony Heart Country is a beautifully written children&amp;rsquo;s book by David Metzenthen that captures the essence of Australian history and culture. The story follows the life of a young boy named Henry who lives in a small country town during the 1930s. The book is targeted towards children aged 8-12 years old and offers valuable life lessons about friendship, resilience, and the importance of family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When the World Was Still Young</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/when_the_world_was_still_young_by_jurg_schubiger_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/when_the_world_was_still_young_by_jurg_schubiger_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>When the World Was Still Young by Jurg Schubiger Title: When the World Was Still Young Author: Jurg Schubiger Review: When the World Was Still Young is a beautifully illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young boy named Jonas who embarks on a magical adventure. The book is suitable for children between the ages of 6 and 10 years old. The story follows Jonas as he discovers a hidden door in his grandfather&amp;rsquo;s attic, which leads him to a world where time has stopped.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Parcel of Patterns</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/a_parcel_of_patterns_by_jill_paton_walsh_isbn_722658982/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/a_parcel_of_patterns_by_jill_paton_walsh_isbn_722658982/</guid>
      <description>A Parcel of Patterns by Jill Paton Walsh Title: A Parcel of Patterns Author: Jill Paton Walsh A Parcel of Patterns is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book by Jill Paton Walsh, set in the 17th century during the time of the Great Plague. The story revolves around a young girl named Matilda, who lives in the village of Eyam. When the plague strikes, Matilda&amp;rsquo;s life takes a dramatic turn, and she must learn to cope with the challenges that come her way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Friedrich</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/friedrich_by_hans-peter_richter_isbn_9782010141591/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/friedrich_by_hans-peter_richter_isbn_9782010141591/</guid>
      <description>Friedrich by Hans-Peter Richter Title: Friedrich Author: Hans-Peter Richter Friedrich is a beautifully written children&amp;rsquo;s book by Hans-Peter Richter that tells the story of a young boy named Friedrich who is growing up in Germany during World War II. The book is suitable for children aged 9-12 years old and is an excellent choice for parents and educators looking to introduce historical events and important life lessons to their young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Lark and the Laurel</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_lark_and_the_laurel_by_barbara_willard_isbn_356131696/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_lark_and_the_laurel_by_barbara_willard_isbn_356131696/</guid>
      <description>The Lark and the Laurel by Barbara Willard Title: The Lark and the Laurel Author: Barbara Willard Review: The Lark and the Laurel is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Barbara Willard. The story revolves around the adventures of a young lark and a laurel tree, both of whom face various challenges and learn valuable life lessons along the way. The book is targeted towards children aged 6 to 10 years old, as it contains beautiful illustrations and a simple yet engaging narrative that captures the imagination of young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Silver Sword</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_silver_sword_isbn_8712803723/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_silver_sword_isbn_8712803723/</guid>
      <description>The Silver Sword Title: The Silver Sword Author: Ian Serraillier Review: The Silver Sword is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of four siblings, Edek, Ruth, Bronia, and Jan, who are forced to flee their home in Warsaw during World War II. The book is set in the aftermath of the war and focuses on the siblings&amp;rsquo; journey to find their missing parents. The Silver Sword is a beautifully written book that targets children aged 8 to 12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ede and Unku</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/ede_and_unku_by_alex_wedding_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/ede_and_unku_by_alex_wedding_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Ede and Unku by Alex Wedding Title: &amp;ldquo;Ede and Unku&amp;rdquo; by Alex Wedding &amp;ldquo;Ede and Unku&amp;rdquo; is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes young readers on a delightful adventure through the eyes of two lovable characters, Ede and Unku. Written by Alex Wedding, this book is a perfect choice for children between the ages of 4 to 8 years old. The story revolves around Ede and Unku, two friends who live in a small village.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Biggles Books</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_biggles_books_isbn_1628739134/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_biggles_books_isbn_1628739134/</guid>
      <description>The Biggles Books Title: The Biggles Books Author: W.E. Johns The Biggles Books is a series of children&amp;rsquo;s books written by W.E. Johns, focusing on the adventures of a fictional pilot named James &amp;ldquo;Biggles&amp;rdquo; Bigglesworth. The series is aimed at children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old, and it is a perfect blend of excitement, adventure, and valuable life lessons. The stories in the Biggles Books are set in various historical periods, from World War I to the Cold War era, and they follow the adventures of Biggles and his friends, Algy, Ginger, and Bertie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>White Fang</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/white_fang_isbn_816158924/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/white_fang_isbn_816158924/</guid>
      <description>White Fang Title: White Fang Author: Jack London Target Age Group: 8-12 years old Review: White Fang is a captivating and heartwarming story that follows the life of a wolf-dog hybrid named White Fang. Set in the Yukon Territory during the Klondike Gold Rush, the book delves into the themes of survival, loyalty, and the transformative power of love. The story is divided into two parts, each focusing on a different phase of White Fang&amp;rsquo;s life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Father Grew Wings in Spring</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/father_grew_wings_in_spring_by_tomi_kontio_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/father_grew_wings_in_spring_by_tomi_kontio_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Father Grew Wings in Spring by Tomi Kontio Title: Father Grew Wings in Spring Author: Tomi Kontio Review: &amp;ldquo;Father Grew Wings in Spring&amp;rdquo; is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Tomi Kontio that tells the story of a young boy named Jari, who loves to spend time with his father. The book is perfect for children between the ages of 5 and 10, as it explores themes of family, love, and the importance of cherishing every moment together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three Fairy Tales</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/three_fairy_tales_by_gustavo_martin_garzo_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/three_fairy_tales_by_gustavo_martin_garzo_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Three Fairy Tales by Gustavo Martin Garzo Title: Three Fairy Tales Author: Gustavo Martin Garzo Review: &amp;ldquo;Three Fairy Tales&amp;rdquo; by Gustavo Martin Garzo is a delightful collection of enchanting stories that captivate the imagination of young readers. The book is beautifully illustrated and designed to appeal to children between the ages of 5 and 10. The first tale, &amp;ldquo;The Little Frog,&amp;rdquo; teaches children the importance of self-confidence and believing in oneself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Thief in the Village</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/a_thief_in_the_village_by_james_berry_isbn_9780582344075/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/a_thief_in_the_village_by_james_berry_isbn_9780582344075/</guid>
      <description>A Thief in the Village by James Berry Title: A Thief in the Village Author: James Berry Review: A Thief in the Village is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by James Berry, which tells the story of a small village that faces the challenge of a thief among them. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 8 to 12 years old. The story follows the journey of the villagers as they try to uncover the identity of the thief, while also learning valuable life lessons along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Almost Everyone Could Topple</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/almost_everyone_could_topple_by_toon_tellegen_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/almost_everyone_could_topple_by_toon_tellegen_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Almost Everyone Could Topple by Toon Tellegen Title: Almost Everyone Could Topple Author: Toon Tellegen Review: Almost Everyone Could Topple is a charming and thought-provoking children&amp;rsquo;s book that explores the lives of various animals in a whimsical forest. Written by the talented Toon Tellegen, this book is a delightful read for children aged 6 to 10 years old. The book consists of a series of short stories, each focusing on a different animal character and the challenges they face in their daily lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fire, Bed and Bone</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/fire_bed_and_bone_by_henrietta_branford_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/fire_bed_and_bone_by_henrietta_branford_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Fire, Bed and Bone by Henrietta Branford Title: Fire, Bed and Bone Author: Henrietta Branford Review: Fire, Bed and Bone is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book by Henrietta Branford that tells the story of a young boy named Robin who, after a series of unfortunate events, finds himself living on the streets of London. The book is a perfect blend of adventure, mystery, and historical fiction, making it an engaging read for children aged 8-12 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mouth Open, Story Jump Out</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/mouth_open_story_jump_out_by_grace_hallworth_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/mouth_open_story_jump_out_by_grace_hallworth_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Mouth Open, Story Jump Out by Grace Hallworth Title: Mouth Open, Story Jump Out Author: Grace Hallworth &amp;ldquo;Mouth Open, Story Jump Out&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Grace Hallworth, which is perfect for young readers between the ages of 5 and 8. The book is filled with charming illustrations and engaging stories that capture the imagination of its young audience. The book is divided into several short stories, each one featuring a unique character and a valuable life lesson.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schoolboy Jia Li</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/schoolboy_jia_li_by_qin_wenjun_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/schoolboy_jia_li_by_qin_wenjun_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Schoolboy Jia Li by Qin Wenjun Title: Schoolboy Jia Li Author: Qin Wenjun Schoolboy Jia Li is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Qin Wenjun, which follows the story of a young boy named Jia Li as he navigates through the ups and downs of school life. This heartwarming tale is perfect for children between the ages of 6 and 10, as it addresses various life lessons and challenges that young readers can relate to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conrad: The Factory Made Boy</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/conrad_the_factory_made_boy_by_christine_nostlinger_isbn_745112498/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/conrad_the_factory_made_boy_by_christine_nostlinger_isbn_745112498/</guid>
      <description>Conrad: The Factory Made Boy by Christine Nostlinger Title: Conrad: The Factory Made Boy Author: Christine Nostlinger Review: Conrad: The Factory Made Boy is a heartwarming and thought-provoking children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Christine Nostlinger. The story revolves around a young boy named Conrad, who is created in a factory and shipped to a family as a &amp;ldquo;perfect&amp;rdquo; child. However, as Conrad starts to experience life, he realizes that being perfect is not as important as being loved and accepted for who he is.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ash Road</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/ash_road_by_ivan_southall_isbn_9780140303148/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/ash_road_by_ivan_southall_isbn_9780140303148/</guid>
      <description>Ash Road by Ivan Southall Title: Ash Road Author: Ivan Southall Ash Road is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Ivan Southall, which tells the story of a young boy named David and his journey to find his missing father. The book is targeted towards children aged 8-12 years old, and it provides valuable life lessons through its engaging narrative. The story begins with David and his family living in a small town, struggling to make ends meet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gaston</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/gaston_isbn_9782800126074/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/gaston_isbn_9782800126074/</guid>
      <description>Gaston Title: Gaston Author: Kelly DiPucchio Illustrator: Christian Robinson Recommended Age Group: 4-8 years old Gaston is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a charming little bulldog who finds himself in a family of poodles. The book is beautifully illustrated by Christian Robinson, and the story is written by Kelly DiPucchio, who is known for her engaging and heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s books. The story follows Gaston, a little bulldog who is raised by a family of poodles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Children on the Oregon Trail</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/children_on_the_oregon_trail_by_a._rutgers_van_der_loeff_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/children_on_the_oregon_trail_by_a._rutgers_van_der_loeff_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Children on the Oregon Trail by A. Rutgers Van Der Loeff Title: Children on the Oregon Trail Author: A. Rutgers Van Der Loeff &amp;ldquo;Children on the Oregon Trail&amp;rdquo; is a captivating and educational book that takes young readers on a journey through the historical events of the Oregon Trail. Aimed at children between the ages of 8 and 12, this book is an excellent choice for parents and educators looking to spark an interest in history while teaching valuable life lessons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little House on the Prairie</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/little_house_on_the_prairie_isbn_006054399x/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/little_house_on_the_prairie_isbn_006054399x/</guid>
      <description>Little House on the Prairie Title: Little House on the Prairie Author: Laura Ingalls Wilder Review: Little House on the Prairie is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that transports readers to the pioneer life of the late 1800s. The story follows the Ingalls family as they leave their home in the Big Woods of Wisconsin and embark on a journey to build a new life on the prairie. The book is written in a simple, engaging style that makes it accessible to young readers, while also providing an accurate portrayal of the challenges and joys of pioneer life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rabbit Hill by Robert Lawson</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/rabbit_hill_isbn_7530749889/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/rabbit_hill_isbn_7530749889/</guid>
      <description>Rabbit Hill Title: Rabbit Hill Author: Robert Lawson Review: Rabbit Hill is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Robert Lawson, which tells the story of a group of animals living in a small community. The book primarily focuses on the adventures of a young rabbit named Little Georgie, who is eager to explore the world around him. The story takes place in a charming and peaceful setting, where the animals are able to live in harmony with one another.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Good Master</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_good_master_by_kate_seredy_isbn_9780329061791/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_good_master_by_kate_seredy_isbn_9780329061791/</guid>
      <description>The Good Master by Kate Seredy Title: The Good Master Author: Kate Seredy Review: The Good Master is a charming and heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Kate Seredy. The story is set in the Hungarian countryside and follows the adventures of a young boy named János and his uncle, known as the Good Master. The book is suitable for children aged 8-12, as it offers a rich and engaging narrative that will capture the imagination of young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Celia Says</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/what_celia_says_by_elena_fortun_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/what_celia_says_by_elena_fortun_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>What Celia Says by Elena Fortun Title: What Celia Says Author: Elena Fortun &amp;ldquo;What Celia Says&amp;rdquo; is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Elena Fortun, which tells the story of a young girl named Celia who has a unique way of looking at the world. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 5 to 10 years old, and it is an excellent choice for parents and teachers looking for a book that teaches valuable life lessons in a fun and engaging manner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arsene Lupin Gentleman Thief</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/arsene_lupin_gentleman_thief_isbn_1538707462/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/arsene_lupin_gentleman_thief_isbn_1538707462/</guid>
      <description>Arsene Lupin Gentleman Thief Title: Arsene Lupin, Gentleman Thief Author: Maurice Leblanc Genre: Children&amp;rsquo;s Adventure Target Age Group: 8-12 years old &amp;ldquo;Arsene Lupin, Gentleman Thief&amp;rdquo; is a thrilling adventure story that follows the cunning exploits of the master thief, Arsene Lupin. Written by Maurice Leblanc, this book is a delightful read for children between the ages of 8 and 12. The story is filled with mystery, suspense, and humor, making it an engaging read for young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zen Shorts</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/zen_shorts_isbn_9780545040877/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/zen_shorts_isbn_9780545040877/</guid>
      <description>Zen Shorts Title: Zen Shorts Author: Jon J. Muth Target Age Group: 5-10 years old &amp;ldquo;Zen Shorts&amp;rdquo; is a beautifully illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book that captures the essence of mindfulness and the importance of finding inner peace. Author Jon J. Muth has skillfully crafted a story that is both engaging and educational for young readers. The book follows the story of three siblings, Michael, Karl, and Addy, who meet a wise and mysterious panda named Stillwater.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are We There Yet?</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/are_we_there_yet_by_alison_lester_isbn_670880671/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/are_we_there_yet_by_alison_lester_isbn_670880671/</guid>
      <description>Are We There Yet? by Alison Lester Title: Are We There Yet? Author: Alison Lester Review: Are We There Yet? is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Alison Lester, which takes young readers on an exciting journey across Australia. The story follows Grace and her family as they embark on a road trip from their home in Melbourne to visit relatives in far-off Western Australia. The book is filled with vibrant illustrations and engaging storytelling, making it a perfect choice for children between the ages of 4 and 8.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lend Me Your Wings</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/lend_me_your_wings_by_john_agard_isbn_9780316020107/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/lend_me_your_wings_by_john_agard_isbn_9780316020107/</guid>
      <description>Lend Me Your Wings by John Agard Title: Lend Me Your Wings Author: John Agard Lend Me Your Wings is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by John Agard, a well-known poet and author. This engaging story is perfect for children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old. The book is filled with beautiful illustrations that capture the imagination and bring the story to life. The story follows a young boy named Joe, who discovers a magical pair of wings that allow him to fly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Big Sister</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_big_sister_by_siv_widerberg_isbn_9129591864/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_big_sister_by_siv_widerberg_isbn_9129591864/</guid>
      <description>The Big Sister by Siv Widerberg Title: The Big Sister Author: Siv Widerberg Review: The Big Sister is a heartwarming and beautifully illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young girl who becomes a big sister for the first time. This book is perfect for children between the ages of 3 and 8, as it captures the excitement and challenges of welcoming a new sibling into the family. The story follows the protagonist as she navigates the complex emotions of being a big sister, including jealousy, pride, and love.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flat Stanley</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/flat_stanley_by_jeff_brown_isbn_9781405211000/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/flat_stanley_by_jeff_brown_isbn_9781405211000/</guid>
      <description>Flat Stanley by Jeff Brown Title: Flat Stanley Author: Jeff Brown Review: Flat Stanley is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Jeff Brown. The story follows the adventures of Stanley Lambchop, a young boy who becomes flat after a mysterious event involving a bulletin board and a falling bed. As a result, Stanley is able to slide under doors, fly like a kite, and even travel through the mail. This book is targeted towards children between the ages of 4 and 8.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frederick</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/frederick_isbn_1979021686/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/frederick_isbn_1979021686/</guid>
      <description>Frederick Title: Frederick Author: Leo Lionni Recommended Age Group: 4-8 years old Frederick is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Leo Lionni, which tells the story of a family of field mice living in a beautiful meadow. The book primarily focuses on the character of Frederick, a field mouse who spends his time daydreaming and observing the world around him, rather than actively participating in the preparations for winter like the other mice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harold and the Purple Crayon</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/harold_and_the_purple_crayon_isbn_9780439132534/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/harold_and_the_purple_crayon_isbn_9780439132534/</guid>
      <description>Harold and the Purple Crayon Title: Harold and the Purple Crayon Author: Crockett Johnson Recommended Age Group: 4-8 years old &amp;ldquo;Harold and the Purple Crayon&amp;rdquo; is a timeless classic that has been enjoyed by children for generations. The story follows the adventures of a young boy named Harold, who uses his purple crayon to create a world of his own. This imaginative tale teaches valuable life lessons and is perfect for children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Old Master Q</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/old_master_q_by_wong_chak_isbn_692588213/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/old_master_q_by_wong_chak_isbn_692588213/</guid>
      <description>Old Master Q by Wong Chak Title: Old Master Q Author: Wong Chak Review: Old Master Q is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the adventures of a lovable and mischievous character named Old Master Q. The book is perfect for young readers between the ages of 7 and 12, as it contains engaging illustrations and simple, yet captivating storylines. The book targets children in the elementary school age group, as it focuses on teaching important life lessons through the humorous escapades of Old Master Q.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Biggest Bear</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_biggest_bear_isbn_9780440842026/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_biggest_bear_isbn_9780440842026/</guid>
      <description>The Biggest Bear Title: The Biggest Bear Author: Lynd Ward Review: The Biggest Bear is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young boy named Johnny who encounters a massive, friendly bear in the woods. The story is set in a small village surrounded by beautiful forests, where Johnny and his family live. The illustrations in this book are simply breathtaking, as they were created by the talented Lynd Ward, who uses intricate wood engravings to bring the story to life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rupert the Bear</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/rupert_the_bear_by_mary_tourtel_isbn_9780361029575/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/rupert_the_bear_by_mary_tourtel_isbn_9780361029575/</guid>
      <description>Rupert the Bear by Mary Tourtel Title: Rupert the Bear Author: Mary Tourtel Rupert the Bear is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Mary Tourtel, which follows the adventures of the lovable bear, Rupert, and his friends. This book is perfect for children between the ages of 4 and 8, as it contains colorful illustrations and engaging stories that are sure to capture their attention. The book is divided into several short stories, each of which focuses on a different life lesson.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tales and Legends</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/tales_and_legends_by_javier_villafane_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/tales_and_legends_by_javier_villafane_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Tales and Legends by Javier Villafane Title: Tales and Legends Author: Javier Villafane Review: Tales and Legends by Javier Villafane is a delightful collection of stories that captivate the imagination and teach valuable life lessons. This book is perfect for elementary school children, particularly those between the ages of 6 and 10. The stories in Tales and Legends are diverse, covering a wide range of themes and cultures. Each tale is beautifully illustrated, making it visually appealing for young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When We Were Very Young</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/when_we_were_very_young_isbn_808538330/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/when_we_were_very_young_isbn_808538330/</guid>
      <description>When We Were Very Young Title: When We Were Very Young Author: A.A. Milne Illustrator: E.H. Shepard Age Group: 4-8 years old &amp;ldquo;When We Were Very Young&amp;rdquo; is a delightful collection of poems written by A.A. Milne, the author of the beloved Winnie-the-Pooh series. This book is an excellent choice for children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old, as it contains simple, yet engaging poems that will capture their imagination and attention.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Poems for the Very Young</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/poems_for_the_very_young_by_michael_rosen_isbn_9781856971164/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/poems_for_the_very_young_by_michael_rosen_isbn_9781856971164/</guid>
      <description>Poems for the Very Young by Michael Rosen Title: Poems for the Very Young Author: Michael Rosen Target Age Group: 4-8 years old &amp;ldquo;Poems for the Very Young&amp;rdquo; is a delightful collection of poems by Michael Rosen, specifically designed for young children. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old, making it an excellent choice for parents, teachers, and caregivers looking for engaging and educational content for their little ones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Barbapapa</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/barbapapa_by_annette_tison_and_talus_taylor_isbn_590711997/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/barbapapa_by_annette_tison_and_talus_taylor_isbn_590711997/</guid>
      <description>Barbapapa by Annette Tison and Talus Taylor Title: Barbapapa Author: Annette Tison and Talus Taylor Barbapapa is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the adventures of a lovable, shape-shifting character named Barbapapa. The story is written by Annette Tison and Talus Taylor, and it is perfect for children between the ages of 4 to 8 years old. The book is filled with vibrant illustrations that capture the imagination of young readers, as they follow Barbapapa on his journey through various transformations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Freight Train</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/freight_train_isbn_9789573212409/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/freight_train_isbn_9789573212409/</guid>
      <description>Freight Train Title: Freight Train Author: Donald Crews Freight Train is a charming and vibrant children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes young readers on a journey through the world of trains. With its simple yet engaging story and colorful illustrations, this book is perfect for children aged 2 to 5 years old. The story follows a freight train as it travels through different landscapes, passing by cities, mountains, and tunnels. The book teaches children about colors, shapes, and the concept of a train&amp;rsquo;s journey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ivor the Engine</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/ivor_the_engine_by_oliver_postgate_isbn_9780200715256/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/ivor_the_engine_by_oliver_postgate_isbn_9780200715256/</guid>
      <description>Ivor the Engine by Oliver Postgate Title: Ivor the Engine Author: Oliver Postgate Ivor the Engine is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Oliver Postgate, which tells the story of a small locomotive named Ivor who lives in the magical village of Llaniog. The book is filled with delightful illustrations and is perfect for children between the ages of 4 to 8 years old. The story revolves around Ivor, who is a hardworking and friendly engine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little I Am I</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/little_i_am_i_by_mira_lobe_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/little_i_am_i_by_mira_lobe_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Little I Am I by Mira Lobe Title: Little I Am I Author: Mira Lobe Review: Little I Am I is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Mira Lobe, which is perfect for young readers between the ages of 4 and 8. The book follows the story of a little girl who is trying to find her place in the world and learn about the importance of self-worth. The illustrations in the book are vibrant and eye-catching, which helps to keep the young readers engaged.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pancakes for Findus</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/pancakes_for_findus_by_sven_nordqvist_isbn_1912480441/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/pancakes_for_findus_by_sven_nordqvist_isbn_1912480441/</guid>
      <description>Pancakes for Findus by Sven Nordqvist Title: Pancakes for Findus Author: Sven Nordqvist &amp;ldquo;Pancakes for Findus&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Sven Nordqvist, which tells the story of an old man named Farmer Pettson and his curious cat, Findus. The book is a part of a series that revolves around the adventures of Pettson and Findus, and this particular story focuses on the duo&amp;rsquo;s attempt to make pancakes together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Miffy</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/miffy_by_dick_bruna_isbn_1592260225/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/miffy_by_dick_bruna_isbn_1592260225/</guid>
      <description>Miffy by Dick Bruna Title: Miffy Author: Dick Bruna Review: Miffy, written by Dick Bruna, is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young bunny named Miffy. This book is perfect for children aged 3-6 years old, as it features simple yet engaging illustrations and a straightforward narrative. The story follows Miffy as she goes about her day, encountering various situations and learning valuable life lessons along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pat the Bunny</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/pat_the_bunny_isbn_9784062740036/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/pat_the_bunny_isbn_9784062740036/</guid>
      <description>Pat the Bunny Title: Pat the Bunny Author: Dorothy Kunhardt Age Group: Infants and Toddlers (0-3 years old) Pat the Bunny is a classic children&amp;rsquo;s book that has been cherished by generations of young readers. Written by Dorothy Kunhardt and first published in 1940, this timeless story has become a staple in many households. The book is specifically designed for infants and toddlers, making it an excellent choice for parents looking to introduce their little ones to the world of reading.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Elephant and the Bad Baby</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_elephant_and_the_bad_baby_by_elfrida_vipont_isbn_9780140500486/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_elephant_and_the_bad_baby_by_elfrida_vipont_isbn_9780140500486/</guid>
      <description>The Elephant and the Bad Baby by Elfrida Vipont Title: The Elephant and the Bad Baby Author: Elfrida Vipont The Elephant and the Bad Baby is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Elfrida Vipont. The story follows the adventures of a mischievous baby who encounters an elephant in his quest for sweets. The book is beautifully illustrated by Raymond Briggs, adding to the charm of the story. The target age group for this book is 3-7 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where&#39;s Spot?</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/wheres_spot_isbn_399243739/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/wheres_spot_isbn_399243739/</guid>
      <description>Where&amp;rsquo;s Spot? Title: Where&amp;rsquo;s Spot? Author: Eric Hill Age Group: 2-5 years old &amp;ldquo;Where&amp;rsquo;s Spot?&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written and illustrated by Eric Hill. The story follows the adventures of a lovable dog named Spot as he explores his world and makes new friends. The book is targeted towards children aged 2-5 years old, and it teaches valuable life lessons through its engaging and colorful illustrations. The book&amp;rsquo;s primary focus is on the importance of friendship, as Spot encounters various animals throughout the story.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
