<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Childrens Books that talk about &#39;Stereotypes&#39; on Monsty The Monster Truck</title>
    <link>https://www.monsty.co/tags/childrens-books-that-talk-about-stereotypes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Childrens Books that talk about &#39;Stereotypes&#39; on Monsty The Monster Truck</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.monsty.co/tags/childrens-books-that-talk-about-stereotypes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bud, Not Buddy</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/bud_not_buddy_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/bud_not_buddy_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Bud, Not Buddy Title: Bud, Not Buddy Author: Christopher Paul Curtis Review: Bud, Not Buddy is a heartwarming and adventurous story about a 10-year-old boy named Bud Caldwell, who embarks on a journey to find his father. Set in the 1930s during the Great Depression, the book takes readers on a rollercoaster of emotions as Bud encounters various obstacles and makes new friends along the way. The target age group for this book is 8-12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deadly, Unna?</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/deadly_unna_by_phillip_gwynne_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/deadly_unna_by_phillip_gwynne_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Deadly, Unna? by Phillip Gwynne Title: Deadly, Unna? Author: Phillip Gwynne Review: Deadly, Unna? is a captivating and thought-provoking children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Phillip Gwynne. The story follows the life of a young boy named Gary Black, who is a member of the Australian football team. Gary&amp;rsquo;s life takes an unexpected turn when he befriends a young indigenous girl named Nunga, who teaches him about her culture and the struggles her community faces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alex</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/alex_by_tessa_duder_isbn_9780195581690/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/alex_by_tessa_duder_isbn_9780195581690/</guid>
      <description>Alex by Tessa Duder Title: Alex Author: Tessa Duder Review: &amp;ldquo;Alex&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Tessa Duder, which follows the adventures of a young girl named Alex as she navigates the challenges of growing up. The book is a perfect fit for children between the ages of 8 and 12, as it addresses themes that are relatable to this age group, such as friendship, self-discovery, and overcoming obstacles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Homecoming</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/homecoming_isbn_9780413413307/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/homecoming_isbn_9780413413307/</guid>
      <description>Homecoming Title: Homecoming Author: K.A. Applegate Review: Homecoming is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the journey of a young girl named Lily, who discovers the importance of family, friendship, and finding one&amp;rsquo;s true home. The story is filled with beautiful illustrations and captivating characters that will keep young readers engaged from start to finish. Target Age Group: Homecoming is suitable for children between the ages of 7 and 10. The book&amp;rsquo;s themes and language are appropriate for this age range, and the story provides valuable life lessons that children can relate to and learn from.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Kestrel for a Knave</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/a_kestrel_for_a_knave_isbn_1858481465/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/a_kestrel_for_a_knave_isbn_1858481465/</guid>
      <description>A Kestrel for a Knave Title: A Kestrel for a Knave Author: Barry Hines Recommended Age Group: 10-14 years old A Kestrel for a Knave is a captivating and thought-provoking novel by Barry Hines, which tells the story of Billy Casper, a young boy from a working-class family in a small English town. The book is a perfect blend of emotions, struggles, and triumphs, making it an excellent read for children between the ages of 10 and 14.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where the Lilies Bloom</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/where_the_lilies_bloom_isbn_881032913/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/where_the_lilies_bloom_isbn_881032913/</guid>
      <description>Where the Lilies Bloom Title: Where the Lilies Bloom Author: Vera Cleaver and Bill Cleaver Review: &amp;ldquo;Where the Lilies Bloom&amp;rdquo; is a heartwarming and inspiring children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a family living in the Appalachian Mountains. The story follows the lives of Mary Call, her siblings, and their struggle to survive after their father&amp;rsquo;s death. The book is suitable for children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bill&#39;s New Frock</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/bills_new_frock_by_anne_fine_isbn_9789582401757/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/bills_new_frock_by_anne_fine_isbn_9789582401757/</guid>
      <description>Bill&amp;rsquo;s New Frock by Anne Fine Title: Bill&amp;rsquo;s New Frock Author: Anne Fine &amp;ldquo;Bill&amp;rsquo;s New Frock&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Anne Fine, which tells the story of a young boy named Bill who wakes up one morning to find himself in the body of a girl. The book is targeted towards children aged 8-12 years old and teaches valuable life lessons about empathy, understanding, and the importance of treating others with kindness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Girragundji</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/my_girragundji_by_meme_mcdonald_and_boon_pryor_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/my_girragundji_by_meme_mcdonald_and_boon_pryor_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>My Girragundji by Meme Mcdonald and Boon Pryor Title: My Girragundji Author: Meme McDonald and Boon Pryor Review: My Girragundji is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young boy named Jake and his special bond with a pet fish named Girragundji. The book is beautifully illustrated, and the text is simple and engaging, making it perfect for children aged 4 to 8 years old. The story explores themes of friendship, loss, and the importance of cherishing the memories we create with our loved ones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jacob Have I Loved</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/jacob_have_i_loved_isbn_9788420460819/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/jacob_have_i_loved_isbn_9788420460819/</guid>
      <description>Jacob Have I Loved Title: Jacob Have I Loved Author: Katherine Paterson Review: Jacob Have I Loved is a beautifully written children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of two twin sisters, Sara Louise and Caroline, growing up on an island off the coast of Maryland. The story is narrated by Sara Louise, who is constantly overshadowed by her sister Caroline, who is considered to be the more beautiful and talented twin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nothing to Be Afraid of</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/nothing_to_be_afraid_of_by_jan_mark_isbn_9780722656778/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/nothing_to_be_afraid_of_by_jan_mark_isbn_9780722656778/</guid>
      <description>Nothing to Be Afraid of by Jan Mark Title: &amp;ldquo;Nothing to Be Afraid of&amp;rdquo; Author: Jan Mark Review: &amp;ldquo;Nothing to Be Afraid of&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the adventures of a young boy named Gareth, who is afraid of the dark. Throughout the story, Gareth learns valuable life lessons about facing his fears and finding the courage to overcome them. The book is beautifully illustrated, with vibrant colors and engaging images that will capture the attention of young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Goalkeeper&#39;s Revenge</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_goalkeepers_revenge_by_bill_naughton_isbn_340149418/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_goalkeepers_revenge_by_bill_naughton_isbn_340149418/</guid>
      <description>The Goalkeeper&amp;rsquo;s Revenge by Bill Naughton Title: The Goalkeeper&amp;rsquo;s Revenge Author: Bill Naughton Age Group: 8-12 years old The Goalkeeper&amp;rsquo;s Revenge is a charming and engaging children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Bill Naughton. The story follows the adventures of a young boy named Tommy who dreams of becoming a great soccer player. As Tommy faces various challenges and learns valuable life lessons, the reader is taken on a journey filled with humor, excitement, and heartwarming moments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UG: Boy Genius of the Stone Age</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/ug_boy_genius_of_the_stone_age_by_raymond_briggs_isbn_9781856130547/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/ug_boy_genius_of_the_stone_age_by_raymond_briggs_isbn_9781856130547/</guid>
      <description>UG: Boy Genius of the Stone Age by Raymond Briggs Title: UG: Boy Genius of the Stone Age Author: Raymond Briggs Target Age Group: 7-10 years old Review: UG: Boy Genius of the Stone Age is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written and illustrated by the talented Raymond Briggs. The story follows the adventures of Ug, a young boy living in the Stone Age, who is considered a genius by his tribe due to his inventiveness and problem-solving skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Toad Who Wanted to Be a Star</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/a_toad_who_wanted_to_be_a_star_by_oscar_alfaro_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/a_toad_who_wanted_to_be_a_star_by_oscar_alfaro_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>A Toad Who Wanted to Be a Star by Oscar Alfaro Title: A Toad Who Wanted to Be a Star Author: Oscar Alfaro A Toad Who Wanted to Be a Star is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Oscar Alfaro that tells the story of a little toad who dreams of becoming a star. The book is beautifully illustrated and targets children between the ages of 4 to 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Adventures of Maya the Bee</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_adventures_of_maya_the_bee_by_waldemar_bonsels_isbn_1627937587/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_adventures_of_maya_the_bee_by_waldemar_bonsels_isbn_1627937587/</guid>
      <description>The Adventures of Maya the Bee by Waldemar Bonsels Title: The Adventures of Maya the Bee Author: Waldemar Bonsels Review: The Adventures of Maya the Bee, written by Waldemar Bonsels, is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the journey of Maya, a young bee who embarks on an adventure to explore the world outside her hive. The story is filled with colorful characters, exciting adventures, and valuable life lessons that make it an enjoyable read for children aged 6 to 10 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazing Grace</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/amazing_grace_isbn_9781423320166/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/amazing_grace_isbn_9781423320166/</guid>
      <description>Amazing Grace Title: Amazing Grace Author: Mary Hoffman Illustrator: Caroline Binch Amazing Grace is a beautifully illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young girl named Grace who loves to act out stories and dreams of being in a play. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 4 to 8 years old, as it features simple language and engaging illustrations that will capture the attention of young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
