<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Childrens Books that talk about &#39;Mindful&#39; on Monsty The Monster Truck</title>
    <link>https://www.monsty.co/tags/childrens-books-that-talk-about-mindful/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Childrens Books that talk about &#39;Mindful&#39; on Monsty The Monster Truck</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.monsty.co/tags/childrens-books-that-talk-about-mindful/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Molly Goes Shopping</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/molly_goes_shopping_by_eva_eriksson_isbn_9129658195/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/molly_goes_shopping_by_eva_eriksson_isbn_9129658195/</guid>
      <description>Molly Goes Shopping by Eva Eriksson Title: Molly Goes Shopping Author: Eva Eriksson Molly Goes Shopping is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Eva Eriksson, aimed at children between the ages of 4 to 8 years old. The story follows the adventures of a young girl named Molly, who goes shopping with her mother and learns important life lessons along the way. The illustrations in the book are vibrant and engaging, capturing the attention of young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dear Nobody</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/dear_nobody_isbn_531086119/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/dear_nobody_isbn_531086119/</guid>
      <description>Dear Nobody Title: Dear Nobody Author: Berlie Doherty Recommended Age Group: 8-12 years old Dear Nobody is a heartwarming and thought-provoking children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Berlie Doherty. The story revolves around two main characters, Helen and Chris, who are both dealing with the challenges of growing up and navigating their emotions. The book is written in a diary format, with Helen and Chris taking turns to share their thoughts and feelings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tulku</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/tulku_isbn_9780140313574/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/tulku_isbn_9780140313574/</guid>
      <description>Tulku Title: Tulku Author: Pearl Zhu Review: &amp;ldquo;Tulku&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that captures the imagination of young readers with its enchanting story and vibrant illustrations. Author Pearl Zhu has crafted a heartwarming tale that follows the adventures of a young boy named Tulku, who embarks on a journey of self-discovery and friendship. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 5 and 10 years old. The language is simple and easy to understand, making it an excellent choice for early readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heart</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/heart_by_edmondo_de_amicis_isbn_9781410103154/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/heart_by_edmondo_de_amicis_isbn_9781410103154/</guid>
      <description>Heart by Edmondo De Amicis Title: Heart Author: Edmondo De Amicis Review: Heart, written by Edmondo De Amicis, is a beautifully crafted children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes young readers on a heartwarming journey through the ups and downs of life. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 8 and 12, as it deals with themes of friendship, kindness, and empathy. The story follows the adventures of a young boy named Enrico, who learns valuable life lessons from his interactions with the people around him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Katy Did</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/what_katy_did_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/what_katy_did_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>What Katy Did Title: What Katy Did Author: Susan Coolidge Target Age Group: 8-12 years old &amp;ldquo;What Katy Did&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Susan Coolidge, originally published in 1872. The story revolves around the life of a young girl named Katy Carr and her family. The book has been cherished by generations of readers and continues to be a favorite among children today. The story is set in the 19th century and follows Katy, a lively and adventurous girl who loves to play with her siblings and friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Carpet People</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_carpet_people_isbn_9780754050674/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_carpet_people_isbn_9780754050674/</guid>
      <description>The Carpet People Title: The Carpet People Author: Terry Pratchett Review: The Carpet People is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Terry Pratchett, which takes readers on a fantastical journey through the world of tiny people living in the carpet. The story follows the adventures of the Carpet People as they face various challenges and learn important life lessons. The book is suitable for children between the ages of 7 and 12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Half Magic</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/half_magic_isbn_156379902/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/half_magic_isbn_156379902/</guid>
      <description>Half Magic Title: Half Magic Author: Edward Eager Genre: Children&amp;rsquo;s Fantasy Fiction Recommended Age Group: 8-12 years old &amp;ldquo;Half Magic&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes readers on a magical adventure with four siblings who stumble upon a wish-granting coin. The story is filled with humor, adventure, and valuable life lessons that children can learn from. The four siblings, Jane, Mark, Katharine, and Martha, are the main characters in the book.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Canterville Ghost</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_canterville_ghost_isbn_9783842451155/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_canterville_ghost_isbn_9783842451155/</guid>
      <description>The Canterville Ghost Title: The Canterville Ghost Author: Oscar Wilde Review: The Canterville Ghost is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the renowned author Oscar Wilde. The story revolves around a family who moves into an old castle haunted by a ghost, Sir Simon. The ghost tries to scare the family away but to his surprise, they are not afraid of him. Instead, they try to help him and understand his story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zen Shorts</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/zen_shorts_isbn_9780545040877/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/zen_shorts_isbn_9780545040877/</guid>
      <description>Zen Shorts Title: Zen Shorts Author: Jon J. Muth Target Age Group: 5-10 years old &amp;ldquo;Zen Shorts&amp;rdquo; is a beautifully illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book that captures the essence of mindfulness and the importance of finding inner peace. Author Jon J. Muth has skillfully crafted a story that is both engaging and educational for young readers. The book follows the story of three siblings, Michael, Karl, and Addy, who meet a wise and mysterious panda named Stillwater.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oh, the Places You&#39;ll Go</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/oh_the_places_youll_go_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/oh_the_places_youll_go_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Oh, the Places You&amp;rsquo;ll Go Title: Oh, the Places You&amp;rsquo;ll Go Author: Dr. Seuss Review: Oh, the Places You&amp;rsquo;ll Go is a delightful and inspiring children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the beloved author Dr. Seuss. This book is perfect for children aged 4 to 8 years old, as it captures their imagination and teaches valuable life lessons in a fun and engaging way. The story follows the journey of a young character as they navigate through the ups and downs of life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Little Bird</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_little_bird_by_paro_anand_isbn_817223077x/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_little_bird_by_paro_anand_isbn_817223077x/</guid>
      <description>The Little Bird by Paro Anand Title: The Little Bird Author: Paro Anand The Little Bird is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Paro Anand, which tells the story of a young bird who embarks on a journey of self-discovery and learns valuable life lessons along the way. This beautifully illustrated book is perfect for children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old. The story revolves around a little bird who is curious about the world around her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Walk in the Park</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/a_walk_in_the_park_by_anthony_browne_isbn_241893976/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/a_walk_in_the_park_by_anthony_browne_isbn_241893976/</guid>
      <description>A Walk in the Park by Anthony Browne Title: A Walk in the Park Author: Anthony Browne Review: A Walk in the Park is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the talented author and illustrator, Anthony Browne. This book is perfect for young readers between the ages of 4 to 8 years old. The story follows a young boy and his father as they take a walk in the park. The book is filled with beautiful illustrations that capture the essence of the story and make it an enjoyable read for both children and adults.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Cat That Lived a Million Times</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_cat_that_lived_a_million_times_by_yoko_sano_isbn_9780824820985/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_cat_that_lived_a_million_times_by_yoko_sano_isbn_9780824820985/</guid>
      <description>The Cat That Lived a Million Times by Yoko Sano Title: The Cat That Lived a Million Times Author: Yoko Sano Review: The Cat That Lived a Million Times is a heartwarming and enchanting children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a cat with an extraordinary ability to reincarnate and live multiple lives. The book is a perfect read for children aged 6-10 years old, as it features beautiful illustrations and a captivating narrative that will keep young readers engaged.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Enormous Crocodile</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_enormous_crocodile_isbn_9789750719257/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_enormous_crocodile_isbn_9789750719257/</guid>
      <description>The Enormous Crocodile Title: The Enormous Crocodile Author: Roald Dahl Illustrator: Quentin Blake Recommended Age Group: 4-8 years old The Enormous Crocodile is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the renowned author Roald Dahl and beautifully illustrated by Quentin Blake. This charming story is perfect for children aged 4-8 years old, as it features colorful illustrations and a simple yet engaging plot. The story revolves around a greedy and devious crocodile who has a voracious appetite for children.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two Little Bears</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/two_little_bears_by_hanna_muschg_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/two_little_bears_by_hanna_muschg_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Two Little Bears by Hanna Muschg Title: Two Little Bears Author: Hanna Muschg Review: Two Little Bears is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Hanna Muschg, which tells the story of two young bears, Tina and Tom, who embark on a series of adventures in the forest. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 4 to 8 years old and is a perfect blend of fun, adventure, and valuable life lessons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Tree Is Nice</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/a_tree_is_nice_isbn_64434052/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/a_tree_is_nice_isbn_64434052/</guid>
      <description>A Tree Is Nice Title: A Tree Is Nice Author: Janice May Udry Illustrator: Marc Simont A Tree Is Nice is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that celebrates the beauty and value of trees in our lives. The book is written in a simple and engaging manner, making it an ideal read for children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old. The story begins by highlighting the various reasons why trees are nice, such as providing shade, a place to play, and a home for birds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are You My Mother?</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/are_you_my_mother_isbn_1718185/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/are_you_my_mother_isbn_1718185/</guid>
      <description>Are You My Mother? Title: Are You My Mother? Author: P.D. Eastman Genre: Children&amp;rsquo;s Picture Book Recommended Age Group: 3-7 years old Are You My Mother? is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s picture book written by P.D. Eastman. This charming story follows a baby bird who hatches while his mother is away, and goes on a journey to find her. The book is filled with colorful illustrations and simple language, making it perfect for young readers and listeners alike.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clever Polly and the Stupid Wolf</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/clever_polly_and_the_stupid_wolf_by_catherine_storr_isbn_9995217074/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/clever_polly_and_the_stupid_wolf_by_catherine_storr_isbn_9995217074/</guid>
      <description>Clever Polly and the Stupid Wolf by Catherine Storr Title: Clever Polly and the Stupid Wolf Author: Catherine Storr Review: Clever Polly and the Stupid Wolf is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a clever young girl named Polly who outwits a not-so-bright wolf. The book is perfect for children aged 4-8 years old, as it contains simple yet engaging language and beautiful illustrations. The story teaches valuable life lessons such as the importance of being clever, using one&amp;rsquo;s intelligence to overcome challenges, and treating others with kindness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Biggest Bear</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_biggest_bear_isbn_9780440842026/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_biggest_bear_isbn_9780440842026/</guid>
      <description>The Biggest Bear Title: The Biggest Bear Author: Lynd Ward Review: The Biggest Bear is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young boy named Johnny who encounters a massive, friendly bear in the woods. The story is set in a small village surrounded by beautiful forests, where Johnny and his family live. The illustrations in this book are simply breathtaking, as they were created by the talented Lynd Ward, who uses intricate wood engravings to bring the story to life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ameliaranne and the Green Umbrella</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/ameliaranne_and_the_green_umbrella_by_constance_heward_isbn_245551042/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/ameliaranne_and_the_green_umbrella_by_constance_heward_isbn_245551042/</guid>
      <description>Ameliaranne and the Green Umbrella by Constance Heward Title: Ameliaranne and the Green Umbrella Author: Constance Heward Ameliaranne and the Green Umbrella is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the adventures of a young girl named Ameliaranne and her magical green umbrella. The story takes place in a whimsical world where anything is possible, and Ameliaranne learns valuable life lessons along the way. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 6 and 10 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marc Just Couldn&#39;t Sleep</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/marc_just_couldnt_sleep_by_gabriela_keselman_isbn_9781929132911/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/marc_just_couldnt_sleep_by_gabriela_keselman_isbn_9781929132911/</guid>
      <description>Marc Just Couldn&amp;rsquo;t Sleep by Gabriela Keselman Title: Marc Just Couldn&amp;rsquo;t Sleep Author: Gabriela Keselman Review: Marc Just Couldn&amp;rsquo;t Sleep is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young boy named Marc who struggles to fall asleep at night. Through vivid illustrations and engaging storytelling, author Gabriela Keselman takes readers on a journey with Marc as he tries various methods to overcome his sleeplessness. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 4 and 8, making it an ideal bedtime story for parents to read with their young ones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Poems for the Very Young</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/poems_for_the_very_young_by_michael_rosen_isbn_9781856971164/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/poems_for_the_very_young_by_michael_rosen_isbn_9781856971164/</guid>
      <description>Poems for the Very Young by Michael Rosen Title: Poems for the Very Young Author: Michael Rosen Target Age Group: 4-8 years old &amp;ldquo;Poems for the Very Young&amp;rdquo; is a delightful collection of poems by Michael Rosen, specifically designed for young children. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old, making it an excellent choice for parents, teachers, and caregivers looking for engaging and educational content for their little ones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sleep Well, Little Bear</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/sleep_well_little_bear_by_quint_buckholz_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/sleep_well_little_bear_by_quint_buckholz_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Sleep Well, Little Bear by Quint Buckholz Title: Sleep Well, Little Bear Author: Quint Buckholz Sleep Well, Little Bear is a beautifully illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young bear named Little Bear who is having trouble sleeping. The book is written by Quint Buckholz and is perfect for children between the ages of 3 to 8 years old. The story begins with Little Bear feeling restless and unable to sleep.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Go, Dog. Go!</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/go_dog._go_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/go_dog._go_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Go, Dog. Go! Title: Go, Dog. Go! Author: P.D. Eastman Review: Go, Dog. Go! is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the adventures of a group of dogs as they travel to a big dog party. The book is filled with colorful illustrations and simple, engaging text that makes it perfect for young readers. Target Age Group: The book is suitable for children between the ages of 3 and 7 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mr Archimedes&#39; Bath</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/mr_archimedes_bath_by_pamela_allen_isbn_688419194/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/mr_archimedes_bath_by_pamela_allen_isbn_688419194/</guid>
      <description>Mr Archimedes&amp;rsquo; Bath by Pamela Allen Title: Mr Archimedes&amp;rsquo; Bath Author: Pamela Allen &amp;ldquo;Mr Archimedes&amp;rsquo; Bath&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the talented author, Pamela Allen. The story follows the adventures of a dog named Mr. Archimedes, who loves taking baths in the bathtub. One day, he discovers that the water level in the bathtub is rising, and he embarks on a journey to find out why. This book is an excellent choice for children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Wonderful Tree</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_wonderful_tree_by_ulf_lofgren_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_wonderful_tree_by_ulf_lofgren_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Wonderful Tree by Ulf Lofgren Title: The Wonderful Tree Author: Ulf Lofgren Review: The Wonderful Tree is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a tree that is home to a diverse group of animals. The story is set in a beautiful forest and teaches children about the importance of friendship, cooperation, and respect for nature. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Does the Mouse Think on Thursday</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/what_does_the_mouse_think_on_thursday_by_josef_guggenmos_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/what_does_the_mouse_think_on_thursday_by_josef_guggenmos_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>What Does the Mouse Think on Thursday by Josef Guggenmos Title: &amp;ldquo;What Does the Mouse Think on Thursday&amp;rdquo; Author: Josef Guggenmos Review: &amp;ldquo;What Does the Mouse Think on Thursday&amp;rdquo; is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the adventures of a curious little mouse named Tuffy. The story takes place over the course of a week, with each day bringing new discoveries and experiences for Tuffy. The book is written in a simple and engaging manner, making it perfect for young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where the Wild Things Are</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/where_the_wild_things_are_isbn_9780439052139/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/where_the_wild_things_are_isbn_9780439052139/</guid>
      <description>Where the Wild Things Are Title: Where the Wild Things Are Author: Maurice Sendak Recommended Age Group: 4-8 years old Where the Wild Things Are is a timeless classic written and illustrated by Maurice Sendak. The story follows a young boy named Max, who, after being sent to his room without supper for misbehaving, embarks on a wild adventure with mysterious and fantastical creatures. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alvin Says Good Night</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/alvin_says_good_night_by_ulf_lofgren_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/alvin_says_good_night_by_ulf_lofgren_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Alvin Says Good Night by Ulf Lofgren Title: Alvin Says Good Night Author: Ulf Lofgren Review: Alvin Says Good Night is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the adventures of a young boy named Alvin as he struggles to find the perfect way to say goodnight to all his favorite things. Written by Ulf Lofgren, this book is a delightful addition to any child&amp;rsquo;s bedtime routine. Target Age Group: The book is primarily aimed at children between the ages of 3 to 7 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bedtime for Frances</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/bedtime_for_frances_by_russell_hoban_isbn_9780571052745/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/bedtime_for_frances_by_russell_hoban_isbn_9780571052745/</guid>
      <description>Bedtime for Frances by Russell Hoban Title: Bedtime for Frances Author: Russell Hoban Review: Bedtime for Frances is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Russell Hoban. The story follows a young badger named Frances who is reluctant to go to bed, as she is afraid of the dark and monsters under her bed. With the help of her loving and patient parents, Frances learns to overcome her fears and embrace bedtime.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fly, Little Bird</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/fly_little_bird_by_francesco_tullio_altan_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/fly_little_bird_by_francesco_tullio_altan_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Fly, Little Bird by Francesco Tullio Altan Title: Fly, Little Bird Author: Francesco Tullio Altan Fly, Little Bird is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book by Francesco Tullio Altan that tells the story of a young bird who dreams of flying high and exploring the world. The book is perfect for children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old, as it is filled with colorful illustrations and simple, yet engaging language.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peter in Blueberry Land</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/peter_in_blueberry_land_by_elsa_beskow_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/peter_in_blueberry_land_by_elsa_beskow_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Peter in Blueberry Land by Elsa Beskow Title: Peter in Blueberry Land Author: Elsa Beskow Review: &amp;ldquo;Peter in Blueberry Land&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book by the renowned Swedish author and illustrator, Elsa Beskow. The story follows Peter, a young boy who embarks on a magical adventure in a land filled with talking blueberries and other enchanting creatures. This charming book is perfect for children aged 4 to 8 years old, as it captivates their imaginations and teaches them valuable life lessons.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
