<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Childrens Books that talk about &#39;Expelled&#39; on Monsty The Monster Truck</title>
    <link>https://www.monsty.co/tags/childrens-books-that-talk-about-expelled/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Childrens Books that talk about &#39;Expelled&#39; on Monsty The Monster Truck</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.monsty.co/tags/childrens-books-that-talk-about-expelled/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Alex</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/alex_by_tessa_duder_isbn_9780195581690/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/alex_by_tessa_duder_isbn_9780195581690/</guid>
      <description>Alex by Tessa Duder Title: Alex Author: Tessa Duder Review: &amp;ldquo;Alex&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Tessa Duder, which follows the adventures of a young girl named Alex as she navigates the challenges of growing up. The book is a perfect fit for children between the ages of 8 and 12, as it addresses themes that are relatable to this age group, such as friendship, self-discovery, and overcoming obstacles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Chocolate War</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_chocolate_war_by_robert_cormier_isbn_9781400089963/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_chocolate_war_by_robert_cormier_isbn_9781400089963/</guid>
      <description>The Chocolate War by Robert Cormier Title: The Chocolate War Author: Robert Cormier Genre: Young Adult Fiction, Coming-of-Age Novel Recommended Age Group: 12-18 years old The Chocolate War, written by Robert Cormier, is a gripping and thought-provoking coming-of-age novel that delves into the complexities of adolescent life. This book is a must-read for young adults aged 12-18, as it addresses themes of individuality, conformity, and the consequences of standing up for one&amp;rsquo;s beliefs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tom Sawyer</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/tom_sawyer_isbn_9798417467929/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/tom_sawyer_isbn_9798417467929/</guid>
      <description>Tom Sawyer Title: The Adventures of Tom Sawyer Author: Mark Twain Review: The Adventures of Tom Sawyer is a timeless classic written by Mark Twain, which takes the reader on a thrilling journey through the eyes of a young boy named Tom Sawyer. The story is set in the small town of St. Petersburg, Missouri, and follows Tom&amp;rsquo;s adventures with his friends, particularly Huckleberry Finn. The book is suitable for children between the ages of 8 and 12, as it contains elements of fun, mischief, and learning.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
