<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Childrens Books that talk about &#39;Endure&#39; on Monsty The Monster Truck</title>
    <link>https://www.monsty.co/tags/childrens-books-that-talk-about-endure/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Childrens Books that talk about &#39;Endure&#39; on Monsty The Monster Truck</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.monsty.co/tags/childrens-books-that-talk-about-endure/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Refugee Boy</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/refugee_boy_by_benjamin_zephaniah_isbn_1408825406/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/refugee_boy_by_benjamin_zephaniah_isbn_1408825406/</guid>
      <description>Refugee Boy by Benjamin Zephaniah Title: Refugee Boy Author: Benjamin Zephaniah Target Age Group: 9-12 years old Review: Refugee Boy is a poignant and thought-provoking children&amp;rsquo;s book by Benjamin Zephaniah that tells the story of a young boy named Alem, who is forced to flee his war-torn country and seek asylum in the United Kingdom. The book is written in a simple yet engaging manner, making it accessible to young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Devil&#39;s Arithmetic</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_devils_arithmetic_by_jane_yolen_isbn_9781664495296/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_devils_arithmetic_by_jane_yolen_isbn_9781664495296/</guid>
      <description>The Devil&amp;rsquo;s Arithmetic by Jane Yolen Title: The Devil&amp;rsquo;s Arithmetic Author: Jane Yolen Review: The Devil&amp;rsquo;s Arithmetic, written by Jane Yolen, is a poignant and thought-provoking children&amp;rsquo;s book that delves into the harsh realities of the Holocaust. The story follows a young girl named Hannah, who is transported back in time to a concentration camp during the Holocaust. Through her experiences, she learns the importance of remembering and honoring the past, as well as the value of courage and resilience in the face of adversity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Machine Gunners</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_machine_gunners_isbn_033033428x/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_machine_gunners_isbn_033033428x/</guid>
      <description>The Machine Gunners Title: The Machine Gunners Author: Robert Westall Review: The Machine Gunners is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Robert Westall, which takes the reader on a thrilling journey through the lives of a group of young friends living in the midst of World War II. The story is set in the north of England and follows the adventures of a group of children who discover a German machine gun in the wreckage of a downed aircraft.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Stowaway of the Ulysses</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_stowaway_of_the_ulysses_by_ana_maria_matute_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_stowaway_of_the_ulysses_by_ana_maria_matute_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Stowaway of the Ulysses by Ana Maria Matute Title: The Stowaway of the Ulysses Author: Ana Maria Matute Review: The Stowaway of the Ulysses is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young boy named David who embarks on a thrilling adventure aboard the ship Ulysses. The book is suitable for children aged 8-12 years old, as it contains elements of excitement, friendship, and self-discovery that will appeal to this age group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Poordog the Starved</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/poordog_the_starved_by_graciela_montes_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/poordog_the_starved_by_graciela_montes_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Poordog the Starved by Graciela Montes Title: Poordog the Starved Author: Graciela Montes Poordog the Starved is a heartwarming and engaging children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Graciela Montes. This beautifully illustrated story follows the life of a little dog named Poordog, who struggles to find food and shelter in a world that seems to have forgotten him. The book targets children aged 6-10 years old and offers valuable life lessons about empathy, resilience, and the importance of helping others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schoolboy Jia Li</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/schoolboy_jia_li_by_qin_wenjun_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/schoolboy_jia_li_by_qin_wenjun_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Schoolboy Jia Li by Qin Wenjun Title: Schoolboy Jia Li Author: Qin Wenjun Schoolboy Jia Li is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Qin Wenjun, which follows the story of a young boy named Jia Li as he navigates through the ups and downs of school life. This heartwarming tale is perfect for children between the ages of 6 and 10, as it addresses various life lessons and challenges that young readers can relate to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Old Yeller</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/old_yeller_isbn_9780061070082/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/old_yeller_isbn_9780061070082/</guid>
      <description>Old Yeller Title: Old Yeller Author: Phyllis Reynolds Naylor Review: Old Yeller is a heartwarming and engaging children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young boy named Travis and his loyal dog, Old Yeller. Set in the 1860s in the Texas wilderness, the book is filled with adventure, friendship, and valuable life lessons. The story is suitable for children aged 8-12, as it deals with themes of responsibility, bravery, and the importance of family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Little Prince</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_little_prince_isbn_9583002585/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_little_prince_isbn_9583002585/</guid>
      <description>The Little Prince Title: The Little Prince Author: Antoine de Saint-Exupéry Age Group: 8-12 years old &amp;ldquo;The Little Prince&amp;rdquo; is a timeless classic that has captured the hearts of readers of all ages. The story, written by Antoine de Saint-Exupéry, is a beautifully crafted tale that explores the complexities of life, love, and the human experience through the eyes of a young prince visiting different planets. The book is primarily targeted at children between the ages of 8 and 12, but its universal themes and lessons make it an enjoyable read for adults as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sleep Well, Little Bear</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/sleep_well_little_bear_by_quint_buckholz_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/sleep_well_little_bear_by_quint_buckholz_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Sleep Well, Little Bear by Quint Buckholz Title: Sleep Well, Little Bear Author: Quint Buckholz Sleep Well, Little Bear is a beautifully illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young bear named Little Bear who is having trouble sleeping. The book is written by Quint Buckholz and is perfect for children between the ages of 3 to 8 years old. The story begins with Little Bear feeling restless and unable to sleep.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazing Grace</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/amazing_grace_isbn_9781423320166/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/amazing_grace_isbn_9781423320166/</guid>
      <description>Amazing Grace Title: Amazing Grace Author: Mary Hoffman Illustrator: Caroline Binch Amazing Grace is a beautifully illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young girl named Grace who loves to act out stories and dreams of being in a play. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 4 to 8 years old, as it features simple language and engaging illustrations that will capture the attention of young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little Blue and Little Yellow</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/little_blue_and_little_yellow_by_leo_lionni_isbn_9780340035764/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/little_blue_and_little_yellow_by_leo_lionni_isbn_9780340035764/</guid>
      <description>Little Blue and Little Yellow by Leo Lionni Title: Little Blue and Little Yellow Author: Leo Lionni Review: Little Blue and Little Yellow is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written and illustrated by Leo Lionni. The story follows the adventures of two friends, Little Blue and Little Yellow, who are both colors. Throughout the book, they learn about the importance of friendship, acceptance, and embracing change. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 4 to 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
