<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Childrens Books that talk about &#39;Persist&#39; on Monsty The Monster Truck</title>
    <link>https://www.monsty.co/tags/childrens-books-that-talk-about-persist/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Childrens Books that talk about &#39;Persist&#39; on Monsty The Monster Truck</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.monsty.co/tags/childrens-books-that-talk-about-persist/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Holes</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/holes_isbn_374332665/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/holes_isbn_374332665/</guid>
      <description>Holes Title: Holes Author: Louis Sachar Review: Holes is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s novel written by Louis Sachar, which tells the story of Stanley Yelnats, a young boy who is wrongly accused of stealing a pair of sneakers and is sent to a juvenile detention center called Camp Green Lake. The book is filled with adventure, mystery, and humor, making it an enjoyable read for children aged 8-12. One of the key life lessons covered in the book is the importance of perseverance and determination.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Switchers</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/switchers_by_kate_thompson_isbn_9781480424203/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/switchers_by_kate_thompson_isbn_9781480424203/</guid>
      <description>Switchers by Kate Thompson Title: Switchers Author: Kate Thompson Review: Switchers is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the adventures of two young teenagers, Tess and Kevin, who discover they have the ability to &amp;lsquo;switch&amp;rsquo; into the bodies of other creatures. The story is set in Ireland and beautifully captures the essence of Irish folklore and mythology. The target age group for this book is 8-12 years old. The language used is simple yet engaging, making it an enjoyable read for young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Crowstarver</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_crowstarver_by_dick_king-smith_isbn_9780385410083/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_crowstarver_by_dick_king-smith_isbn_9780385410083/</guid>
      <description>The Crowstarver by Dick King-Smith Title: The Crowstarver Author: Dick King-Smith The Crowstarver is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the talented author Dick King-Smith. This book is an excellent choice for young readers between the ages of 8 and 12. The story follows the life of a young boy named Simon, who discovers a mysterious creature called a Crowstarver. The Crowstarver is a shape-shifting creature that can change its appearance to suit its surroundings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Handles</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/handles_isbn_9781708024031/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/handles_isbn_9781708024031/</guid>
      <description>Handles Title: Handles Author: Jane Doe Review: Handles is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that captures the hearts of young readers with its engaging story and beautiful illustrations. The book, written by Jane Doe, is a perfect fit for children aged 4 to 8 years old. The story revolves around a lovable character named Handles, who is a little boy with a big heart. Handles goes on an adventure in his small town, where he encounters various challenges and learns valuable life lessons along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jolanda, Daughter of the Black Corsair</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/jolanda_daughter_of_the_black_corsair_by_emilio_salgari_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/jolanda_daughter_of_the_black_corsair_by_emilio_salgari_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Jolanda, Daughter of the Black Corsair by Emilio Salgari Title: Jolanda, Daughter of the Black Corsair Author: Emilio Salgari Review: Jolanda, Daughter of the Black Corsair is a thrilling adventure story that follows the life of a young girl named Jolanda, who is the daughter of the infamous Black Corsair. This book is a perfect fit for children between the ages of 8 and 12, as it is filled with exciting pirate adventures, mysterious islands, and valuable life lessons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Something&#39;s Fishy, Hazel Green!</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/somethings_fishy_hazel_green_by_odo_hirsch_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/somethings_fishy_hazel_green_by_odo_hirsch_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Something&amp;rsquo;s Fishy, Hazel Green! by Odo Hirsch Title: Something&amp;rsquo;s Fishy, Hazel Green! Author: Odo Hirsch Review: &amp;ldquo;Something&amp;rsquo;s Fishy, Hazel Green!&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Odo Hirsch, which takes readers on a captivating journey through the eyes of its protagonist, Hazel Green. The story follows Hazel as she sets out to uncover the mystery behind a peculiar smell that has been plaguing her school. The book is primarily targeted towards children between the ages of 7 to 10 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mufaro&#39;s Beautiful Daughters</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/mufaros_beautiful_daughters_isbn_1591123178/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/mufaros_beautiful_daughters_isbn_1591123178/</guid>
      <description>Mufaro&amp;rsquo;s Beautiful Daughters Title: Mufaro&amp;rsquo;s Beautiful Daughters Author: John Steptoe Recommended Age Group: 4-8 years old &amp;ldquo;Mufaro&amp;rsquo;s Beautiful Daughters&amp;rdquo; is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book written and illustrated by John Steptoe. This African folktale, set in the land of Zimbabwe, tells the story of two sisters, Nyasha and Manyara, who are both vying for the attention of the king, who is seeking a bride. The book beautifully highlights the importance of inner beauty, kindness, and compassion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bridge to Terabithia</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/bridge_to_terabithia_isbn_9786051732077/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/bridge_to_terabithia_isbn_9786051732077/</guid>
      <description>Bridge to Terabithia Title: Bridge to Terabithia Author: Katherine Paterson Review: Bridge to Terabithia is a captivating and heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s novel written by Katherine Paterson. The story follows the lives of two young protagonists, Jess Aarons and Leslie Burke, as they embark on a journey of friendship, imagination, and self-discovery. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old. The themes and life lessons presented in the story are relatable and relevant to this age group, making it an excellent choice for young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boxcar Children</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/boxcar_children_isbn_606041761/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/boxcar_children_isbn_606041761/</guid>
      <description>Boxcar Children Title: The Boxcar Children Author: Gertrude Chandler Warner Review: The Boxcar Children is a timeless classic that has captured the hearts of young readers for generations. Written by Gertrude Chandler Warner, this book tells the story of four orphaned siblings - Henry, Jessie, Violet, and Benny - who create a home for themselves in an abandoned boxcar. The target age group for this book is children between the ages of 7 and 10.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kubula and Kuba Kubikula</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/kubula_and_kuba_kubikula_by_vladisla_vancura_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/kubula_and_kuba_kubikula_by_vladisla_vancura_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Kubula and Kuba Kubikula by Vladisla Vancura Title: Kubula and Kuba Kubikula Author: Vladislav Vancura Review: Kubula and Kuba Kubikula is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Vladislav Vancura. The story follows the adventures of two young friends, Kubula and Kuba Kubikula, as they explore their world and learn valuable life lessons along the way. The book is beautifully illustrated, with vibrant colors and engaging images that capture the imagination of young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Henry and Amy</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/henry_and_amy_by_stephen_michael_king_isbn_802786871/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/henry_and_amy_by_stephen_michael_king_isbn_802786871/</guid>
      <description>Henry and Amy by Stephen Michael King Title: Henry and Amy Author: Stephen Michael King Target Age Group: 4-8 years old Henry and Amy is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book written and illustrated by the talented Stephen Michael King. The story revolves around the friendship between a young boy named Henry and a magical, flying pig named Amy. Together, they embark on a series of adventures, learning valuable life lessons along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Will Not Ever Never Eat a Tomato</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/i_will_not_ever_never_eat_a_tomato_by_lauren_child_isbn_9780763611880/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/i_will_not_ever_never_eat_a_tomato_by_lauren_child_isbn_9780763611880/</guid>
      <description>I Will Not Ever Never Eat a Tomato by Lauren Child Title: I Will Not Ever Never Eat a Tomato Author: Lauren Child Review: &amp;ldquo;I Will Not Ever Never Eat a Tomato&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Lauren Child, targeting young readers between the ages of 4 to 8 years old. The story revolves around a young girl named Lola, who is very particular about her food choices and refuses to eat anything that is not her favorite.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Day the Babies Crawled Away</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_day_the_babies_crawled_away_by_peggy_rathman_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_day_the_babies_crawled_away_by_peggy_rathman_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Day the Babies Crawled Away by Peggy Rathman Title: The Day the Babies Crawled Away Author: Peggy Rathman Genre: Children&amp;rsquo;s Fiction, Picture Book Recommended Age Group: 4-8 years old The Day the Babies Crawled Away is a delightful and engaging children&amp;rsquo;s book written and illustrated by Peggy Rathman. This book tells the story of a group of babies who decide to crawl away from their families and embark on a grand adventure together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lilly&#39;s Purple Plastic Purse</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/lillys_purple_plastic_purse_isbn_8949110008/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/lillys_purple_plastic_purse_isbn_8949110008/</guid>
      <description>Lilly&amp;rsquo;s Purple Plastic Purse Title: Lilly&amp;rsquo;s Purple Plastic Purse Author: Kevin Henkes Target Age Group: 4-8 years old Lilly&amp;rsquo;s Purple Plastic Purse is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written and illustrated by Kevin Henkes. The story follows the adventures of Lilly, a young mouse with a big personality, and her treasured purple plastic purse. The book is perfect for children aged 4-8 years old, as it teaches valuable life lessons through a fun and engaging story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oh, the Places You&#39;ll Go</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/oh_the_places_youll_go_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/oh_the_places_youll_go_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Oh, the Places You&amp;rsquo;ll Go Title: Oh, the Places You&amp;rsquo;ll Go Author: Dr. Seuss Review: Oh, the Places You&amp;rsquo;ll Go is a delightful and inspiring children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the beloved author Dr. Seuss. This book is perfect for children aged 4 to 8 years old, as it captures their imagination and teaches valuable life lessons in a fun and engaging way. The story follows the journey of a young character as they navigate through the ups and downs of life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Nest</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/best_nest_by_pd_eastman_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/best_nest_by_pd_eastman_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Best Nest by PD Eastman Title: Best Nest Author: P.D. Eastman &amp;ldquo;Best Nest&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by P.D. Eastman, which follows the story of a bird named Peter who is on a quest to find the perfect nest. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 3 to 7 years old, as it features simple and engaging illustrations, as well as easy-to-understand language. The story begins with Peter&amp;rsquo;s dissatisfaction with his current nest, which he deems too small and uncomfortable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Story of the Little Mole</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_story_of_the_little_mole_by_werner_holzwarth_isbn_9781856025256/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_story_of_the_little_mole_by_werner_holzwarth_isbn_9781856025256/</guid>
      <description>The Story of the Little Mole by Werner Holzwarth Title: The Story of the Little Mole Author: Werner Holzwarth The Story of the Little Mole is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Werner Holzwarth, which tells the story of a curious little mole who sets out on an adventure to discover the world above ground. The book is beautifully illustrated by Wolf Erlbruch, adding a charming and whimsical touch to the story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where&#39;s My Teddy</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/wheres_my_teddy_by_jez_alborough_isbn_1564020487/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/wheres_my_teddy_by_jez_alborough_isbn_1564020487/</guid>
      <description>Where&amp;rsquo;s My Teddy by Jez Alborough Title: Where&amp;rsquo;s My Teddy Author: Jez Alborough Review: Where&amp;rsquo;s My Teddy is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written and illustrated by Jez Alborough. The story revolves around a young boy named Eddie who loses his teddy bear, Freddy, and embarks on a journey to find him. Along the way, Eddie encounters various animals who help him in his quest, each teaching him valuable life lessons. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 3 and 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crocodile Beat</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/crocodile_beat_by_gail_jorgensen_isbn_689718810/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/crocodile_beat_by_gail_jorgensen_isbn_689718810/</guid>
      <description>Crocodile Beat by Gail Jorgensen Title: Crocodile Beat Author: Gail Jorgensen Crocodile Beat is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Gail Jorgensen, which takes the reader on an adventurous journey into the world of a young crocodile named Croc. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 4 to 8 years old and is filled with vibrant illustrations that capture the imagination of young readers. The story follows Croc as he learns to play the drums and eventually forms a band with his animal friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slinky Malinki</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/slinky_malinki_by_lynley_dodd_isbn_9780907349747/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/slinky_malinki_by_lynley_dodd_isbn_9780907349747/</guid>
      <description>Slinky Malinki by Lynley Dodd Title: Slinky Malinki Author: Lynley Dodd Review: Slinky Malinki is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Lynley Dodd, which follows the adventures of a mischievous cat named Slinky Malinki. The story is engaging and fun, making it a perfect read for children between the ages of 3 to 7 years old. The book&amp;rsquo;s illustrations are vibrant and captivating, which adds to the overall charm of the story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Green Eggs and Ham</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/green_eggs_and_ham_isbn_1717952/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/green_eggs_and_ham_isbn_1717952/</guid>
      <description>Green Eggs and Ham Title: Green Eggs and Ham Author: Dr. Seuss Review: Green Eggs and Ham is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the renowned author Dr. Seuss. This book is a classic and has been enjoyed by children for generations. The story follows the adventures of Sam-I-Am, who tries to convince an unnamed character to try green eggs and ham. The unnamed character is initially hesitant, but eventually gives in and ends up enjoying the dish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lyle, Lyle Crocodile</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/lyle_lyle_crocodile_by_bernard_waber_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/lyle_lyle_crocodile_by_bernard_waber_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Lyle, Lyle Crocodile by Bernard Waber Title: Lyle, Lyle Crocodile Author: Bernard Waber Review: Lyle, Lyle Crocodile is a charming and delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Bernard Waber. The story revolves around a friendly crocodile named Lyle, who lives in a house on East 88th Street in New York City with the Primm family. Lyle loves to sing and perform, and he becomes a beloved member of the community. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Cat in the Hat</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_cat_in_the_hat_by_dr._seuss_isbn_000820151x/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_cat_in_the_hat_by_dr._seuss_isbn_000820151x/</guid>
      <description>The Cat in the Hat by Dr. Seuss Title: The Cat in the Hat Author: Dr. Seuss Review: The Cat in the Hat is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the renowned author Dr. Seuss. The story follows the adventures of a mischievous cat who visits two children, Sally and her brother, on a rainy day. The Cat in the Hat teaches valuable life lessons while keeping the reader entertained with its whimsical rhymes and colorful illustrations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Handa&#39;s Surprise</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/handas_surprise_by_eileen_browne_isbn_9781852694784/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/handas_surprise_by_eileen_browne_isbn_9781852694784/</guid>
      <description>Handa&amp;rsquo;s Surprise by Eileen Browne Title: Handa&amp;rsquo;s Surprise Author: Eileen Browne Handa&amp;rsquo;s Surprise is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Eileen Browne. The story follows Handa, a young girl from Kenya, as she visits her grandmother and embarks on a journey to surprise her with a special gift. The book is beautifully illustrated with vibrant colors and detailed pictures, which help bring the story to life. The target age group for this book is children between 4 to 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Baby&#39;s Catalogue</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_babys_catalogue_by_allan_ahlberg_isbn_9780316020381/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_babys_catalogue_by_allan_ahlberg_isbn_9780316020381/</guid>
      <description>The Baby&amp;rsquo;s Catalogue by Allan Ahlberg Title: The Baby&amp;rsquo;s Catalogue Author: Allan Ahlberg Review: The Baby&amp;rsquo;s Catalogue is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Allan Ahlberg, which takes young readers on a fun and engaging journey through the world of babies and their various belongings. The book is beautifully illustrated with vibrant and colorful pictures, which will surely capture the attention of young children. The Baby&amp;rsquo;s Catalogue is targeted towards children between the ages of 2 and 5 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Tale of Mr Jeremy Fisher</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_tale_of_mr_jeremy_fisher_by_beatrix_potter_isbn_9780723244257/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_tale_of_mr_jeremy_fisher_by_beatrix_potter_isbn_9780723244257/</guid>
      <description>The Tale of Mr Jeremy Fisher by Beatrix Potter Title: The Tale of Mr. Jeremy Fisher Author: Beatrix Potter Review: The Tale of Mr. Jeremy Fisher is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Beatrix Potter, a renowned author and illustrator. The story revolves around Mr. Jeremy Fisher, a frog who lives in a beautiful pond and is on a quest to find a tasty meal. Throughout the book, readers are taken on a journey with Mr.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
