<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Childrens Books that talk about &#39;Embrace&#39; on Monsty The Monster Truck</title>
    <link>https://www.monsty.co/tags/childrens-books-that-talk-about-embrace/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Childrens Books that talk about &#39;Embrace&#39; on Monsty The Monster Truck</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.monsty.co/tags/childrens-books-that-talk-about-embrace/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bud, Not Buddy</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/bud_not_buddy_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/bud_not_buddy_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Bud, Not Buddy Title: Bud, Not Buddy Author: Christopher Paul Curtis Review: Bud, Not Buddy is a heartwarming and adventurous story about a 10-year-old boy named Bud Caldwell, who embarks on a journey to find his father. Set in the 1930s during the Great Depression, the book takes readers on a rollercoaster of emotions as Bud encounters various obstacles and makes new friends along the way. The target age group for this book is 8-12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grimpow</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/grimpow_by_rafael_abalos_isbn_9788483462386/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/grimpow_by_rafael_abalos_isbn_9788483462386/</guid>
      <description>Grimpow by Rafael Abalos Title: Grimpow Author: Rafael Abalos Review: Grimpow is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Rafael Abalos, which takes readers on a magical journey through the eyes of its young protagonist. The story follows the adventures of Grimpow, a twelve-year-old boy who discovers a hidden world full of mystery and wonder. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 8 to 12 years old. The age-appropriate language and engaging plot make it an enjoyable read for this age group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peeling the Onion</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/peeling_the_onion_by_wendy_orr_isbn_9781741149333/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/peeling_the_onion_by_wendy_orr_isbn_9781741149333/</guid>
      <description>Peeling the Onion by Wendy Orr Title: Peeling the Onion Author: Wendy Orr Review: Peeling the Onion is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Wendy Orr, which takes the reader on a journey of self-discovery and friendship. The story revolves around a young girl named Mia, who struggles with the challenges of growing up and finding her place in the world. Target Age Group: The book is suitable for children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slaves of Quentaris</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/slaves_of_quentaris_by_paul_collins_isbn_9780734405579/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/slaves_of_quentaris_by_paul_collins_isbn_9780734405579/</guid>
      <description>Slaves of Quentaris by Paul Collins Title: Slaves of Quentaris Author: Paul Collins Slaves of Quentaris is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Paul Collins, which takes the reader on a thrilling adventure through the fantastical world of Quentaris. The story follows the journey of two young protagonists, Tilda and Tobin, who find themselves enslaved in the underground city of Quentaris. Target Age Group: The book is primarily targeted towards children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Illustrated Mum</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_illustrated_mum_isbn_9780385902632/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_illustrated_mum_isbn_9780385902632/</guid>
      <description>The Illustrated Mum Title: The Illustrated Mum Author: Jacqueline Wilson Review: The Illustrated Mum is a heartwarming and poignant children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of two sisters, Dolphin and Star, who navigate the challenges of growing up with a mother suffering from mental illness. The book is beautifully illustrated and the artwork complements the emotional depth of the story. The target age group for this book is children between the ages of 8 and 12.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Wind Singer</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_wind_singer_isbn_606246231/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_wind_singer_isbn_606246231/</guid>
      <description>The Wind Singer Title: The Wind Singer Author: William Nicholson Genre: Children&amp;rsquo;s Fantasy Fiction Recommended Age Group: 8-12 years old The Wind Singer is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s fantasy novel by William Nicholson that tells the story of a young girl named Kestrel, her brother Bowman, and their friend Mumpo, as they embark on a thrilling adventure to save their city from the destructive force of the evil Morah. The book is set in the dystopian city of Aramanth, where the people&amp;rsquo;s lives are controlled by a system of tests and rankings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toby Alone</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/toby_alone_by_timothee_de_fombelle_isbn_1441888837/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/toby_alone_by_timothee_de_fombelle_isbn_1441888837/</guid>
      <description>Toby Alone by Timothee De Fombelle Title: Toby Alone Author: Timothee De Fombelle Review: Toby Alone is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Timothee De Fombelle, which tells the story of a young boy named Toby who lives in a world of miniature people hidden within the trees. The book is a perfect blend of adventure, friendship, and courage, making it an ideal read for children between the ages of 8 and 12.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Walking Naked</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/walking_naked_by_alyssa_brugman_isbn_385901410/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/walking_naked_by_alyssa_brugman_isbn_385901410/</guid>
      <description>Walking Naked by Alyssa Brugman Title: Walking Naked Author: Alyssa Brugman Review: Walking Naked is a beautifully written children&amp;rsquo;s book by Alyssa Brugman, which is suitable for children between the ages of 8 and 12. The story follows the life of a young girl named Nina, who is trying to find her place in the world and navigate the challenges of growing up. The book tackles various life lessons, such as the importance of self-acceptance, empathy, and resilience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brother in the Land</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/brother_in_the_land_by_robert_swindells_isbn_9780140317985/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/brother_in_the_land_by_robert_swindells_isbn_9780140317985/</guid>
      <description>Brother in the Land by Robert Swindells Title: Brother in the Land Author: Robert Swindells Target Age Group: 10-14 years old &amp;ldquo;Brother in the Land&amp;rdquo; is a poignant and thought-provoking novel by Robert Swindells that delves into the harsh realities of a post-apocalyptic world. The story is set in a small town in northern England, where the devastating effects of a nuclear war have left the landscape barren and the community struggling to survive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dear Nobody</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/dear_nobody_isbn_531086119/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/dear_nobody_isbn_531086119/</guid>
      <description>Dear Nobody Title: Dear Nobody Author: Berlie Doherty Recommended Age Group: 8-12 years old Dear Nobody is a heartwarming and thought-provoking children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Berlie Doherty. The story revolves around two main characters, Helen and Chris, who are both dealing with the challenges of growing up and navigating their emotions. The book is written in a diary format, with Helen and Chris taking turns to share their thoughts and feelings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hating Alison Ashley</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/hating_alison_ashley_isbn_440842980/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/hating_alison_ashley_isbn_440842980/</guid>
      <description>Hating Alison Ashley Title: Hating Alison Ashley Author: Judith Rossner Genre: Children&amp;rsquo;s Fiction, Coming-of-Age Recommended Age Group: 8-12 years old &amp;ldquo;Hating Alison Ashley&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Judith Rossner that takes young readers on a journey of self-discovery, friendship, and acceptance. The story follows the life of Erica, a young girl who struggles with jealousy and insecurity as she compares herself to the seemingly perfect Alison Ashley. Throughout the book, Erica learns valuable life lessons about embracing one&amp;rsquo;s unique qualities, appreciating the people around her, and finding happiness in her own accomplishments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>There Will Be Wolves</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/there_will_be_wolves_by_karleen_bradford_isbn_9780525675396/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/there_will_be_wolves_by_karleen_bradford_isbn_9780525675396/</guid>
      <description>There Will Be Wolves by Karleen Bradford Title: There Will Be Wolves Author: Karleen Bradford Review: There Will Be Wolves is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Karleen Bradford, which tells the story of a young boy named Connor who is forced to confront his fears and overcome challenges in a thrilling adventure. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 8 and 12, and it teaches valuable life lessons about courage, resilience, and the importance of family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thunderwith</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/thunderwith_by_libby_hathorn_isbn_732005566/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/thunderwith_by_libby_hathorn_isbn_732005566/</guid>
      <description>Thunderwith by Libby Hathorn Title: Thunderwith Author: Libby Hathorn Thunderwith is a beautifully written children&amp;rsquo;s book by Libby Hathorn that captures the imagination of young readers with its enchanting storytelling and vivid illustrations. The book is primarily targeted towards children between the ages of 6 and 10 years old, making it an excellent choice for elementary school students. The story follows the adventures of a young boy named Tim, who discovers a magical world filled with talking animals and a powerful storm called Thunderwith.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Walk Two Moons</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/walk_two_moons_isbn_9780590649438/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/walk_two_moons_isbn_9780590649438/</guid>
      <description>Walk Two Moons Title: Walk Two Moons Author: Sharon Creech Review: Walk Two Moons is a beautifully written children&amp;rsquo;s novel by Sharon Creech, which tells the story of a young girl named Salamanca Tree Hiddle, who embarks on a journey to find her missing mother. The book is an engaging and thought-provoking read that explores themes of family, friendship, and the power of storytelling. Target Age Group: The book is suitable for children aged 9-12 years old, as it contains relatable themes and characters that resonate well with this age group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When the World Was Still Young</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/when_the_world_was_still_young_by_jurg_schubiger_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/when_the_world_was_still_young_by_jurg_schubiger_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>When the World Was Still Young by Jurg Schubiger Title: When the World Was Still Young Author: Jurg Schubiger Review: When the World Was Still Young is a beautifully illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young boy named Jonas who embarks on a magical adventure. The book is suitable for children between the ages of 6 and 10 years old. The story follows Jonas as he discovers a hidden door in his grandfather&amp;rsquo;s attic, which leads him to a world where time has stopped.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whispers in the Graveyard</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/whispers_in_the_graveyard_isbn_749744804/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/whispers_in_the_graveyard_isbn_749744804/</guid>
      <description>Whispers in the Graveyard Title: Whispers in the Graveyard Author: Theresa Breslin Target Age Group: 8-12 years old &amp;ldquo;Whispers in the Graveyard&amp;rdquo; is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Theresa Breslin, which tells the story of a young boy named Solomon who possesses a unique gift – he can hear the whispers of the dead. The book is suitable for children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old, and it offers valuable life lessons that can help them navigate through various challenges in life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Long Way From Verona</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/a_long_way_from_verona_by_jane_gardam_isbn_349114056/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/a_long_way_from_verona_by_jane_gardam_isbn_349114056/</guid>
      <description>A Long Way From Verona by Jane Gardam Title: A Long Way From Verona Author: Jane Gardam Review: A Long Way From Verona is a delightful and thought-provoking children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Jane Gardam. The story follows the life of a young girl named Betty Carpenter, who is growing up in a small village during World War II. The book is an engaging read for children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old, as it covers themes such as friendship, family, and resilience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Agnes Cecilia</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/agnes_cecilia_by_maria_gripe_isbn_60222816/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/agnes_cecilia_by_maria_gripe_isbn_60222816/</guid>
      <description>Agnes Cecilia by Maria Gripe Title: Agnes Cecilia Author: Maria Gripe Review: Agnes Cecilia is a beautifully written children&amp;rsquo;s book by Maria Gripe that tells the story of a young girl named Agnes Cecilia. The book is perfect for children aged 8-12 years old and provides valuable life lessons throughout the story. The story follows Agnes Cecilia, a young girl who lives in a small village with her family. She is a curious and adventurous child who loves to explore the world around her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dragonsong</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/dragonsong_isbn_689860234/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/dragonsong_isbn_689860234/</guid>
      <description>Dragonsong Title: Dragonsong Author: Anne McCaffrey Target Age Group: 8-12 years old Dragonsong is a delightful and enchanting children&amp;rsquo;s book that transports young readers into the magical world of Pern. The story follows the journey of Menolly, a young girl with a passion for music, as she navigates the challenges of her society and discovers her true calling. One of the key strengths of this book is its ability to captivate the imagination of its young audience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sounder</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/sounder_isbn_575006536/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/sounder_isbn_575006536/</guid>
      <description>Sounder Title: Sounder Author: William H. Armstrong Review: Sounder is a heartwarming and thought-provoking children&amp;rsquo;s book written by William H. Armstrong. The story is set in the rural South during the early 1900s and follows the life of a young African American boy named David and his loyal dog, Sounder. The book primarily targets children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old. It is a great read for this age group as it touches upon themes of family, friendship, and perseverance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Chocolate War</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_chocolate_war_by_robert_cormier_isbn_9781400089963/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_chocolate_war_by_robert_cormier_isbn_9781400089963/</guid>
      <description>The Chocolate War by Robert Cormier Title: The Chocolate War Author: Robert Cormier Genre: Young Adult Fiction, Coming-of-Age Novel Recommended Age Group: 12-18 years old The Chocolate War, written by Robert Cormier, is a gripping and thought-provoking coming-of-age novel that delves into the complexities of adolescent life. This book is a must-read for young adults aged 12-18, as it addresses themes of individuality, conformity, and the consequences of standing up for one&amp;rsquo;s beliefs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Friends</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_friends_by_rosa_guy_isbn_9780808554028/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_friends_by_rosa_guy_isbn_9780808554028/</guid>
      <description>The Friends by Rosa Guy Title: The Friends Author: Rosa Guy Review: The Friends is a heartwarming and thought-provoking children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Rosa Guy. This book is a perfect fit for children aged 8-12 years old, as it delves into themes of friendship, understanding, and acceptance. The story revolves around two young girls, Phyllisia and Celie, who come from different cultural backgrounds but develop a strong bond of friendship. Throughout the book, the author beautifully portrays the importance of embracing diversity and understanding the experiences of others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Lark and the Laurel</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_lark_and_the_laurel_by_barbara_willard_isbn_356131696/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_lark_and_the_laurel_by_barbara_willard_isbn_356131696/</guid>
      <description>The Lark and the Laurel by Barbara Willard Title: The Lark and the Laurel Author: Barbara Willard Review: The Lark and the Laurel is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Barbara Willard. The story revolves around the adventures of a young lark and a laurel tree, both of whom face various challenges and learn valuable life lessons along the way. The book is targeted towards children aged 6 to 10 years old, as it contains beautiful illustrations and a simple yet engaging narrative that captures the imagination of young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Neverending Story</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_neverending_story_isbn_9780140076196/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_neverending_story_isbn_9780140076196/</guid>
      <description>The Neverending Story Title: The Neverending Story Author: Michael Ende The Neverending Story is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Michael Ende, which takes the reader on a magical journey through the world of Fantastica. This enchanting tale is perfect for children between the ages of 8 and 12, as it offers a perfect blend of adventure, fantasy, and valuable life lessons. The story revolves around a young boy named Bastian Balthazar Bux, who stumbles upon a mysterious book called &amp;ldquo;The Neverending Story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The October Child</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_october_child_by_eleanor_spence_isbn_340605480/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_october_child_by_eleanor_spence_isbn_340605480/</guid>
      <description>The October Child by Eleanor Spence Title: The October Child Author: Eleanor Spence Review: The October Child is a beautifully written and illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book that captures the essence of the changing seasons and the magic of childhood. The story follows a young girl named October, who is born on the first day of October and experiences the world around her through the lens of the changing seasons. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Peppermint Pig</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_peppermint_pig_by_nina_bawden_isbn_9780582186897/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_peppermint_pig_by_nina_bawden_isbn_9780582186897/</guid>
      <description>The Peppermint Pig by Nina Bawden Title: The Peppermint Pig Author: Nina Bawden Review: The Peppermint Pig is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Nina Bawden. The story follows the adventures of a family of mice, who live in a dollhouse, as they try to help their youngest member, Timothy, who is suffering from pneumonia. To save Timothy, the family decides to make a peppermint pig, a traditional English good luck charm, in the hopes that it will bring them good fortune and help Timothy recover.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tulku</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/tulku_isbn_9780140313574/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/tulku_isbn_9780140313574/</guid>
      <description>Tulku Title: Tulku Author: Pearl Zhu Review: &amp;ldquo;Tulku&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that captures the imagination of young readers with its enchanting story and vibrant illustrations. Author Pearl Zhu has crafted a heartwarming tale that follows the adventures of a young boy named Tulku, who embarks on a journey of self-discovery and friendship. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 5 and 10 years old. The language is simple and easy to understand, making it an excellent choice for early readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where the Lilies Bloom</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/where_the_lilies_bloom_isbn_881032913/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/where_the_lilies_bloom_isbn_881032913/</guid>
      <description>Where the Lilies Bloom Title: Where the Lilies Bloom Author: Vera Cleaver and Bill Cleaver Review: &amp;ldquo;Where the Lilies Bloom&amp;rdquo; is a heartwarming and inspiring children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a family living in the Appalachian Mountains. The story follows the lives of Mary Call, her siblings, and their struggle to survive after their father&amp;rsquo;s death. The book is suitable for children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Carry On, Mr. Bowditch</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/carry_on_mr._bowditch_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/carry_on_mr._bowditch_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Carry On, Mr. Bowditch Title: Carry On, Mr. Bowditch Author: Jean Lee Latham Recommended Age Group: 8-12 years old &amp;ldquo;Carry On, Mr. Bowditch&amp;rdquo; is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of Nathaniel Bowditch, a young boy who grew up to become a famous mathematician, astronomer, and navigator. This book is a perfect read for children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old, as it combines elements of adventure, history, and science.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emily Climbs</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/emily_climbs_isbn_1844089894/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/emily_climbs_isbn_1844089894/</guid>
      <description>Emily Climbs Title: Emily Climbs Author: L.M. Montgomery Emily Climbs is the second book in the Emily series by L.M. Montgomery, following the story of a young orphan girl named Emily Starr. The book is set in the early 20th century and takes place in the fictional town of New Moon, where Emily lives with her strict and traditional relatives. The story follows Emily&amp;rsquo;s journey as she navigates her way through adolescence, her passion for writing, and the challenges of growing up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Capture the Castle</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/i_capture_the_castle_by_dodie_smith_isbn_8379430069/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/i_capture_the_castle_by_dodie_smith_isbn_8379430069/</guid>
      <description>I Capture the Castle by Dodie Smith Title: I Capture the Castle Author: Dodie Smith Review: I Capture the Castle is a charming and delightful novel that captures the essence of childhood and the complexities of growing up. The story follows the adventures of Cassandra Mortmain, a young girl living in a crumbling castle with her family. As Cassandra navigates the ups and downs of life, she learns valuable lessons about love, friendship, and the importance of staying true to oneself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Cave Children</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_cave_children_by_alois_theodor_sonnleitner_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_cave_children_by_alois_theodor_sonnleitner_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Cave Children by Alois Theodor Sonnleitner Title: The Cave Children Author: Alois Theodor Sonnleitner Review: The Cave Children is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes readers on an adventurous journey through a world of imagination. The story follows a group of children who stumble upon a hidden cave and discover a magical new world filled with enchanting creatures and exciting challenges. Author Alois Theodor Sonnleitner has skillfully crafted a tale that is both engaging and educational, making it an ideal read for children between the ages of 7 and 12.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time of Trial</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/time_of_trial_isbn_9780192720429/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/time_of_trial_isbn_9780192720429/</guid>
      <description>Time of Trial Title: Time of Trial Author: C.S. Lakin Target Age Group: 8-12 years old Time of Trial is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by C.S. Lakin. The story follows the adventures of a young boy named Jadiel, who finds himself in a world where time is a valuable commodity. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 8 and 12, as it contains elements of adventure, mystery, and fantasy that are sure to engage young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aldabra</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/aldabra_by_silvana_gandolfi_isbn_849580865x/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/aldabra_by_silvana_gandolfi_isbn_849580865x/</guid>
      <description>Aldabra by Silvana Gandolfi Title: Aldabra Author: Silvana Gandolfi Review: Aldabra is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young boy named Al who lives on a remote island. The book is filled with beautiful illustrations and captivating storytelling that transports readers to a world of adventure and discovery. Target Age Group: Aldabra is best suited for children between the ages of 7 and 12. The book&amp;rsquo;s engaging narrative and relatable characters make it an enjoyable read for this age group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Barrumbi Kids</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/barrumbi_kids_by_leonie_norrington_isbn_9781862914964/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/barrumbi_kids_by_leonie_norrington_isbn_9781862914964/</guid>
      <description>Barrumbi Kids by Leonie Norrington Title: Barrumbi Kids Author: Leonie Norrington Review: Barrumbi Kids is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes young readers on an adventure through the Australian outback. The story follows the lives of four Indigenous children, each with their unique personalities and talents. Leonie Norrington has beautifully crafted a tale that not only entertains but also teaches valuable life lessons. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 7 and 12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cirque De Freak: A Living Nightmare</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/cirque_de_freak_a_living_nightmare_by_darren_shan_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/cirque_de_freak_a_living_nightmare_by_darren_shan_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Cirque De Freak: A Living Nightmare by Darren Shan Title: Cirque De Freak: A Living Nightmare Author: Darren Shan Review: Cirque De Freak: A Living Nightmare is a captivating and thrilling children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Darren Shan. The story follows the life of a young boy named Darren Shan, who becomes entangled in the mysterious world of vampires after attending a freak show with his best friend, Steve. The book is primarily targeted towards children between the ages of 10 to 14 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eclipse of the Crescent Moon</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/eclipse_of_the_crescent_moon_isbn_9789631343687/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/eclipse_of_the_crescent_moon_isbn_9789631343687/</guid>
      <description>Eclipse of the Crescent Moon Title: Eclipse of the Crescent Moon Author: John Sobol Illustrator: Derek Shapton Genre: Children&amp;rsquo;s Fiction, Historical Fiction Age Group: 8-12 years old Review: Eclipse of the Crescent Moon is a beautifully written and illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes readers on a captivating journey through a historical setting. The story is set in the 13th century, where a young boy named Nassir, living in a small village, dreams of adventure and excitement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Father Grew Wings in Spring</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/father_grew_wings_in_spring_by_tomi_kontio_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/father_grew_wings_in_spring_by_tomi_kontio_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Father Grew Wings in Spring by Tomi Kontio Title: Father Grew Wings in Spring Author: Tomi Kontio Review: &amp;ldquo;Father Grew Wings in Spring&amp;rdquo; is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Tomi Kontio that tells the story of a young boy named Jari, who loves to spend time with his father. The book is perfect for children between the ages of 5 and 10, as it explores themes of family, love, and the importance of cherishing every moment together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little Women</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/little_women_by_louisa_may_alcott_isbn_1974138135/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/little_women_by_louisa_may_alcott_isbn_1974138135/</guid>
      <description>Little Women by Louisa May Alcott Title: Little Women Author: Louisa May Alcott Little Women, written by Louisa May Alcott, is a timeless classic that has captured the hearts of readers for generations. This heartwarming novel tells the story of the March sisters - Meg, Jo, Beth, and Amy - as they navigate their lives during the American Civil War. The book is an excellent choice for children aged 8 to 12 years old, as it provides valuable life lessons and a glimpse into the lives of these remarkable young women.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Millions</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/millions_isbn_9781548920760/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/millions_isbn_9781548920760/</guid>
      <description>Millions Title: Millions Author: Matt Crowley Review: Millions is a heartwarming and thought-provoking children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young boy named Damian, who discovers a bag filled with millions of pounds. The book, written by Matt Crowley, is an engaging and entertaining read that is perfect for children between the ages of 8 and 12. Throughout the story, Damian is faced with a series of dilemmas and difficult decisions as he navigates the consequences of his newfound wealth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rupert the Rapper and Aunt Deep Freeze</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/rupert_the_rapper_and_aunt_deep_freeze_by_sinikka_and_tiina_nopola_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/rupert_the_rapper_and_aunt_deep_freeze_by_sinikka_and_tiina_nopola_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Rupert the Rapper and Aunt Deep Freeze by Sinikka and Tiina Nopola Title: Rupert the Rapper and Aunt Deep Freeze Author: Sinikka and Tiina Nopola Review: Rupert the Rapper and Aunt Deep Freeze is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young boy named Rupert who discovers his passion for rapping. The book is filled with engaging illustrations and an entertaining storyline that captures the attention of young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Something&#39;s Fishy, Hazel Green!</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/somethings_fishy_hazel_green_by_odo_hirsch_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/somethings_fishy_hazel_green_by_odo_hirsch_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Something&amp;rsquo;s Fishy, Hazel Green! by Odo Hirsch Title: Something&amp;rsquo;s Fishy, Hazel Green! Author: Odo Hirsch Review: &amp;ldquo;Something&amp;rsquo;s Fishy, Hazel Green!&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Odo Hirsch, which takes readers on a captivating journey through the eyes of its protagonist, Hazel Green. The story follows Hazel as she sets out to uncover the mystery behind a peculiar smell that has been plaguing her school. The book is primarily targeted towards children between the ages of 7 to 10 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Adventures of Baron Munchhausen</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_adventures_of_baron_munchhausen_by_gottfried_burger_isbn_9788420655956/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_adventures_of_baron_munchhausen_by_gottfried_burger_isbn_9788420655956/</guid>
      <description>The Adventures of Baron Munchhausen by Gottfried Burger Title: The Adventures of Baron Munchhausen Author: Gottfried Burger The Adventures of Baron Munchhausen is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Gottfried Burger. This book takes the reader on a thrilling journey with the legendary character, Baron Munchhausen, who embarks on a series of extraordinary adventures. The story is filled with vivid descriptions and exciting illustrations that will captivate the imagination of young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Cat: Or, How I Lost Eternity</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_cat_or_how_i_lost_eternity_by_jutta_richter_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_cat_or_how_i_lost_eternity_by_jutta_richter_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Cat: Or, How I Lost Eternity by Jutta Richter Title: The Cat: Or, How I Lost Eternity Author: Jutta Richter Review: The Cat: Or, How I Lost Eternity is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Jutta Richter. This story is an excellent choice for young readers between the ages of 8 and 12 years old. The book&amp;rsquo;s engaging narrative and beautiful illustrations make it an enjoyable read for both children and adults.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Composition</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_composition_isbn_9781305633858/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_composition_isbn_9781305633858/</guid>
      <description>The Composition Title: The Composition Author: Antonia Banyard Genre: Children&amp;rsquo;s Picture Book Target Age Group: 4-8 years old Review: &amp;ldquo;The Composition&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s picture book that tells the story of a young boy named Sam who is tasked with creating a picture for his school&amp;rsquo;s art competition. The book takes readers on a journey as Sam struggles to find inspiration for his artwork, eventually discovering that the beauty of nature can be found in the most unexpected places.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Graveyard Book</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_graveyard_book_isbn_9780747598626/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_graveyard_book_isbn_9780747598626/</guid>
      <description>The Graveyard Book Title: The Graveyard Book Author: Neil Gaiman Review: The Graveyard Book is a captivating and enchanting novel written by the renowned author Neil Gaiman. This book is a perfect blend of mystery, adventure, and fantasy, making it an ideal read for children aged 8 to 12 years old. The story revolves around the life of a young boy named Nobody Owens, or Bod for short, who is adopted by the ghostly residents of a graveyard after his family is tragically murdered.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Naming of Tishkin Silk</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_naming_of_tishkin_silk_by_glenda_millard_isbn_9780374354817/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_naming_of_tishkin_silk_by_glenda_millard_isbn_9780374354817/</guid>
      <description>The Naming of Tishkin Silk by Glenda Millard Title: The Naming of Tishkin Silk Author: Glenda Millard The Naming of Tishkin Silk is a beautifully written children&amp;rsquo;s book by Glenda Millard that captures the essence of love, friendship, and self-discovery. This enchanting story is perfect for children between the ages of 8 to 12 years old, as it delves into themes that are both relatable and important for this age group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bill&#39;s New Frock</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/bills_new_frock_by_anne_fine_isbn_9789582401757/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/bills_new_frock_by_anne_fine_isbn_9789582401757/</guid>
      <description>Bill&amp;rsquo;s New Frock by Anne Fine Title: Bill&amp;rsquo;s New Frock Author: Anne Fine &amp;ldquo;Bill&amp;rsquo;s New Frock&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Anne Fine, which tells the story of a young boy named Bill who wakes up one morning to find himself in the body of a girl. The book is targeted towards children aged 8-12 years old and teaches valuable life lessons about empathy, understanding, and the importance of treating others with kindness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gargling With Jelly</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/gargling_with_jelly_by_brian_patten_isbn_9780573050923/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/gargling_with_jelly_by_brian_patten_isbn_9780573050923/</guid>
      <description>Gargling With Jelly by Brian Patten Title: Gargling with Jelly Author: Brian Patten &amp;ldquo;Gargling with Jelly&amp;rdquo; is a whimsical and delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book by Brian Patten, a well-known poet and author. This book is perfect for young readers aged 6-10, as it captures their imaginations with its fantastical tales and engaging illustrations. The book is a collection of short stories, each one more captivating than the last. The stories range from the amusing tale of a boy who tries to catch the wind to the touching story of a lonely man who finds friendship in a magical fish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Philosopher&#39;s Stone</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/harry_potter_and_the_philosophers_stone_isbn_9781435238138/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/harry_potter_and_the_philosophers_stone_isbn_9781435238138/</guid>
      <description>Harry Potter and the Philosopher&amp;rsquo;s Stone Title: Harry Potter and the Philosopher&amp;rsquo;s Stone Author: J.K. Rowling Review: Harry Potter and the Philosopher&amp;rsquo;s Stone is a captivating and magical children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the story of a young orphan named Harry Potter. The book is the first installment in the Harry Potter series and is perfect for children between the ages of 8 and 12. The story begins with Harry living a miserable life with his cruel aunt, uncle, and cousin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hayflower and Quiltshoe</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/hayflower_and_quiltshoe_by_sinikka_and_tiina_nopola_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/hayflower_and_quiltshoe_by_sinikka_and_tiina_nopola_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Hayflower and Quiltshoe by Sinikka and Tiina Nopola Title: Hayflower and Quiltshoe Author: Sinikka and Tiina Nopola Review: Hayflower and Quiltshoe is a charming and delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of two sisters, Hayflower and Quiltshoe, who embark on a magical adventure. The story is filled with vivid illustrations that capture the imagination of young readers and bring the characters to life. The book is suitable for children aged 4 to 8 years old, as it contains simple language and engaging storytelling that captivates the young audience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Am Susannah</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/i_am_susannah_by_libby_gleeson_isbn_082340742x/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/i_am_susannah_by_libby_gleeson_isbn_082340742x/</guid>
      <description>I Am Susannah by Libby Gleeson Title: I Am Susannah Author: Libby Gleeson Target Age Group: 6-10 years old Review: &amp;ldquo;I Am Susannah&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young girl named Susannah, who embarks on a journey of self-discovery and learns the importance of embracing her unique qualities. The book, written by Libby Gleeson, is an engaging and heartwarming tale that is perfect for children between the ages of 6 and 10 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maniac Magee</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/maniac_magee_isbn_316807222/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/maniac_magee_isbn_316807222/</guid>
      <description>Maniac Magee Title: Maniac Magee Author: Jerry Spinelli Review: Maniac Magee is a heartwarming and engaging children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Jerry Spinelli. The story follows the life of Jeffrey Lionel Magee, also known as Maniac Magee, a young boy who finds himself homeless after a tragic event. Maniac&amp;rsquo;s journey takes him through the racially divided town of Two Mills, where he becomes a legend for his extraordinary athletic abilities and his kind-hearted nature.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manolito Quattrocchi</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/manolito_quattrocchi_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/manolito_quattrocchi_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Manolito Quattrocchi Title: Manolito Quattrocchi Author: Jorge Bucay Manolito Quattrocchi is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Jorge Bucay, which tells the story of a young boy named Manolito who embarks on a journey of self-discovery and learns valuable life lessons along the way. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old and is a perfect read for young readers who are beginning to explore the complexities of life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Max and Sally</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/max_and_sally_by_milos_macourek_isbn_9788000007007/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/max_and_sally_by_milos_macourek_isbn_9788000007007/</guid>
      <description>Max and Sally by Milos Macourek Title: Max and Sally Author: Milos Macourek Max and Sally is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Milos Macourek. This book is a perfect choice for children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old. The story revolves around two young siblings, Max and Sally, who embark on an adventure together. The illustrations are vibrant and engaging, making it a visually appealing book for young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Friend the Painter</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/my_friend_the_painter_by_lygia_bojunga_isbn_9780152563400/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/my_friend_the_painter_by_lygia_bojunga_isbn_9780152563400/</guid>
      <description>My Friend the Painter by Lygia Bojunga Title: My Friend the Painter Author: Lygia Bojunga Target Age Group: 8-12 years old &amp;ldquo;My Friend the Painter&amp;rdquo; is a beautifully written and illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book by Lygia Bojunga. The story revolves around a young boy named Tim, who befriends a talented painter named Pablo. Through their friendship, Tim learns about the importance of following one&amp;rsquo;s passion, the power of imagination, and the beauty of art.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Only You Can Save Mankind</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/only_you_can_save_mankind_isbn_61376817/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/only_you_can_save_mankind_isbn_61376817/</guid>
      <description>Only You Can Save Mankind Title: Only You Can Save Mankind Author: Terry Pratchett Review: Only You Can Save Mankind is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Terry Pratchett, which takes the reader on a thrilling adventure into the world of virtual reality gaming. The story follows the life of a young boy named Johnny Maxwell, who becomes the leader of a group of aliens known as &amp;ldquo;ScreeWee.&amp;rdquo; As the story unfolds, Johnny and his friends must navigate the complexities of their new virtual world while learning valuable life lessons along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shiloh</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/shiloh_isbn_9681658051/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/shiloh_isbn_9681658051/</guid>
      <description>Shiloh Title: Shiloh Author: Phyllis Reynolds Naylor Genre: Children&amp;rsquo;s Fiction, Realistic Fiction Recommended Age Group: 8-12 years old Shiloh is a heartwarming and engaging children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of an 11-year-old boy named Marty Preston who rescues a beagle named Shiloh. The book explores themes of friendship, loyalty, and the importance of standing up for what is right. The story is set in a small town in West Virginia, where Marty finds Shiloh, a mistreated beagle, and decides to take care of him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Storm</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/storm_isbn_9781593556501/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/storm_isbn_9781593556501/</guid>
      <description>Storm Title: Storm Author: Sam Usher Recommended Age Group: 6-10 years old Storm is a beautifully illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book by Sam Usher that tells the story of a young boy named Jack and his adventures with his loyal dog, Lucky. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 6 and 10, and it is a perfect blend of imagination, adventure, and learning. The story begins with Jack, who is excited about a rainy day and the prospect of playing in the puddles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Superfudge</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/superfudge_isbn_1581180616/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/superfudge_isbn_1581180616/</guid>
      <description>Superfudge Title: Superfudge Author: Judy Blume Target Age Group: 8-12 years old &amp;ldquo;Superfudge&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Judy Blume, which is perfect for the 8-12 age group. The story follows the life of a young boy named Peter Hatcher, who has just moved to a new town with his family. As he navigates the challenges of adjusting to a new environment, Peter also deals with the antics of his younger brother, Fudge, who is always getting into mischief.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Bed and Breakfast Star</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_bed_and_breakfast_star_isbn_9780440863243/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_bed_and_breakfast_star_isbn_9780440863243/</guid>
      <description>The Bed and Breakfast Star Title: The Bed and Breakfast Star Author: Jacqueline Wilson Illustrator: Nick Sharratt Recommended Age Group: 8-12 years old The Bed and Breakfast Star is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the talented Jacqueline Wilson. The story revolves around a young girl named Elsa, who is forced to move in with her unconventional aunt, along with her siblings, when her parents are unable to take care of them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Painted House</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_painted_house_by_montserrate_del_amo_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_painted_house_by_montserrate_del_amo_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Painted House by Montserrate Del Amo Title: The Painted House Author: Montserrate Del Amo Review: The Painted House is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that captures the imagination of young readers with its vibrant illustrations and heartwarming story. The book is perfect for children aged 4-8, as it is both engaging and educational. The story follows the adventures of a young girl named Lily, who loves to paint and dreams of creating a colorful world around her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Story of Tracy Beaker</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_story_of_tracy_beaker_isbn_9781855497887/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_story_of_tracy_beaker_isbn_9781855497887/</guid>
      <description>The Story of Tracy Beaker Title: The Story of Tracy Beaker Author: Jacqueline Wilson The Story of Tracy Beaker is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the talented Jacqueline Wilson. The story revolves around a 10-year-old girl named Tracy, who lives in a children&amp;rsquo;s home and dreams of finding a loving family to adopt her. Tracy is a spunky, independent, and sometimes mischievous character who is easy to love and root for.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The View From Saturday</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_view_from_saturday_isbn_068980993x/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_view_from_saturday_isbn_068980993x/</guid>
      <description>The View From Saturday Title: The View from Saturday Author: E.L. Konigsburg Recommended Age Group: 8-12 years old &amp;ldquo;The View from Saturday&amp;rdquo; is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book by E.L. Konigsburg that tells the story of four sixth-grade students - Noah, Nadia, Ethan, and Julian - who come together to form an academic team. The book is a perfect blend of humor, heart, and adventure, making it an enjoyable read for children aged 8-12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Pair of Jesus Boots</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/a_pair_of_jesus_boots_by_sylvia_sherry_isbn_224615769/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/a_pair_of_jesus_boots_by_sylvia_sherry_isbn_224615769/</guid>
      <description>A Pair of Jesus Boots by Sylvia Sherry Title: A Pair of Jesus Boots Author: Sylvia Sherry Review: A Pair of Jesus Boots is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Sylvia Sherry. The story follows a young boy named Timmy, who desperately wants a pair of Jesus Boots - boots that can walk on water just like Jesus did. The book is targeted towards children aged 4-8 years old and is a perfect blend of adventure, imagination, and heartwarming lessons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bridge to Terabithia</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/bridge_to_terabithia_isbn_9786051732077/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/bridge_to_terabithia_isbn_9786051732077/</guid>
      <description>Bridge to Terabithia Title: Bridge to Terabithia Author: Katherine Paterson Review: Bridge to Terabithia is a captivating and heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s novel written by Katherine Paterson. The story follows the lives of two young protagonists, Jess Aarons and Leslie Burke, as they embark on a journey of friendship, imagination, and self-discovery. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old. The themes and life lessons presented in the story are relatable and relevant to this age group, making it an excellent choice for young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chlorophyll From the Blue Sky</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/chlorophyll_from_the_blue_sky_by_bianca_pitzorno_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/chlorophyll_from_the_blue_sky_by_bianca_pitzorno_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Chlorophyll From the Blue Sky by Bianca Pitzorno Title: Chlorophyll From the Blue Sky Author: Bianca Pitzorno Review: Chlorophyll From the Blue Sky is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes young readers on a captivating journey through the eyes of its protagonist, 12-year-old Chlorophyll. The story, written by the talented Bianca Pitzorno, is a perfect blend of adventure, fantasy, and life lessons, making it an excellent choice for children aged 8-12.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crusade in Jeans</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/crusade_in_jeans_isbn_9781935954071/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/crusade_in_jeans_isbn_9781935954071/</guid>
      <description>Crusade in Jeans Title: Crusade in Jeans Author: Thea Beckman Review: Crusade in Jeans is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young boy named Dolf, who is unexpectedly transported back in time to the Middle Ages. The book, written by Thea Beckman, is an engaging and thought-provoking adventure that is perfect for children aged 10-14. The story is filled with historical details, and it provides an exciting and immersive way for young readers to learn about the past.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fantomette</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/fantomette_by_georges_chaulet_isbn_2010177886/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/fantomette_by_georges_chaulet_isbn_2010177886/</guid>
      <description>Fantomette by Georges Chaulet Title: Fantomette Author: Georges Chaulet Review: Fantomette is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Georges Chaulet that tells the story of a young girl named Fantomette, who is a mysterious superheroine. This book is a perfect read for children between the ages of 7 to 12 years old. The story revolves around Fantomette, who uses her superpowers to help people in need and fight against injustice. Throughout the book, the readers are taken on an exciting adventure filled with action, suspense, and mystery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Granny</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/granny_by_peter_hartling_isbn_905478118/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/granny_by_peter_hartling_isbn_905478118/</guid>
      <description>Granny by Peter Hartling Title: Granny Author: Peter Hartling Review: Granny, written by Peter Hartling, is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that captures the heart of its young readers with its simple yet profound message. The story revolves around a young boy named Tommy, who lives with his grandmother, Granny, in a small village. Granny is the heart and soul of the village, always ready to help anyone in need with her kindness and wisdom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Graveyard Kitaro</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/graveyard_kitaro_by_shigeru_mizuki_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/graveyard_kitaro_by_shigeru_mizuki_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Graveyard Kitaro by Shigeru Mizuki Title: Graveyard Kitaro Author: Shigeru Mizuki Graveyard Kitaro is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Shigeru Mizuki, which takes the readers on a thrilling adventure filled with supernatural creatures and valuable life lessons. This book is suitable for children between the ages of 8 to 12 years old. The story revolves around Kitaro, a young boy who lives in a graveyard with his ghostly friends. Together, they embark on various adventures, encountering monsters, spirits, and other supernatural beings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grinny</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/grinny_by_nicholas_fisk_isbn_140307451/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/grinny_by_nicholas_fisk_isbn_140307451/</guid>
      <description>Grinny by Nicholas Fisk Title: Grinny Author: Nicholas Fisk Review: Grinny is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Nicholas Fisk, which tells the story of a young boy named Pete and his adventures with a small, friendly alien named Grinny. The book is a perfect blend of science fiction, adventure, and humor, making it an enjoyable read for children aged 8-12 years old. The story begins when Pete finds a small, lost alien named Grinny in his backyard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mrs. Frisby and the Rats of NIMH</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/mrs._frisby_and_the_rats_of_nimh_by_robert_c._obrien_isbn_9788434816015/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/mrs._frisby_and_the_rats_of_nimh_by_robert_c._obrien_isbn_9788434816015/</guid>
      <description>Mrs. Frisby and the Rats of NIMH by Robert C. O&amp;rsquo;Brien Title: Mrs. Frisby and the Rats of NIMH Author: Robert C. O&amp;rsquo;Brien Review: Mrs. Frisby and the Rats of NIMH is a captivating and thought-provoking children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a courageous and determined widowed field mouse, Mrs. Frisby, who embarks on a quest to save her family from a dangerous situation. The book is set in a world where animals, specifically rats, have developed intelligence and the ability to communicate with humans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Sweet-Orange Tree</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/my_sweet-orange_tree_by_jose_mauro_de_vasconcelos_isbn_9780718108779/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/my_sweet-orange_tree_by_jose_mauro_de_vasconcelos_isbn_9780718108779/</guid>
      <description>My Sweet-Orange Tree by Jose Mauro De Vasconcelos Title: My Sweet-Orange Tree Author: Jose Mauro De Vasconcelos &amp;ldquo;My Sweet-Orange Tree&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Jose Mauro De Vasconcelos, which takes readers on a heartwarming journey through the life of a young boy named Zezé. The story is set in a small Brazilian town and beautifully portrays the innocence and joy of childhood, as well as the importance of friendship, love, and imagination.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Phantom Tollbooth</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/phantom_tollbooth_isbn_9781984887016/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/phantom_tollbooth_isbn_9781984887016/</guid>
      <description>Phantom Tollbooth Title: The Phantom Tollbooth Author: Norton Juster Review: The Phantom Tollbooth is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes readers on a fantastical journey through the Kingdom of Wisdom. Written by Norton Juster, this book is a perfect blend of adventure, humor, and valuable life lessons. The story follows Milo, a young boy who is bored with his life until he receives a mysterious gift – a tollbooth. This tollbooth transports him to a magical land where he encounters a variety of colorful characters, including the Humbug, the Spelling Bee, and the ever-hungry Whether Man.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stig of the Dump</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/stig_of_the_dump_isbn_754065766/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/stig_of_the_dump_isbn_754065766/</guid>
      <description>Stig of the Dump Title: Stig of the Dump Author: Clive King Target Age Group: 7-12 years old Stig of the Dump is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Clive King, which tells the story of a young boy named Barney who discovers a caveman named Stig living in a nearby dump. The book takes readers on a delightful adventure as Barney and Stig form a unique friendship, teaching valuable life lessons along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Storm Boy</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/storm_boy_isbn_1921024658/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/storm_boy_isbn_1921024658/</guid>
      <description>Storm Boy Title: Storm Boy Author: Colin Thiele Review: Storm Boy is a heartwarming and poignant children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Colin Thiele. The story revolves around a young boy who lives alone with his father in a small shack on the coast of South Australia. The boy befriends a group of pelicans and forms a special bond with one of them, whom he names Mr. Percival. The book targets the age group of 8-12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Garden</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_garden_by_jiri_trnka_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_garden_by_jiri_trnka_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Garden by Jiri Trnka Title: The Garden Author: Jiri Trnka The Garden is a beautifully illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book by Jiri Trnka, which tells the story of a young boy named John who embarks on a magical adventure in a mysterious garden. This book is a perfect read for children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old, as it is filled with vibrant pictures and simple yet engaging text.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Little Man Dressed in Gray</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_little_man_dressed_in_gray_by_fernando_alonso_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_little_man_dressed_in_gray_by_fernando_alonso_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Little Man Dressed in Gray by Fernando Alonso Title: The Little Man Dressed in Gray Author: Fernando Alonso Review: The Little Man Dressed in Gray is a charming and delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that captures the hearts of young readers with its beautiful illustrations and engaging story. Written by Fernando Alonso, this book is perfect for children aged 4 to 8 years old. The story revolves around a little man dressed in gray who lives in a world of color.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Little Pot Boiler</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_little_pot_boiler_by_spike_milligan_isbn_9780234777558/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_little_pot_boiler_by_spike_milligan_isbn_9780234777558/</guid>
      <description>The Little Pot Boiler by Spike Milligan Title: The Little Pot Boiler Author: Spike Milligan Review: The Little Pot Boiler is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the talented Spike Milligan. This delightful story is a perfect fit for children between the ages of 5 and 8 years old. The book&amp;rsquo;s engaging illustrations and simple language make it an enjoyable read for young readers. The story revolves around a little pot that dreams of becoming a boiler, just like the big, shiny ones in the factory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Mouse and His Child</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_mouse_and_his_child_by_russell_hoban_isbn_9781849434652/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_mouse_and_his_child_by_russell_hoban_isbn_9781849434652/</guid>
      <description>The Mouse and His Child by Russell Hoban Title: The Mouse and His Child Author: Russell Hoban Review: The Mouse and His Child is a heartwarming and adventurous children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Russell Hoban. The story follows the journey of two wind-up toy mice, a parent and child, as they navigate the world in search of a place to call home. The book is targeted towards children aged 8-12 years old, as it contains complex themes and challenging vocabulary.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Turbulent Term of Tyke Tiler</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_turbulent_term_of_tyke_tiler_isbn_198312695/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_turbulent_term_of_tyke_tiler_isbn_198312695/</guid>
      <description>The Turbulent Term of Tyke Tiler Title: The Turbulent Term of Tyke Tiler Author: Gene Kemp The Turbulent Term of Tyke Tiler is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Gene Kemp. The story follows the adventures of Tyke Tiler, a young boy who is struggling to fit in at his new school. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 8 and 12, and is an engaging read that teaches valuable life lessons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uncle</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/uncle_by_j.p._martin_isbn_9780099294504/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/uncle_by_j.p._martin_isbn_9780099294504/</guid>
      <description>Uncle by J.P. Martin Title: Uncle Author: J.P. Martin Review: &amp;ldquo;Uncle&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by J.P. Martin, which takes the readers on an exciting adventure in the world of fantasy. The story follows the life of a wealthy, kind-hearted man named Uncle, who lives in a huge, magical house called &amp;ldquo;The Manor.&amp;rdquo; Uncle&amp;rsquo;s house is filled with talking animals, who are his loyal friends and helpers. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 6 and 12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Astro Boy</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/astro_boy_by_mighty_atom_isbn_848449439x/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/astro_boy_by_mighty_atom_isbn_848449439x/</guid>
      <description>Astro Boy by Mighty Atom Title: Astro Boy (Mighty Atom) Author: Osamu Tezuka Astro Boy, also known as Mighty Atom, is a children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Osamu Tezuka. The story follows the adventures of a young robot named Astro Boy, who was created by the brilliant scientist Dr. Tenma after the tragic loss of his son. Astro Boy possesses superhuman abilities and a kind heart, which he uses to help people and fight against evil forces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Betsy-Tacy Books</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/betsy-tacy_books_isbn_9780064401272/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/betsy-tacy_books_isbn_9780064401272/</guid>
      <description>Betsy-Tacy Books Title: Betsy-Tacy Books Review: The Betsy-Tacy Books, written by Maud Hart Lovelace, is a delightful series that captures the essence of childhood friendships, imagination, and the innocence of a bygone era. This heartwarming collection of stories is perfect for young readers between the ages of 7 and 12, and it is an ideal choice for parents and teachers looking to instill important life lessons in their children. Set in the early 20th century, the Betsy-Tacy Books follow the adventures of two best friends, Betsy and Tacy, as they grow up together in the charming town of Deep Valley.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Down With Skool</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/down_with_skool_by_geoffrey_willans_isbn_9780141191683/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/down_with_skool_by_geoffrey_willans_isbn_9780141191683/</guid>
      <description>Down With Skool by Geoffrey Willans Title: Down With Skool Author: Geoffrey Willans Review: Down With Skool is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Geoffrey Willans, which takes readers on a humorous journey through the eyes of a young boy named Nigel Molesworth. The book is a collection of short stories and illustrations that capture the essence of life in a British boarding school. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 8 and 12, and is perfect for those who enjoy a good laugh and relatable situations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Half Magic</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/half_magic_isbn_156379902/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/half_magic_isbn_156379902/</guid>
      <description>Half Magic Title: Half Magic Author: Edward Eager Genre: Children&amp;rsquo;s Fantasy Fiction Recommended Age Group: 8-12 years old &amp;ldquo;Half Magic&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes readers on a magical adventure with four siblings who stumble upon a wish-granting coin. The story is filled with humor, adventure, and valuable life lessons that children can learn from. The four siblings, Jane, Mark, Katharine, and Martha, are the main characters in the book.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hurrah for St Trinian&#39;s</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/hurrah_for_st_trinians_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/hurrah_for_st_trinians_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Hurrah for St Trinian&amp;rsquo;s Title: Hurrah for St Trinian&amp;rsquo;s Author: Ronald Searle Target Age Group: 8-12 years old &amp;ldquo;Hurrah for St Trinian&amp;rsquo;s&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of the mischievous and unruly students at St Trinian&amp;rsquo;s, a fictional boarding school for girls. The book, written by Ronald Searle, is a perfect blend of humor, adventure, and a touch of rebellion, making it an entertaining read for children between the ages of 8 and 12.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>James Thurber: The 13 Clocks</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/james_thurber_the_13_clocks_isbn_573651221/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/james_thurber_the_13_clocks_isbn_573651221/</guid>
      <description>James Thurber: The 13 Clocks Title: &amp;ldquo;James Thurber: The 13 Clocks&amp;rdquo; Author: James Thurber Illustrator: Marc Simont Recommended Age Group: 8-12 years old &amp;ldquo;James Thurber: The 13 Clocks&amp;rdquo; is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book that transports readers to a magical kingdom where the mysterious Prince Zorn is on a quest to save the beautiful Princess Saralinda from the clutches of the evil Duke. The story is filled with enchanting characters, such as the Golux, a wise and witty creature, and the Todal, a magical creature with the ability to grant wishes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minnow on the Say</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/minnow_on_the_say_by_philippa_pearce_isbn_9780192710772/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/minnow_on_the_say_by_philippa_pearce_isbn_9780192710772/</guid>
      <description>Minnow on the Say by Philippa Pearce Title: Minnow on the Say Author: Philippa Pearce Review: Minnow on the Say is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Philippa Pearce, which tells the story of two young boys, David and Adam, who embark on a thrilling adventure along the River Say. The book is suitable for children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old and is filled with captivating themes, life lessons, and an engaging narrative.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Hundred Dresses</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_hundred_dresses_isbn_9780812455274/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_hundred_dresses_isbn_9780812455274/</guid>
      <description>The Hundred Dresses Title: The Hundred Dresses Author: Eleanese Estes Review: The Hundred Dresses is a heartwarming and thought-provoking children&amp;rsquo;s book that tackles the important themes of bullying, empathy, and the power of kindness. Written by Eleanor Estes, this classic story has been cherished by generations of young readers since its publication in 1944. The book follows the story of Wanda Petronski, a young girl who is bullied by her classmates for being different.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Little Bookroom</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_little_bookroom_isbn_9780192719478/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_little_bookroom_isbn_9780192719478/</guid>
      <description>The Little Bookroom Title: The Little Bookroom Author: Eleanor Farjeon Illustrator: Edward Ardizzone The Little Bookroom is a charming and delightful collection of short stories that will captivate the hearts of young readers. Eleanor Farjeon, the author, has skillfully woven a tapestry of tales that transport the reader to a world of enchantment and adventure. The book is accompanied by beautiful illustrations by Edward Ardizzone, which add to the overall charm of the stories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Princess Who Had Magic Fingers</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_princess_who_had_magic_fingers_by_maria_luisa_gefaell_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_princess_who_had_magic_fingers_by_maria_luisa_gefaell_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Princess Who Had Magic Fingers by Maria Luisa Gefaell Title: The Princess Who Had Magic Fingers Author: Maria Luisa Gefaell The Princess Who Had Magic Fingers is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Maria Luisa Gefaell. This enchanting story is perfect for children aged 4-8 years old, as it features captivating illustrations and a simple yet engaging narrative. The story follows a young princess who discovers that she has magical fingers that can create beautiful art.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Swish of the Curtain</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_swish_of_the_curtain_by_pamela_brown_isbn_9780340041451/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_swish_of_the_curtain_by_pamela_brown_isbn_9780340041451/</guid>
      <description>The Swish of the Curtain by Pamela Brown Title: The Swish of the Curtain Author: Pamela Brown Review: The Swish of the Curtain is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes the reader on a captivating journey through the lives of a group of young friends who decide to put on their own play. This heartwarming story, written by Pamela Brown, is an ideal read for children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Wind on the Moon</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_wind_on_the_moon_isbn_1590171004/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_wind_on_the_moon_isbn_1590171004/</guid>
      <description>The Wind on the Moon Title: The Wind on the Moon Author: Eric Linklater Recommended Age Group: 8-12 years old The Wind on the Moon is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Eric Linklater, which tells the story of two young sisters, Dinah and Dorinda, who embark on a magical adventure. The book, first published in 1944, has aged remarkably well and continues to captivate young readers with its whimsical tale and valuable life lessons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Warden&#39;s Niece</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/wardens_niece_by_gillian_avery_isbn_6707947/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/wardens_niece_by_gillian_avery_isbn_6707947/</guid>
      <description>Warden&amp;rsquo;s Niece by Gillian Avery Title: The Warden&amp;rsquo;s Niece Author: Gillian Avery Review: The Warden&amp;rsquo;s Niece is a charming and delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Gillian Avery. This story follows the adventures of a young girl named Matilda, who is sent to live with her uncle, the warden of a castle, after her parents pass away. As Matilda navigates her new life, she learns valuable lessons about friendship, courage, and the importance of embracing one&amp;rsquo;s unique qualities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Adventures of the Wishing-Chair</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_adventures_of_the_wishing-chair_by_enid_blyton_isbn_1405278633/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_adventures_of_the_wishing-chair_by_enid_blyton_isbn_1405278633/</guid>
      <description>The Adventures of the Wishing-Chair by Enid Blyton Title: The Adventures of the Wishing-Chair Author: Enid Blyton Review: The Adventures of the Wishing-Chair is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the prolific author Enid Blyton. This enchanting story follows the adventures of two siblings, Mollie and Peter, who discover a magical wishing-chair in their playroom. The chair has the power to grant wishes and take the children on exciting and educational journeys to far-off lands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Black Corsair</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_black_corsair_by_emilio_salgari_isbn_6077200069/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_black_corsair_by_emilio_salgari_isbn_6077200069/</guid>
      <description>The Black Corsair by Emilio Salgari Title: The Black Corsair Author: Emilio Salgari Review: The Black Corsair, written by Emilio Salgari, is a thrilling adventure story that is perfect for elementary school-aged children. The book is filled with action, excitement, and valuable life lessons that will captivate young readers. The story follows the adventures of Emilio, a young boy who is captured by pirates and forced to join their crew. As Emilio becomes part of the pirate world, he learns about courage, friendship, and the importance of standing up for what is right.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Box of Delights</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_box_of_delights_by_john_masefield_isbn_9781850899259/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_box_of_delights_by_john_masefield_isbn_9781850899259/</guid>
      <description>The Box of Delights by John Masefield Title: The Box of Delights Author: John Masefield Review: The Box of Delights is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by John Masefield. The story follows the adventures of a young boy named Kay Harker, who finds himself caught up in a thrilling battle between good and evil. The book is filled with enchanting characters, magical objects, and an exciting plot that keeps readers engaged from beginning to end.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Hobbit</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_hobbit_by_j.r.r._tolkien_isbn_034521532x/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_hobbit_by_j.r.r._tolkien_isbn_034521532x/</guid>
      <description>The Hobbit by J.R.R. Tolkien Title: The Hobbit Author: J.R.R. Tolkien Review: The Hobbit is a timeless classic written by J.R.R. Tolkien, which takes readers on an enchanting journey through the magical world of Middle Earth. This book is a perfect fit for children between the ages of 8 and 12, as it is filled with adventure, fantasy, and valuable life lessons. The story follows the adventures of a hobbit named Bilbo Baggins, who embarks on a quest to reclaim the lost dwarf kingdom of Erebor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The School at the Chalet</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_school_at_the_chalet_by_elinor_m._brent-dyer_isbn_6903347/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_school_at_the_chalet_by_elinor_m._brent-dyer_isbn_6903347/</guid>
      <description>The School at the Chalet by Elinor M. Brent-Dyer Title: The School at the Chalet Author: Elinor M. Brent-Dyer Review: The School at the Chalet is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Elinor M. Brent-Dyer. The story follows the adventures of Jo Bettany, a young girl who finds herself at a new boarding school in the Swiss Alps called the Chalet School. The book is filled with heartwarming friendships, exciting adventures, and valuable life lessons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Wonderful Wizard of Oz</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_wonderful_wizard_of_oz_isbn_9781520209166/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_wonderful_wizard_of_oz_isbn_9781520209166/</guid>
      <description>The Wonderful Wizard of Oz Title: The Wonderful Wizard of Oz Author: L. Frank Baum Review: The Wonderful Wizard of Oz is a timeless classic that has enchanted readers of all ages since its publication in 1900. The story follows the adventures of a young girl named Dorothy, who is swept away from her Kansas farm by a tornado and finds herself in the magical land of Oz. Along her journey, she encounters a colorful cast of characters, including the Scarecrow, the Tin Woodman, and the Cowardly Lion, who join her on her quest to find the Wizard of Oz and help her return home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tintin in the Land of the Soviets</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/tintin_in_the_land_of_the_soviets_by_herg%C3%A9_isbn_316003743/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/tintin_in_the_land_of_the_soviets_by_herg%C3%A9_isbn_316003743/</guid>
      <description>Tintin in the Land of the Soviets by Hergé Title: Tintin in the Land of the Soviets Author: Hergé Review: Tintin in the Land of the Soviets is an adventurous and captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the story of the young reporter, Tintin, as he embarks on a thrilling journey to the Soviet Union. The book, written by the talented Hergé, is a perfect read for children aged 8 to 12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Celia Says</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/what_celia_says_by_elena_fortun_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/what_celia_says_by_elena_fortun_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>What Celia Says by Elena Fortun Title: What Celia Says Author: Elena Fortun &amp;ldquo;What Celia Says&amp;rdquo; is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Elena Fortun, which tells the story of a young girl named Celia who has a unique way of looking at the world. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 5 to 10 years old, and it is an excellent choice for parents and teachers looking for a book that teaches valuable life lessons in a fun and engaging manner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Bad Case of Stripes</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/a_bad_case_of_stripes_isbn_439924944/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/a_bad_case_of_stripes_isbn_439924944/</guid>
      <description>A Bad Case of Stripes Title: A Bad Case of Stripes Author: David Shannon Review: A Bad Case of Stripes is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young girl named Camilla Cream, who loves lima beans but is afraid to eat them because she is worried about what others will think. One day, she wakes up with a bad case of stripes, and the situation only gets worse from there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beegu</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/beegu_by_alexis_deacon_isbn_9780091768294/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/beegu_by_alexis_deacon_isbn_9780091768294/</guid>
      <description>Beegu by Alexis Deacon Title: Beegu Author: Alexis Deacon Beegu is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written and illustrated by Alexis Deacon. The story follows the adventures of Beegu, an adorable, lovable, and friendly alien who becomes stranded on Earth. As Beegu encounters various animals and people, she struggles to find a way back to her home planet. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 4 to 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bridget and the Moose Brothers</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/bridget_and_the_moose_brothers_by_pija_lindenbaum_isbn_9789129660463/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/bridget_and_the_moose_brothers_by_pija_lindenbaum_isbn_9789129660463/</guid>
      <description>Bridget and the Moose Brothers by Pija Lindenbaum Title: Bridget and the Moose Brothers Author: Pija Lindenbaum Review: Bridget and the Moose Brothers is a charming and delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young girl named Bridget who embarks on an adventure with two mischievous moose brothers. The book is filled with vibrant illustrations and captivating storytelling that will keep young readers engaged from beginning to end. The target age group for this book is 4 to 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dodo Gets Married</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/dodo_gets_married_by_petra_mathers_isbn_1481442805/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/dodo_gets_married_by_petra_mathers_isbn_1481442805/</guid>
      <description>Dodo Gets Married by Petra Mathers Title: Dodo Gets Married Author: Petra Mathers Dodo Gets Married is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written and illustrated by Petra Mathers. The story follows Dodo, a lovable bird, as she prepares for her wedding to the charming and handsome Dodo. The book is targeted towards children aged 4-8 years old, as it contains simple yet engaging illustrations and a straightforward storyline. The language used is easy to understand, making it an enjoyable read for young children.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>George MacDonald at the Back of the North Wind</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/george_macdonald_at_the_back_of_the_north_wind_isbn_9798519978361/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/george_macdonald_at_the_back_of_the_north_wind_isbn_9798519978361/</guid>
      <description>George MacDonald at the Back of the North Wind Title: George MacDonald at the Back of the North Wind Author: George MacDonald Age Group: 8-12 years old The children&amp;rsquo;s book &amp;lsquo;George MacDonald at the Back of the North Wind&amp;rsquo; is a beautifully written and enchanting story that captures the hearts of young readers. Author George MacDonald weaves a tale that is both magical and thought-provoking, making it an excellent choice for children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Will Not Ever Never Eat a Tomato</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/i_will_not_ever_never_eat_a_tomato_by_lauren_child_isbn_9780763611880/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/i_will_not_ever_never_eat_a_tomato_by_lauren_child_isbn_9780763611880/</guid>
      <description>I Will Not Ever Never Eat a Tomato by Lauren Child Title: I Will Not Ever Never Eat a Tomato Author: Lauren Child Review: &amp;ldquo;I Will Not Ever Never Eat a Tomato&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Lauren Child, targeting young readers between the ages of 4 to 8 years old. The story revolves around a young girl named Lola, who is very particular about her food choices and refuses to eat anything that is not her favorite.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In Mr. Thunder&#39;s House</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/in_mr._thunders_house_by_guido_quarzo_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/in_mr._thunders_house_by_guido_quarzo_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>In Mr. Thunder&amp;rsquo;s House by Guido Quarzo Title: In Mr. Thunder&amp;rsquo;s House Author: Guido Quarzo In Mr. Thunder&amp;rsquo;s House is a charming and delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Guido Quarzo. The story follows the adventures of a young boy named Tommy, who stumbles upon a magical house belonging to the enigmatic Mr. Thunder. As Tommy explores the house, he encounters various fantastical creatures and learns valuable life lessons along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Boy Who Grew Flowers</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_boy_who_grew_flowers_by_jen_wojtowicz_isbn_1846867495/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_boy_who_grew_flowers_by_jen_wojtowicz_isbn_1846867495/</guid>
      <description>The Boy Who Grew Flowers by Jen Wojtowicz Title: The Boy Who Grew Flowers Author: Jen Wojtowicz Review: The Boy Who Grew Flowers is a heartwarming and imaginative children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Jen Wojtowicz. The story follows a young boy named Rink, who possesses a unique ability to grow flowers from his body. Initially, Rink feels embarrassed and isolated due to his extraordinary gift, but he eventually learns to embrace his differences and make friends with a kind and understanding girl named Angelina.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Girl and the Jackdaw Tree</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_girl_and_the_jackdaw_tree_by_riitta_jalonen_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_girl_and_the_jackdaw_tree_by_riitta_jalonen_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Girl and the Jackdaw Tree by Riitta Jalonen Title: The Girl and the Jackdaw Tree Author: Riitta Jalonen Review: The Girl and the Jackdaw Tree is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Riitta Jalonen. This beautifully illustrated story follows the journey of a young girl who embarks on a quest to save her beloved jackdaw tree from being cut down. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 6 and 10 years old and is a perfect blend of adventure, friendship, and environmental awareness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Love Book</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_love_book_by_pernilla_stalfelt_isbn_888994559/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_love_book_by_pernilla_stalfelt_isbn_888994559/</guid>
      <description>The Love Book by Pernilla Stalfelt Title: The Love Book Author: Pernilla Stalfelt Review: The Love Book by Pernilla Stalfelt is a heartwarming and visually stunning children&amp;rsquo;s book that beautifully captures the essence of love and kindness. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 4 to 8 years old and is a perfect addition to any child&amp;rsquo;s library. The Love Book is a vibrant and imaginative exploration of love, showcasing the many ways love can be expressed and experienced.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Night Pirates</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_night_pirates_by_peter_harris_isbn_9780545004893/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_night_pirates_by_peter_harris_isbn_9780545004893/</guid>
      <description>The Night Pirates by Peter Harris Title: The Night Pirates Author: Peter Harris The Night Pirates is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Peter Harris, which is perfect for young readers between the ages of 4 and 8. The story follows a group of young pirates who, under the cover of darkness, take over a little girl&amp;rsquo;s bedroom and transform it into their pirate ship. Together, they embark on a thrilling adventure filled with treasure, mermaids, and even a giant sea monster!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Water-Babies</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_water-babies_isbn_9798485198176/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_water-babies_isbn_9798485198176/</guid>
      <description>The Water-Babies Title: The Water-Babies Author: Charles Kingsley Genre: Children&amp;rsquo;s Fantasy/Adventure Age Group: 8-12 years old &amp;ldquo;The Water-Babies&amp;rdquo; is a delightful and imaginative children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes readers on an enchanting journey through the world of water-babies. Written by Charles Kingsley, this book was first published in 1863 and has since become a classic in children&amp;rsquo;s literature. The story revolves around Tom, a young chimney sweeper, who is transformed into a water-baby after his death.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UG: Boy Genius of the Stone Age</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/ug_boy_genius_of_the_stone_age_by_raymond_briggs_isbn_9781856130547/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/ug_boy_genius_of_the_stone_age_by_raymond_briggs_isbn_9781856130547/</guid>
      <description>UG: Boy Genius of the Stone Age by Raymond Briggs Title: UG: Boy Genius of the Stone Age Author: Raymond Briggs Target Age Group: 7-10 years old Review: UG: Boy Genius of the Stone Age is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written and illustrated by the talented Raymond Briggs. The story follows the adventures of Ug, a young boy living in the Stone Age, who is considered a genius by his tribe due to his inventiveness and problem-solving skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zen Shorts</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/zen_shorts_isbn_9780545040877/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/zen_shorts_isbn_9780545040877/</guid>
      <description>Zen Shorts Title: Zen Shorts Author: Jon J. Muth Target Age Group: 5-10 years old &amp;ldquo;Zen Shorts&amp;rdquo; is a beautifully illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book that captures the essence of mindfulness and the importance of finding inner peace. Author Jon J. Muth has skillfully crafted a story that is both engaging and educational for young readers. The book follows the story of three siblings, Michael, Karl, and Addy, who meet a wise and mysterious panda named Stillwater.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Pocket for Corduroy</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/a_pocket_for_corduroy_by_don_freeman_isbn_140951245/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/a_pocket_for_corduroy_by_don_freeman_isbn_140951245/</guid>
      <description>A Pocket for Corduroy by Don Freeman Title: A Pocket for Corduroy Author: Don Freeman &amp;ldquo;A Pocket for Corduroy&amp;rdquo; is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Don Freeman, which follows the adventures of a lovable teddy bear named Corduroy. This charming story is perfect for young readers between the ages of 4 and 8 years old. The book revolves around Corduroy, who lives in a department store and dreams of finding a home with a loving family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Walk in the Park</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/a_walk_in_the_park_by_anthony_browne_isbn_241893976/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/a_walk_in_the_park_by_anthony_browne_isbn_241893976/</guid>
      <description>A Walk in the Park by Anthony Browne Title: A Walk in the Park Author: Anthony Browne Review: A Walk in the Park is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the talented author and illustrator, Anthony Browne. This book is perfect for young readers between the ages of 4 to 8 years old. The story follows a young boy and his father as they take a walk in the park. The book is filled with beautiful illustrations that capture the essence of the story and make it an enjoyable read for both children and adults.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Friends From the Other Side</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/friends_from_the_other_side_by_gloria_anzaldua_isbn_9780892391134/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/friends_from_the_other_side_by_gloria_anzaldua_isbn_9780892391134/</guid>
      <description>Friends From the Other Side by Gloria Anzaldua Title: Friends From the Other Side Author: Gloria Anzaldua Review: &amp;ldquo;Friends From the Other Side&amp;rdquo; is a beautifully written and illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young girl named Marisol, who lives near the U.S.-Mexico border. The book explores themes of friendship, empathy, and understanding, as Marisol befriends a group of children from the other side of the border. The story is engaging and age-appropriate for children between the ages of 6 and 10 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Haunted House</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/haunted_house_by_jan_pienkowski_isbn_9780744581157/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/haunted_house_by_jan_pienkowski_isbn_9780744581157/</guid>
      <description>Haunted House by Jan Pienkowski Title: Haunted House Author: Jan Pienkowski Review: Haunted House is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book by Jan Pienkowski, filled with vibrant illustrations and a spooky yet fun storyline. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old, making it a perfect addition to any young reader&amp;rsquo;s collection. The story follows a group of ghosts, witches, and other supernatural creatures as they prepare for a grand party at their haunted house.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jennifer Jones Won&#39;t Leave Me Alone</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/jennifer_jones_wont_leave_me_alone_by_frieda_wishinsky_isbn_9780876149218/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/jennifer_jones_wont_leave_me_alone_by_frieda_wishinsky_isbn_9780876149218/</guid>
      <description>Jennifer Jones Won&amp;rsquo;t Leave Me Alone by Frieda Wishinsky Title: Jennifer Jones Won&amp;rsquo;t Leave Me Alone Author: Frieda Wishinsky Review: &amp;ldquo;Jennifer Jones Won&amp;rsquo;t Leave Me Alone&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tackles the relatable theme of dealing with a bothersome classmate. Author Frieda Wishinsky has created a story that will resonate with young readers, as they follow the protagonist&amp;rsquo;s journey to find a solution to his problem. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 8 and 12.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moka the Cow</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/moka_the_cow_by_agostino_traini_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/moka_the_cow_by_agostino_traini_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Moka the Cow by Agostino Traini Title: Moka the Cow Author: Agostino Traini Moka the Cow is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young cow named Moka who is different from the other cows in her herd. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old and provides valuable life lessons through its engaging narrative and colorful illustrations. The story follows Moka as she embarks on a journey to discover her unique talents and abilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mr Majeika</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/mr_majeika_by_humphrey_carpenter_isbn_141323086/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/mr_majeika_by_humphrey_carpenter_isbn_141323086/</guid>
      <description>Mr Majeika by Humphrey Carpenter Title: Mr Majeika Author: Humphrey Carpenter &amp;ldquo;Mr Majeika&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Humphrey Carpenter, which tells the story of a young girl named Hilary and her encounters with the magical Mr Majeika. The book is suitable for children aged 7 to 10 years old, and it covers various life lessons that are essential for their growth and development. The story revolves around Hilary, who is having a hard time fitting in at her new school.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Kingdom for a Horse</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/my_kingdom_for_a_horse_by_ana_m_machado_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/my_kingdom_for_a_horse_by_ana_m_machado_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>My Kingdom for a Horse by Ana M Machado Title: My Kingdom for a Horse Author: Ana M Machado Review: My Kingdom for a Horse is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Ana M Machado. The story revolves around a young boy named Tim who dreams of owning a horse. Tim&amp;rsquo;s determination and perseverance to achieve his goal teaches valuable life lessons to young readers. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 6 to 10 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not Now, Bernard</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/not_now_bernard_by_david_mckee_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/not_now_bernard_by_david_mckee_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Not Now, Bernard by David McKee Title: Not Now, Bernard Author: David McKee &amp;ldquo;Not Now, Bernard&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written and illustrated by David McKee. This book is a perfect read for children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old. The story follows a young boy named Bernard who is constantly ignored by his parents, and one day, he encounters a monster in his backyard. The book tackles themes such as family relationships, the importance of listening, and the consequences of neglect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oh, the Places You&#39;ll Go</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/oh_the_places_youll_go_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/oh_the_places_youll_go_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Oh, the Places You&amp;rsquo;ll Go Title: Oh, the Places You&amp;rsquo;ll Go Author: Dr. Seuss Review: Oh, the Places You&amp;rsquo;ll Go is a delightful and inspiring children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the beloved author Dr. Seuss. This book is perfect for children aged 4 to 8 years old, as it captures their imagination and teaches valuable life lessons in a fun and engaging way. The story follows the journey of a young character as they navigate through the ups and downs of life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Strega Nona</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/strega_nona_isbn_9780590659673/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/strega_nona_isbn_9780590659673/</guid>
      <description>Strega Nona Title: Strega Nona Author: Tomie dePaola Review: Strega Nona is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Tomie dePaola, which tells the story of a wise old witch named Strega Nona who lives in a small Italian village. The book is filled with beautiful illustrations that bring the story to life and captivate the reader&amp;rsquo;s attention. The story is aimed at children between the ages of 4 to 8 years old, and it teaches important life lessons such as the importance of hard work, responsibility, and the consequences of not following instructions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tar Beach</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/tar_beach_isbn_590463810/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/tar_beach_isbn_590463810/</guid>
      <description>Tar Beach Title: Tar Beach Author: Faith Ringgold Target Age Group: 5-10 years old Tar Beach is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Faith Ringgold, which takes readers on a magical journey through the eyes of a young girl named Cassie. The story is set in the 1930s and is based on the author&amp;rsquo;s own experiences growing up in Harlem. The book is beautifully illustrated with Faith Ringgold&amp;rsquo;s quilt-like artwork, which adds to the charm and uniqueness of the story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The People Could Fly</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_people_could_fly_by_virginia_hamilton_isbn_9780375845536/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_people_could_fly_by_virginia_hamilton_isbn_9780375845536/</guid>
      <description>The People Could Fly by Virginia Hamilton Title: The People Could Fly Author: Virginia Hamilton Review: The People Could Fly is a beautifully written and illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book that captures the essence of African American folklore. Virginia Hamilton has masterfully crafted a collection of stories that not only entertain but also teach valuable life lessons to young readers. Target Age Group: The book is suitable for children between the ages of 8 and 12.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Stinky Cheese Man and Other Fairly Stupid Tales</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_stinky_cheese_man_and_other_fairly_stupid_tales_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_stinky_cheese_man_and_other_fairly_stupid_tales_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Stinky Cheese Man and Other Fairly Stupid Tales Title: The Stinky Cheese Man and Other Fairly Stupid Tales Author: Jon Scieszka and Lane Smith Genre: Children&amp;rsquo;s Humor Recommended Age Group: 7-12 years old The Stinky Cheese Man and Other Fairly Stupid Tales is a hilarious and cleverly written children&amp;rsquo;s book that offers a fresh twist on classic fairy tales. The book is filled with witty humor and captivating illustrations that will keep young readers engaged from start to finish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Lion in the Meadow</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/a_lion_in_the_meadow_by_margaret_mahy_isbn_9780460061742/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/a_lion_in_the_meadow_by_margaret_mahy_isbn_9780460061742/</guid>
      <description>A Lion in the Meadow by Margaret Mahy Title: A Lion in the Meadow Author: Margaret Mahy Review: A Lion in the Meadow is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Margaret Mahy, which tells the story of a young boy named Timothy who has a vivid imagination. The book is perfect for children aged 4 to 8 years old, as it teaches valuable life lessons through a captivating and engaging narrative.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Necklace of Raindrops</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/a_necklace_of_raindrops_by_joan_aiken_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/a_necklace_of_raindrops_by_joan_aiken_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>A Necklace of Raindrops by Joan Aiken Title: A Necklace of Raindrops Author: Joan Aiken Review: A Necklace of Raindrops is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Joan Aiken, which takes readers on a magical journey through a series of enchanting stories. The book is beautifully illustrated by Jan Pienkowski, whose artwork adds to the charm and whimsy of the tales. The book is suitable for children aged 6 to 10 years old, as it features simple yet engaging language and captivating illustrations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apoutsiak</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/apoutsiak_by_paul-emile_victor_isbn_9782081604452/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/apoutsiak_by_paul-emile_victor_isbn_9782081604452/</guid>
      <description>Apoutsiak by Paul-Emile Victor Title: Apoutsiak Author: Paul-Emile Victor Review: Apoutsiak is a beautifully illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young Inuit boy named Apoutsiak who goes on a thrilling adventure with his family. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 5 and 10, and it offers a wonderful blend of adventure, cultural exploration, and important life lessons. The story begins with Apoutsiak and his family embarking on a journey to find a new place to live.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Nest</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/best_nest_by_pd_eastman_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/best_nest_by_pd_eastman_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Best Nest by PD Eastman Title: Best Nest Author: P.D. Eastman &amp;ldquo;Best Nest&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by P.D. Eastman, which follows the story of a bird named Peter who is on a quest to find the perfect nest. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 3 to 7 years old, as it features simple and engaging illustrations, as well as easy-to-understand language. The story begins with Peter&amp;rsquo;s dissatisfaction with his current nest, which he deems too small and uncomfortable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Captain Pugwash</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/captain_pugwash_by_john_ryan_isbn_859680169/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/captain_pugwash_by_john_ryan_isbn_859680169/</guid>
      <description>Captain Pugwash by John Ryan Title: Captain Pugwash Author: John Ryan Review: Captain Pugwash is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes readers on a thrilling adventure with its lovable characters and engaging storyline. The book, written by John Ryan, is an ideal read for children between the ages of 5 and 10 years old. The story revolves around the charming Captain Pugwash, a pirate captain, and his trusty crew as they embark on a treasure hunt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Figgie Hobbin</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/figgie_hobbin_by_charles_causley_isbn_9780330400008/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/figgie_hobbin_by_charles_causley_isbn_9780330400008/</guid>
      <description>Figgie Hobbin by Charles Causley Title: Figgie Hobbin Author: Charles Causley Review: Figgie Hobbin is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the talented Charles Causley. This book is perfect for children between the ages of 6 and 10 years old, as it contains engaging and imaginative stories that will capture their attention and spark their curiosity. The book follows the adventures of Figgie Hobbin, a young boy who embarks on various exciting journeys and encounters interesting characters along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frederick</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/frederick_isbn_1979021686/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/frederick_isbn_1979021686/</guid>
      <description>Frederick Title: Frederick Author: Leo Lionni Recommended Age Group: 4-8 years old Frederick is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Leo Lionni, which tells the story of a family of field mice living in a beautiful meadow. The book primarily focuses on the character of Frederick, a field mouse who spends his time daydreaming and observing the world around him, rather than actively participating in the preparations for winter like the other mice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gumdrop</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/gumdrop_by_val_biro_isbn_340714492/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/gumdrop_by_val_biro_isbn_340714492/</guid>
      <description>Gumdrop by Val Biro Title: Gumdrop Author: Val Biro Gumdrop, written by Val Biro, is a charming and engaging children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the adventures of a little car named Gumdrop. The story is perfect for children between the ages of 4 and 8, as it is filled with colorful illustrations and simple language that young readers can easily understand and enjoy. The book&amp;rsquo;s main character, Gumdrop, is a friendly and curious little car who loves to explore the world around him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harold and the Purple Crayon</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/harold_and_the_purple_crayon_isbn_9780439132534/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/harold_and_the_purple_crayon_isbn_9780439132534/</guid>
      <description>Harold and the Purple Crayon Title: Harold and the Purple Crayon Author: Crockett Johnson Recommended Age Group: 4-8 years old &amp;ldquo;Harold and the Purple Crayon&amp;rdquo; is a timeless classic that has been enjoyed by children for generations. The story follows the adventures of a young boy named Harold, who uses his purple crayon to create a world of his own. This imaginative tale teaches valuable life lessons and is perfect for children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hodja From Pjort</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/hodja_from_pjort_by_ole_lund_kirkegaard_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/hodja_from_pjort_by_ole_lund_kirkegaard_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Hodja From Pjort by Ole Lund Kirkegaard Title: Hodja From Pjort Author: Ole Lund Kirkegaard Review: Hodja From Pjort is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the talented author, Ole Lund Kirkegaard. This book is perfect for children between the ages of 7 and 12 years old. The story follows the adventures of Hodja, a young boy from the fictional town of Pjort, as he embarks on a journey to find a stolen camel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marlaguette</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/marlaguette_by_marie_colmont_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/marlaguette_by_marie_colmont_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Marlaguette by Marie Colmont Title: Marlaguette Author: Marie Colmont Review: Marlaguette is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Marie Colmont that tells the story of a young girl named Marlaguette who embarks on a magical adventure. The book is beautifully illustrated, capturing the whimsical nature of the story and making it a visual treat for young readers. Target Age Group: Marlaguette is best suited for children between the ages of 5 and 10.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pippi Longstocking</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/pippi_longstocking_isbn_192772422/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/pippi_longstocking_isbn_192772422/</guid>
      <description>Pippi Longstocking Title: Pippi Longstocking Author: Astrid Lindgren Illustrator: Ingrid Vang Nyman Review: Pippi Longstocking is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Astrid Lindgren and illustrated by Ingrid Vang Nyman. This book is perfect for children between the ages of 6 and 10 years old, as it features an engaging story with vibrant illustrations that capture the imagination of young readers. The story follows the adventures of Pippi Longstocking, a young girl with fiery red pigtails and incredible strength.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roule Galette</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/roule_galette_by_natha_caputo_isbn_9782081285477/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/roule_galette_by_natha_caputo_isbn_9782081285477/</guid>
      <description>Roule Galette by Natha Caputo Title: Roule Galette Author: Natha Caputo Roule Galette is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a little galette (a type of French pastry) who dreams of exploring the world and embarks on a thrilling adventure. This book is perfect for children aged 4 to 8 years old, as it captures their imagination and teaches them valuable life lessons. The illustrations in Roule Galette are vibrant and eye-catching, which will keep the young readers engaged.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Doll&#39;s House</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_dolls_house_by_rumer_godden_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_dolls_house_by_rumer_godden_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Doll&amp;rsquo;s House by Rumer Godden Title: The Doll&amp;rsquo;s House Author: Rumer Godden The Doll&amp;rsquo;s House, written by Rumer Godden, is a charming and enchanting children&amp;rsquo;s book that captures the essence of childhood imagination and the importance of friendship. The story revolves around two young sisters, Tottie and Emily, who receive a beautiful dollhouse as a gift. The dollhouse becomes a magical world where the dolls come to life and experience their own adventures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Little Red Engine Gets a Name</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_little_red_engine_gets_a_name_by_diana_ross_isbn_571064396/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_little_red_engine_gets_a_name_by_diana_ross_isbn_571064396/</guid>
      <description>The Little Red Engine Gets a Name by Diana Ross Title: The Little Red Engine Gets a Name Author: Diana Ross Review: The Little Red Engine Gets a Name is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Diana Ross. This delightful story follows the adventures of a little red engine who doesn&amp;rsquo;t have a name. The little red engine embarks on a journey to find a name that truly represents who they are.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tiger Who Came to Tea</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/tiger_who_came_to_tea_by_judith_kerr_isbn_9780060517809/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/tiger_who_came_to_tea_by_judith_kerr_isbn_9780060517809/</guid>
      <description>Tiger Who Came to Tea by Judith Kerr Title: The Tiger Who Came to Tea Author: Judith Kerr Review: The Tiger Who Came to Tea is a charming and delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Judith Kerr. This story follows the adventures of a young girl named Sophie and her family, who experience an unexpected visit from a friendly tiger. The book is beautifully illustrated, with vibrant colors and playful drawings that will capture the imagination of young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Visit From St. Nicholas</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/a_visit_from_st._nicholas_by_the_night_before_christmas_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/a_visit_from_st._nicholas_by_the_night_before_christmas_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>A Visit From St. Nicholas by The Night Before Christmas Title: A Visit from St. Nicholas (The Night Before Christmas) Author: Clement C. Moore Illustrator: Jessie Willcox Smith A Visit from St. Nicholas, also known as The Night Before Christmas, is a timeless classic that has been cherished by children and adults alike for generations. Written by Clement C. Moore and beautifully illustrated by Jessie Willcox Smith, this book brings to life the enchanting story of a visit from the jolly old elf, Santa Claus, on Christmas Eve.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ameliaranne and the Green Umbrella</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/ameliaranne_and_the_green_umbrella_by_constance_heward_isbn_245551042/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/ameliaranne_and_the_green_umbrella_by_constance_heward_isbn_245551042/</guid>
      <description>Ameliaranne and the Green Umbrella by Constance Heward Title: Ameliaranne and the Green Umbrella Author: Constance Heward Ameliaranne and the Green Umbrella is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the adventures of a young girl named Ameliaranne and her magical green umbrella. The story takes place in a whimsical world where anything is possible, and Ameliaranne learns valuable life lessons along the way. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 6 and 10 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bad Habits!</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/bad_habits_by_babette_cole_isbn_9780140564518/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/bad_habits_by_babette_cole_isbn_9780140564518/</guid>
      <description>Bad Habits! by Babette Cole Title: Bad Habits! Author: Babette Cole Review: Bad Habits! is a delightful and humorous children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Babette Cole, which takes readers on a journey through the lives of a group of animals who struggle with their own bad habits. The book targets the age group of 4 to 8-year-olds, and it is an excellent choice for parents and teachers looking for a fun and engaging way to teach children about the importance of good habits and self-improvement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crispin</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/crispin_by_ted_dewan_isbn_9780606305556/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/crispin_by_ted_dewan_isbn_9780606305556/</guid>
      <description>Crispin by Ted Dewan Title: Crispin Author: Ted Dewan Crispin is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Ted Dewan, which tells the story of a young boy named Crispin and his adventures in a magical world. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 5 and 8 years old, and it beautifully covers essential life lessons that are crucial for young readers. The story revolves around Crispin, a curious and imaginative boy who embarks on a journey to find his missing toy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crocodile Beat</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/crocodile_beat_by_gail_jorgensen_isbn_689718810/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/crocodile_beat_by_gail_jorgensen_isbn_689718810/</guid>
      <description>Crocodile Beat by Gail Jorgensen Title: Crocodile Beat Author: Gail Jorgensen Crocodile Beat is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Gail Jorgensen, which takes the reader on an adventurous journey into the world of a young crocodile named Croc. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 4 to 8 years old and is filled with vibrant illustrations that capture the imagination of young readers. The story follows Croc as he learns to play the drums and eventually forms a band with his animal friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fire-Engine Lil</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/fire-engine_lil_by_janet_mclean_andrew_mclean_isbn_9780048200358/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/fire-engine_lil_by_janet_mclean_andrew_mclean_isbn_9780048200358/</guid>
      <description>Fire-Engine Lil by Janet McLean, Andrew McLean Title: Fire-Engine Lil Author: Janet McLean, Andrew McLean Review: Fire-Engine Lil is a charming and delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young girl named Lil, who dreams of becoming a firefighter. The book is beautifully illustrated with vibrant colors and engaging images that capture the imagination of young readers. The target age group for this book is 4 to 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marc Just Couldn&#39;t Sleep</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/marc_just_couldnt_sleep_by_gabriela_keselman_isbn_9781929132911/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/marc_just_couldnt_sleep_by_gabriela_keselman_isbn_9781929132911/</guid>
      <description>Marc Just Couldn&amp;rsquo;t Sleep by Gabriela Keselman Title: Marc Just Couldn&amp;rsquo;t Sleep Author: Gabriela Keselman Review: Marc Just Couldn&amp;rsquo;t Sleep is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young boy named Marc who struggles to fall asleep at night. Through vivid illustrations and engaging storytelling, author Gabriela Keselman takes readers on a journey with Marc as he tries various methods to overcome his sleeplessness. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 4 and 8, making it an ideal bedtime story for parents to read with their young ones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Max</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/max_by_bob_graham_isbn_613565177/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/max_by_bob_graham_isbn_613565177/</guid>
      <description>Max by Bob Graham Title: Max Author: Bob Graham Max is a heartwarming and thought-provoking children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the talented author and illustrator, Bob Graham. This beautifully illustrated story follows the adventures of a young boy named Max, who finds a homeless dog and takes it upon himself to care for and protect the animal. Targeted Age Group: Max is most suitable for children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Milly-Molly-Mandy</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/milly-molly-mandy_by_joyce_lankester_brisley_isbn_024556845x/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/milly-molly-mandy_by_joyce_lankester_brisley_isbn_024556845x/</guid>
      <description>Milly-Molly-Mandy by Joyce Lankester Brisley Title: Milly-Molly-Mandy Author: Joyce Lankester Brisley Milly-Molly-Mandy is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Joyce Lankester Brisley, first published in 1928. The story follows the adventures of a young girl named Milly-Molly-Mandy and her friends in a quaint English village. The book is targeted towards children aged 4 to 8 years old, as it contains simple language and charming illustrations that capture the imagination of young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mousehole Cat</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/mousehole_cat_by_antonia_barber_isbn_8426436374/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/mousehole_cat_by_antonia_barber_isbn_8426436374/</guid>
      <description>Mousehole Cat by Antonia Barber Title: The Mousehole Cat Author: Antonia Barber Illustrator: Nicola Bayley Review: The Mousehole Cat is a beautifully illustrated and engaging children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a magical cat named Mowzer, who lives in the Cornish village of Mousehole. The book is set in the 16th century and revolves around the legend of the evil owl-king, who has cast a spell on the village, causing the fishermen to be unable to catch any fish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Now We Are Six</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/now_we_are_six_isbn_749711795/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/now_we_are_six_isbn_749711795/</guid>
      <description>Now We Are Six Title: Now We Are Six Author: A.A. Milne Review: Now We Are Six is a delightful collection of poems and stories written by A.A. Milne, the creator of the beloved Winnie-the-Pooh series. This book is a perfect read for children aged 5 to 8 years old, as it captures the essence of childhood innocence and imagination. The book consists of various poems and short stories, each one offering a unique perspective on the world through the eyes of a child.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Old Bear</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/old_bear_isbn_99413353/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/old_bear_isbn_99413353/</guid>
      <description>Old Bear Title: Old Bear Author: Kevin Henkes Review: Old Bear is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book written and illustrated by Kevin Henkes. The story revolves around a young girl named Emily, who is given a stuffed bear as a gift by her grandmother. The bear, named Old Bear, is well-loved by Emily and becomes her constant companion. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 4 to 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Olivia</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/olivia_isbn_740743090/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/olivia_isbn_740743090/</guid>
      <description>Olivia Title: Olivia Author: Ian Falconer Target Age Group: 4-8 years old Olivia is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the adventures of a young pig named Olivia. The story is written by Ian Falconer and is perfect for children aged 4-8 years old. The book is filled with beautiful illustrations that capture the imagination of young readers and help them connect with the story. One of the key life lessons covered in the book is the importance of being true to oneself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Poems for the Very Young</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/poems_for_the_very_young_by_michael_rosen_isbn_9781856971164/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/poems_for_the_very_young_by_michael_rosen_isbn_9781856971164/</guid>
      <description>Poems for the Very Young by Michael Rosen Title: Poems for the Very Young Author: Michael Rosen Target Age Group: 4-8 years old &amp;ldquo;Poems for the Very Young&amp;rdquo; is a delightful collection of poems by Michael Rosen, specifically designed for young children. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old, making it an excellent choice for parents, teachers, and caregivers looking for engaging and educational content for their little ones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snugglepot and Cuddlepie</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/snugglepot_and_cuddlepie_by_may_gibbs_isbn_9780207167300/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/snugglepot_and_cuddlepie_by_may_gibbs_isbn_9780207167300/</guid>
      <description>Snugglepot and Cuddlepie by May Gibbs Title: Snugglepot and Cuddlepie Author: May Gibbs Review: Snugglepot and Cuddlepie is a charming and delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the talented Australian author and illustrator, May Gibbs. This classic tale, first published in 1918, has captivated the hearts of young readers for generations. The story follows the adventures of two lovable gumnut babies, Snugglepot and Cuddlepie, as they explore the Australian bush and encounter various creatures along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stina</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/stina_by_lena_anderson_isbn_9780688088804/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/stina_by_lena_anderson_isbn_9780688088804/</guid>
      <description>Stina by Lena Anderson Title: Stina Author: Lena Anderson Stina is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Lena Anderson, which follows the story of a young girl named Stina who embarks on a magical adventure. This book is suitable for children between the ages of 6 to 10 years old, as it contains simple language and beautiful illustrations that will captivate young readers. The story revolves around Stina, who discovers a hidden door in her grandmother&amp;rsquo;s house.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tatu and Patu in Helsinki</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/tatu_and_patu_in_helsinki_by_aino_havukainen_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/tatu_and_patu_in_helsinki_by_aino_havukainen_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Tatu and Patu in Helsinki by Aino Havukainen Title: Tatu and Patu in Helsinki Author: Aino Havukainen Review: Tatu and Patu in Helsinki is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes readers on a fun-filled adventure through the city of Helsinki with two lovable characters, Tatu and Patu. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 4 and 8, and is perfect for sparking their curiosity and interest in exploring new places.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Wonderful Farm</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_wonderful_farm_by_marcel_ayme_isbn_9780060203115/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_wonderful_farm_by_marcel_ayme_isbn_9780060203115/</guid>
      <description>The Wonderful Farm by Marcel Ayme Title: The Wonderful Farm Author: Marcel Ayme Review: The Wonderful Farm is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes readers on a magical journey through the eyes of a young boy named Nicolas. This enchanting story, written by the talented Marcel Ayme, is a perfect read for children between the ages of 6 and 10 years old. The story follows Nicolas as he stumbles upon a farm that is anything but ordinary.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Bear Called Paddington</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/a_bear_called_paddington_isbn_9780440404835/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/a_bear_called_paddington_isbn_9780440404835/</guid>
      <description>A Bear Called Paddington Title: A Bear Called Paddington Author: Michael Bond A Bear Called Paddington is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Michael Bond, first published in 1958. The story follows the adventures of a lovable bear named Paddington, who arrives in London from Peru and is taken in by the Brown family. Target Age Group: A Bear Called Paddington is suitable for children aged 6 to 10 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Avocado Baby</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/avocado_baby_by_john_burningham_isbn_690042434/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/avocado_baby_by_john_burningham_isbn_690042434/</guid>
      <description>Avocado Baby by John Burningham Title: Avocado Baby Author: John Burningham Review: Avocado Baby is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book by the talented author and illustrator John Burningham. The story follows the journey of a young couple who, after trying various methods to have a baby, finally succeed in growing one from an avocado seed. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old. It is filled with colorful and engaging illustrations that capture the imagination of young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clever Bill</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/clever_bill_by_william_nicholson_isbn_9780374313630/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/clever_bill_by_william_nicholson_isbn_9780374313630/</guid>
      <description>Clever Bill by William Nicholson Title: Clever Bill Author: William Nicholson Review: Clever Bill is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young boy named Bill, who, despite being small and not very strong, possesses a great deal of intelligence and creativity. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 5 and 8, making it a perfect addition to any elementary school classroom or home library.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corduroy</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/corduroy_isbn_9780140558555/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/corduroy_isbn_9780140558555/</guid>
      <description>Corduroy Title: Corduroy Author: Don Freeman Target Age Group: 3-7 years old Corduroy, written by Don Freeman, is a heartwarming and timeless children&amp;rsquo;s book that has captured the hearts of young readers for generations. The story follows the adventures of a small, lovable teddy bear named Corduroy, who lives in a department store and dreams of finding a home with a loving child. The book is beautifully illustrated with vibrant colors and charming characters that engage the young readers&amp;rsquo; imagination.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Curious George</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/curious_george_isbn_9781435120501/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/curious_george_isbn_9781435120501/</guid>
      <description>Curious George Title: Curious George Author: H.A. Rey Age Group: 4-8 years old Curious George is a classic children&amp;rsquo;s book written by H.A. Rey, first published in 1941. The story follows the adventures of a mischievous monkey named George, who is brought from his home in the jungle to live in a big city. Throughout the book, George gets into various situations as he explores his new surroundings, all while learning valuable life lessons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eloise</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/eloise_isbn_9780689843112/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/eloise_isbn_9780689843112/</guid>
      <description>Eloise Title: Eloise Author: Kay Thompson Illustrator: Hilary Knight Review: Eloise is a charming and delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the adventures of a young girl named Eloise who lives in the Plaza Hotel in New York City. The story is filled with whimsical illustrations and playful rhymes that will capture the attention of young readers. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ernest and Celestine Have Lost Simon</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/ernest_and_celestine_have_lost_simon_by_gabrielle_vincent_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/ernest_and_celestine_have_lost_simon_by_gabrielle_vincent_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Ernest and Celestine Have Lost Simon by Gabrielle Vincent Title: Ernest and Celestine Have Lost Simon Author: Gabrielle Vincent &amp;ldquo;Ernest and Celestine Have Lost Simon&amp;rdquo; is a heartwarming and adventurous children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Gabrielle Vincent. The story follows the endearing characters of Ernest, a large bear, and Celestine, a small mouse, as they embark on a journey to find their lost friend, Simon. Targeted towards children aged 4-8, this book beautifully illustrates the importance of friendship, teamwork, and perseverance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Father Christmas</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/father_christmas_by_raymond_briggs_isbn_9780241022603/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/father_christmas_by_raymond_briggs_isbn_9780241022603/</guid>
      <description>Father Christmas by Raymond Briggs Title: Father Christmas Author: Raymond Briggs Father Christmas, written by Raymond Briggs, is a heartwarming and humorous children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes us on a journey through the life of the beloved Christmas icon. The story follows Father Christmas as he goes about his daily tasks, such as feeding the reindeer, cleaning the sleigh, and, of course, delivering presents to children all over the world. The illustrations in the book are vibrant and engaging, with a unique blend of humor and warmth that is sure to capture the attention of young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gorilla</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/gorilla_by_anthony_browne_isbn_9780763618131/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/gorilla_by_anthony_browne_isbn_9780763618131/</guid>
      <description>Gorilla by Anthony Browne Title: Gorilla Author: Anthony Browne Review: Gorilla is a beautifully illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the talented author and illustrator, Anthony Browne. This heartwarming story follows the journey of a young girl named Hannah, who is trying to cope with the absence of her father. As she struggles to find solace in her everyday life, she turns to her toy gorilla for comfort and support. The book is targeted towards children aged 4-8 years old, as it addresses themes of love, loss, and the importance of family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little Blue and Little Yellow</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/little_blue_and_little_yellow_by_leo_lionni_isbn_9780340035764/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/little_blue_and_little_yellow_by_leo_lionni_isbn_9780340035764/</guid>
      <description>Little Blue and Little Yellow by Leo Lionni Title: Little Blue and Little Yellow Author: Leo Lionni Review: Little Blue and Little Yellow is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written and illustrated by Leo Lionni. The story follows the adventures of two friends, Little Blue and Little Yellow, who are both colors. Throughout the book, they learn about the importance of friendship, acceptance, and embracing change. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 4 to 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little I Am I</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/little_i_am_i_by_mira_lobe_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/little_i_am_i_by_mira_lobe_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Little I Am I by Mira Lobe Title: Little I Am I Author: Mira Lobe Review: Little I Am I is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Mira Lobe, which is perfect for young readers between the ages of 4 and 8. The book follows the story of a little girl who is trying to find her place in the world and learn about the importance of self-worth. The illustrations in the book are vibrant and eye-catching, which helps to keep the young readers engaged.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mike Mulligan</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/mike_mulligan_by_virginia_lee_burton_isbn_9789995250270/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/mike_mulligan_by_virginia_lee_burton_isbn_9789995250270/</guid>
      <description>Mike Mulligan by Virginia Lee Burton Title: Mike Mulligan and His Steam Shovel Author: Virginia Lee Burton Review: Mike Mulligan and His Steam Shovel is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of Mike Mulligan, a hardworking and dedicated steam shovel operator, and his trusty steam shovel, Mary Anne. The book is perfect for children aged 4 to 8 years old and teaches valuable life lessons about perseverance, friendship, and adapting to change.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mister Magnolia</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/mister_magnolia_by_quentin_blake_isbn_224016121/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/mister_magnolia_by_quentin_blake_isbn_224016121/</guid>
      <description>Mister Magnolia by Quentin Blake Title: Mister Magnolia Author: Quentin Blake Review: Mister Magnolia is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written and illustrated by the talented Quentin Blake. The story follows the adventures of Mister Magnolia, a charming and eccentric character who is missing one boot. Throughout the book, Mister Magnolia goes about his day, encountering various animals and objects, all while trying to find his missing boot. The illustrations in Mister Magnolia are vibrant and engaging, with Blake&amp;rsquo;s signature style adding a whimsical touch to the story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Woolly Wombat</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/one_woolly_wombat_by_rod_trinca_isbn_916291006/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/one_woolly_wombat_by_rod_trinca_isbn_916291006/</guid>
      <description>One Woolly Wombat by Rod Trinca Title: One Woolly Wombat Author: Rod Trinca One Woolly Wombat is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Rod Trinca, which takes young readers on a fun and educational journey through the Australian bush. With its engaging illustrations and simple rhyming text, this book is perfect for children aged 3-6 years old. The story follows the adventures of a woolly wombat who encounters various Australian animals along the way, such as kangaroos, koalas, and emus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peace at Last</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/peace_at_last_isbn_9780230015487/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/peace_at_last_isbn_9780230015487/</guid>
      <description>Peace at Last Title: Peace at Last Author: Jill Murphy Target Age Group: 4-8 years old Review: &amp;ldquo;Peace at Last&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Jill Murphy, which takes young readers on a heartwarming adventure with the endearing Mr. Bear and his family. The story follows Mr. Bear as he tries to find a quiet place to sleep after being constantly disturbed by the noises made by his family members.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peter in Blueberry Land</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/peter_in_blueberry_land_by_elsa_beskow_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/peter_in_blueberry_land_by_elsa_beskow_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Peter in Blueberry Land by Elsa Beskow Title: Peter in Blueberry Land Author: Elsa Beskow Review: &amp;ldquo;Peter in Blueberry Land&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book by the renowned Swedish author and illustrator, Elsa Beskow. The story follows Peter, a young boy who embarks on a magical adventure in a land filled with talking blueberries and other enchanting creatures. This charming book is perfect for children aged 4 to 8 years old, as it captivates their imaginations and teaches them valuable life lessons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Possum Magic</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/possum_magic_isbn_1862915644/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/possum_magic_isbn_1862915644/</guid>
      <description>Possum Magic Title: Possum Magic Author: Mem Fox Illustrator: Julie Vivas Recommended Age Group: 4-8 years old Possum Magic is a delightful and enchanting story that captures the hearts of young readers and adults alike. The story follows the adventures of Grandma Poss and her granddaughter, Hush, as they travel across Australia in search of the magic that has been lost. The book is beautifully illustrated by Julie Vivas, who brings the Australian landscape and its unique creatures to life with her whimsical and charming drawings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Cat in the Hat</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_cat_in_the_hat_by_dr._seuss_isbn_000820151x/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_cat_in_the_hat_by_dr._seuss_isbn_000820151x/</guid>
      <description>The Cat in the Hat by Dr. Seuss Title: The Cat in the Hat Author: Dr. Seuss Review: The Cat in the Hat is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the renowned author Dr. Seuss. The story follows the adventures of a mischievous cat who visits two children, Sally and her brother, on a rainy day. The Cat in the Hat teaches valuable life lessons while keeping the reader entertained with its whimsical rhymes and colorful illustrations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Jolly Aunt</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_jolly_aunt_by_lothar_meggendorfer_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_jolly_aunt_by_lothar_meggendorfer_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Jolly Aunt by Lothar Meggendorfer Title: The Jolly Aunt Author: Lothar Meggendorfer Review: The Jolly Aunt is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Lothar Meggendorfer. This book is a perfect read for children aged 4-8 years old. The story revolves around an aunt who is known for her cheerful and playful nature. The aunt visits her nieces and nephews, bringing with her a bag full of surprises. The illustrations in this book are beautiful and captivating, making it a great read for both children and adults.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Does the Mouse Think on Thursday</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/what_does_the_mouse_think_on_thursday_by_josef_guggenmos_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/what_does_the_mouse_think_on_thursday_by_josef_guggenmos_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>What Does the Mouse Think on Thursday by Josef Guggenmos Title: &amp;ldquo;What Does the Mouse Think on Thursday&amp;rdquo; Author: Josef Guggenmos Review: &amp;ldquo;What Does the Mouse Think on Thursday&amp;rdquo; is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the adventures of a curious little mouse named Tuffy. The story takes place over the course of a week, with each day bringing new discoveries and experiences for Tuffy. The book is written in a simple and engaging manner, making it perfect for young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where the Wild Things Are</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/where_the_wild_things_are_isbn_9780439052139/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/where_the_wild_things_are_isbn_9780439052139/</guid>
      <description>Where the Wild Things Are Title: Where the Wild Things Are Author: Maurice Sendak Recommended Age Group: 4-8 years old Where the Wild Things Are is a timeless classic written and illustrated by Maurice Sendak. The story follows a young boy named Max, who, after being sent to his room without supper for misbehaving, embarks on a wild adventure with mysterious and fantastical creatures. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who&#39;s Seen the Scissors?</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/whos_seen_the_scissors_by_fernando_krahn_isbn_525427104/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/whos_seen_the_scissors_by_fernando_krahn_isbn_525427104/</guid>
      <description>Who&amp;rsquo;s Seen the Scissors? by Fernando Krahn Title: &amp;ldquo;Who&amp;rsquo;s Seen the Scissors?&amp;quot; Author: Fernando Krahn Review: &amp;ldquo;Who&amp;rsquo;s Seen the Scissors?&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book by Fernando Krahn that follows the adventures of a group of friendly animals living in a peaceful forest. The story is engaging and filled with colorful illustrations that capture the imagination of young readers. The book targets children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old, making it an excellent choice for parents, teachers, and caregivers looking for a fun and educational read.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bedtime for Frances</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/bedtime_for_frances_by_russell_hoban_isbn_9780571052745/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/bedtime_for_frances_by_russell_hoban_isbn_9780571052745/</guid>
      <description>Bedtime for Frances by Russell Hoban Title: Bedtime for Frances Author: Russell Hoban Review: Bedtime for Frances is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Russell Hoban. The story follows a young badger named Frances who is reluctant to go to bed, as she is afraid of the dark and monsters under her bed. With the help of her loving and patient parents, Frances learns to overcome her fears and embrace bedtime.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elmer the Patchwork Elephant</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/elmer_the_patchwork_elephant_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/elmer_the_patchwork_elephant_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Elmer the Patchwork Elephant Title: Elmer the Patchwork Elephant Author: David McKee Elmer the Patchwork Elephant is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by David McKee. The story follows Elmer, a young elephant with a unique appearance - he is covered in a patchwork of colors. The book is suitable for children between the ages of 3 and 8 years old, and it teaches valuable life lessons about embracing one&amp;rsquo;s individuality and the importance of friendship.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fly, Little Bird</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/fly_little_bird_by_francesco_tullio_altan_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/fly_little_bird_by_francesco_tullio_altan_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Fly, Little Bird by Francesco Tullio Altan Title: Fly, Little Bird Author: Francesco Tullio Altan Fly, Little Bird is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book by Francesco Tullio Altan that tells the story of a young bird who dreams of flying high and exploring the world. The book is perfect for children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old, as it is filled with colorful illustrations and simple, yet engaging language.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kipper</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/kipper_by_mick_inkpen_isbn_152022945/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/kipper_by_mick_inkpen_isbn_152022945/</guid>
      <description>Kipper by Mick Inkpen Title: Kipper Author: Mick Inkpen Review: Kipper, written by Mick Inkpen, is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the adventures of a lovable and curious dog named Kipper. The book is filled with vibrant illustrations that capture the attention of young readers and engage their imagination. The story is suitable for children aged 4 to 8 years old, as it teaches important life lessons in a fun and engaging manner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little Spook&#39;s Baby Sister</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/little_spooks_baby_sister_by_inger_sandberg_isbn_9780416869200/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/little_spooks_baby_sister_by_inger_sandberg_isbn_9780416869200/</guid>
      <description>Little Spook&amp;rsquo;s Baby Sister by Inger Sandberg Title: Little Spook&amp;rsquo;s Baby Sister Author: Inger Sandberg Review: Little Spook&amp;rsquo;s Baby Sister is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Inger Sandberg, which tells the story of Little Spook, a friendly ghost, who is excited to become a big brother. The book is beautifully illustrated and has a charming, whimsical quality that is sure to capture the attention of young readers. The story follows Little Spook as he prepares for the arrival of his baby sister.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Miffy</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/miffy_by_dick_bruna_isbn_1592260225/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/miffy_by_dick_bruna_isbn_1592260225/</guid>
      <description>Miffy by Dick Bruna Title: Miffy Author: Dick Bruna Review: Miffy, written by Dick Bruna, is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young bunny named Miffy. This book is perfect for children aged 3-6 years old, as it features simple yet engaging illustrations and a straightforward narrative. The story follows Miffy as she goes about her day, encountering various situations and learning valuable life lessons along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Bear Went Over the Mountain</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_bear_went_over_the_mountain_by_john_prater_isbn_9780370323688/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_bear_went_over_the_mountain_by_john_prater_isbn_9780370323688/</guid>
      <description>The Bear Went Over the Mountain by John Prater Title: The Bear Went Over the Mountain Author: John Prater Review: The Bear Went Over the Mountain is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a curious bear who decides to explore the world beyond his familiar mountain home. With vibrant illustrations and engaging storytelling, author John Prater captures the imagination of young readers and takes them on a journey of discovery and adventure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Elephant and the Bad Baby</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_elephant_and_the_bad_baby_by_elfrida_vipont_isbn_9780140500486/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_elephant_and_the_bad_baby_by_elfrida_vipont_isbn_9780140500486/</guid>
      <description>The Elephant and the Bad Baby by Elfrida Vipont Title: The Elephant and the Bad Baby Author: Elfrida Vipont The Elephant and the Bad Baby is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Elfrida Vipont. The story follows the adventures of a mischievous baby who encounters an elephant in his quest for sweets. The book is beautifully illustrated by Raymond Briggs, adding to the charm of the story. The target age group for this book is 3-7 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Little Engine That Could</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_little_engine_that_could_by_watty_piper_isbn_448189631/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_little_engine_that_could_by_watty_piper_isbn_448189631/</guid>
      <description>The Little Engine That Could by Watty Piper Title: The Little Engine That Could Author: Watty Piper The Little Engine That Could is a classic children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Watty Piper. This heartwarming story has been a favorite among children and parents alike for generations. The book is beautifully illustrated and has a simple, yet powerful message that resonates with readers of all ages. The story revolves around a little blue engine that is faced with the daunting task of pulling a long train over a steep mountain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We&#39;re Going on a Bear Hunt</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/were_going_on_a_bear_hunt_isbn_9781844280841/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/were_going_on_a_bear_hunt_isbn_9781844280841/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re Going on a Bear Hunt Title: We&amp;rsquo;re Going on a Bear Hunt Author: Michael Rosen Illustrator: Helen Oxenbury Recommended Age Group: 3-8 years old We&amp;rsquo;re Going on a Bear Hunt is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Michael Rosen and illustrated by Helen Oxenbury. The story follows a family on a thrilling adventure as they go on a bear hunt. The book is a perfect blend of engaging illustrations and a captivating narrative that captures the attention of young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
