<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Childrens Books that talk about &#39;Nurture&#39; on Monsty The Monster Truck</title>
    <link>https://www.monsty.co/tags/childrens-books-that-talk-about-nurture/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Childrens Books that talk about &#39;Nurture&#39; on Monsty The Monster Truck</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.monsty.co/tags/childrens-books-that-talk-about-nurture/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Toby Alone</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/toby_alone_by_timothee_de_fombelle_isbn_1441888837/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/toby_alone_by_timothee_de_fombelle_isbn_1441888837/</guid>
      <description>Toby Alone by Timothee De Fombelle Title: Toby Alone Author: Timothee De Fombelle Review: Toby Alone is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Timothee De Fombelle, which tells the story of a young boy named Toby who lives in a world of miniature people hidden within the trees. The book is a perfect blend of adventure, friendship, and courage, making it an ideal read for children between the ages of 8 and 12.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>White Fang</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/white_fang_isbn_816158924/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/white_fang_isbn_816158924/</guid>
      <description>White Fang Title: White Fang Author: Jack London Target Age Group: 8-12 years old Review: White Fang is a captivating and heartwarming story that follows the life of a wolf-dog hybrid named White Fang. Set in the Yukon Territory during the Klondike Gold Rush, the book delves into the themes of survival, loyalty, and the transformative power of love. The story is divided into two parts, each focusing on a different phase of White Fang&amp;rsquo;s life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Journey to the River Sea</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/journey_to_the_river_sea_by_eva_ibbotson_isbn_9780525467397/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/journey_to_the_river_sea_by_eva_ibbotson_isbn_9780525467397/</guid>
      <description>Journey to the River Sea by Eva Ibbotson Title: Journey to the River Sea Author: Eva Ibbotson Review: Journey to the River Sea is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book by Eva Ibbotson, which takes the reader on a thrilling adventure through the Amazon rainforest. The story follows the life of Maia, an orphan who is sent to live with distant relatives in Brazil. The book is targeted towards children aged 9-12 years old, as it features relatable themes and engaging storytelling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Friday or the Savage Life</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/friday_or_the_savage_life_by_michel_tournier_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/friday_or_the_savage_life_by_michel_tournier_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Friday or the Savage Life by Michel Tournier Title: Friday or the Savage Life Author: Michel Tournier Friday or the Savage Life is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Michel Tournier. The story is set in a remote island where the protagonist, Friday, lives a life of solitude, far away from the hustle and bustle of civilization. The book is a perfect blend of adventure, self-discovery, and the importance of friendship.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stig of the Dump</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/stig_of_the_dump_isbn_754065766/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/stig_of_the_dump_isbn_754065766/</guid>
      <description>Stig of the Dump Title: Stig of the Dump Author: Clive King Target Age Group: 7-12 years old Stig of the Dump is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Clive King, which tells the story of a young boy named Barney who discovers a caveman named Stig living in a nearby dump. The book takes readers on a delightful adventure as Barney and Stig form a unique friendship, teaching valuable life lessons along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Adventures of Rupert the Toad</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_adventures_of_rupert_the_toad_by_roy_berocay_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_adventures_of_rupert_the_toad_by_roy_berocay_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Adventures of Rupert the Toad by Roy Berocay Title: The Adventures of Rupert the Toad Author: Roy Berocay Review: The Adventures of Rupert the Toad is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the journey of a young toad named Rupert. Author Roy Berocay has skillfully crafted a story that is not only entertaining but also teaches valuable life lessons to young readers. The book is suitable for children aged 4-8 years old, as it features simple language and engaging illustrations that capture the imagination of young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Bagthorpe Saga: Ordinary Jack</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_bagthorpe_saga_ordinary_jack_by_helen_cresswell_isbn_27255409/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_bagthorpe_saga_ordinary_jack_by_helen_cresswell_isbn_27255409/</guid>
      <description>The Bagthorpe Saga: Ordinary Jack by Helen Cresswell Title: The Bagthorpe Saga: Ordinary Jack Author: Helen Cresswell Review: The Bagthorpe Saga: Ordinary Jack is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Helen Cresswell. This engaging story follows the life of a young boy named Jack and his adventures with his eccentric family, the Bagthorpes. The book is filled with humor, relatable characters, and a heartwarming message that will resonate with readers of all ages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Garden</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_garden_by_jiri_trnka_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_garden_by_jiri_trnka_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Garden by Jiri Trnka Title: The Garden Author: Jiri Trnka The Garden is a beautifully illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book by Jiri Trnka, which tells the story of a young boy named John who embarks on a magical adventure in a mysterious garden. This book is a perfect read for children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old, as it is filled with vibrant pictures and simple yet engaging text.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The White Stone</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_white_stone_by_gunnel_linde_isbn_152959106/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_white_stone_by_gunnel_linde_isbn_152959106/</guid>
      <description>The White Stone by Gunnel Linde Title: The White Stone Author: Gunnel Linde Review: The White Stone is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Gunnel Linde that tells the story of a young girl named Mia, who is trying to find her place in the world. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old and covers various life lessons that are essential for their growth and development.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minnow on the Say</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/minnow_on_the_say_by_philippa_pearce_isbn_9780192710772/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/minnow_on_the_say_by_philippa_pearce_isbn_9780192710772/</guid>
      <description>Minnow on the Say by Philippa Pearce Title: Minnow on the Say Author: Philippa Pearce Review: Minnow on the Say is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Philippa Pearce, which tells the story of two young boys, David and Adam, who embark on a thrilling adventure along the River Say. The book is suitable for children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old and is filled with captivating themes, life lessons, and an engaging narrative.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Hundred Dresses</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_hundred_dresses_isbn_9780812455274/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_hundred_dresses_isbn_9780812455274/</guid>
      <description>The Hundred Dresses Title: The Hundred Dresses Author: Eleanese Estes Review: The Hundred Dresses is a heartwarming and thought-provoking children&amp;rsquo;s book that tackles the important themes of bullying, empathy, and the power of kindness. Written by Eleanor Estes, this classic story has been cherished by generations of young readers since its publication in 1944. The book follows the story of Wanda Petronski, a young girl who is bullied by her classmates for being different.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Little Bookroom</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_little_bookroom_isbn_9780192719478/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_little_bookroom_isbn_9780192719478/</guid>
      <description>The Little Bookroom Title: The Little Bookroom Author: Eleanor Farjeon Illustrator: Edward Ardizzone The Little Bookroom is a charming and delightful collection of short stories that will captivate the hearts of young readers. Eleanor Farjeon, the author, has skillfully woven a tapestry of tales that transport the reader to a world of enchantment and adventure. The book is accompanied by beautiful illustrations by Edward Ardizzone, which add to the overall charm of the stories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Happy Prince and Other Tales</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_happy_prince_and_other_tales_by_oscar_wilde_isbn_9780486270913/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_happy_prince_and_other_tales_by_oscar_wilde_isbn_9780486270913/</guid>
      <description>The Happy Prince and Other Tales by Oscar Wilde Title: The Happy Prince and Other Tales Author: Oscar Wilde Review: The Happy Prince and Other Tales is a collection of five beautifully written and illustrated stories by the renowned author, Oscar Wilde. The book is designed to target children between the ages of 6 to 12 years old, making it an excellent choice for parents, teachers, and caregivers looking for an engaging and meaningful read for their young ones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Wonderful Wizard of Oz</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_wonderful_wizard_of_oz_isbn_9781520209166/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_wonderful_wizard_of_oz_isbn_9781520209166/</guid>
      <description>The Wonderful Wizard of Oz Title: The Wonderful Wizard of Oz Author: L. Frank Baum Review: The Wonderful Wizard of Oz is a timeless classic that has enchanted readers of all ages since its publication in 1900. The story follows the adventures of a young girl named Dorothy, who is swept away from her Kansas farm by a tornado and finds herself in the magical land of Oz. Along her journey, she encounters a colorful cast of characters, including the Scarecrow, the Tin Woodman, and the Cowardly Lion, who join her on her quest to find the Wizard of Oz and help her return home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Boy Who Grew Flowers</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_boy_who_grew_flowers_by_jen_wojtowicz_isbn_1846867495/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_boy_who_grew_flowers_by_jen_wojtowicz_isbn_1846867495/</guid>
      <description>The Boy Who Grew Flowers by Jen Wojtowicz Title: The Boy Who Grew Flowers Author: Jen Wojtowicz Review: The Boy Who Grew Flowers is a heartwarming and imaginative children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Jen Wojtowicz. The story follows a young boy named Rink, who possesses a unique ability to grow flowers from his body. Initially, Rink feels embarrassed and isolated due to his extraordinary gift, but he eventually learns to embrace his differences and make friends with a kind and understanding girl named Angelina.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crispin</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/crispin_by_ted_dewan_isbn_9780606305556/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/crispin_by_ted_dewan_isbn_9780606305556/</guid>
      <description>Crispin by Ted Dewan Title: Crispin Author: Ted Dewan Crispin is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Ted Dewan, which tells the story of a young boy named Crispin and his adventures in a magical world. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 5 and 8 years old, and it beautifully covers essential life lessons that are crucial for young readers. The story revolves around Crispin, a curious and imaginative boy who embarks on a journey to find his missing toy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Garden of Little Creatures</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/garden_of_little_creatures_by_antoon_krings_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/garden_of_little_creatures_by_antoon_krings_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Garden of Little Creatures by Antoon Krings Title: Garden of Little Creatures Author: Antoon Krings Review: Garden of Little Creatures is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes readers on a whimsical journey through a magical garden filled with enchanting creatures. Author Antoon Krings has beautifully crafted a story that not only entertains but also teaches valuable life lessons to young readers. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brown Bear, Brown Bear, What Do You See?</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/brown_bear_brown_bear_what_do_you_see_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/brown_bear_brown_bear_what_do_you_see_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Brown Bear, Brown Bear, What Do You See? Title: Brown Bear, Brown Bear, What Do You See? Author: Bill Martin Jr. Illustrator: Eric Carle Review: Brown Bear, Brown Bear, What Do You See? is a delightful and engaging children&amp;rsquo;s book that captivates young readers with its vibrant illustrations and simple, rhythmic text. The book is ideal for children aged 2 to 5 years old, as it helps them develop their visual and auditory skills while introducing them to various animals and colors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peter in Blueberry Land</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/peter_in_blueberry_land_by_elsa_beskow_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/peter_in_blueberry_land_by_elsa_beskow_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Peter in Blueberry Land by Elsa Beskow Title: Peter in Blueberry Land Author: Elsa Beskow Review: &amp;ldquo;Peter in Blueberry Land&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book by the renowned Swedish author and illustrator, Elsa Beskow. The story follows Peter, a young boy who embarks on a magical adventure in a land filled with talking blueberries and other enchanting creatures. This charming book is perfect for children aged 4 to 8 years old, as it captivates their imaginations and teaches them valuable life lessons.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
