<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Childrens Books that talk about &#39;Patience&#39; on Monsty The Monster Truck</title>
    <link>https://www.monsty.co/tags/childrens-books-that-talk-about-patience/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Childrens Books that talk about &#39;Patience&#39; on Monsty The Monster Truck</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.monsty.co/tags/childrens-books-that-talk-about-patience/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Molly Goes Shopping</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/molly_goes_shopping_by_eva_eriksson_isbn_9129658195/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/molly_goes_shopping_by_eva_eriksson_isbn_9129658195/</guid>
      <description>Molly Goes Shopping by Eva Eriksson Title: Molly Goes Shopping Author: Eva Eriksson Molly Goes Shopping is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Eva Eriksson, aimed at children between the ages of 4 to 8 years old. The story follows the adventures of a young girl named Molly, who goes shopping with her mother and learns important life lessons along the way. The illustrations in the book are vibrant and engaging, capturing the attention of young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Big Birkett</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/my_big_birkett_by_lisa_shanahan_isbn_9781283918206/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/my_big_birkett_by_lisa_shanahan_isbn_9781283918206/</guid>
      <description>My Big Birkett by Lisa Shanahan Title: My Big Birkett Author: Lisa Shanahan My Big Birkett is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Lisa Shanahan. This beautifully illustrated story is perfect for children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old. The book is filled with valuable life lessons that will help children understand the importance of friendship, love, and self-acceptance. The story follows the life of a young boy named Birkett, who is known for being quite small in size.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Curious Incident of the Dog in the Night-Time – Mark Haddon</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_curious_incident_of_the_dog_in_the_night-time__mark_haddon_isbn_521613795/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_curious_incident_of_the_dog_in_the_night-time__mark_haddon_isbn_521613795/</guid>
      <description>The Curious Incident of the Dog in the Night-Time – Mark Haddon Title: The Curious Incident of the Dog in the Night-Time Author: Mark Haddon Age Group: 12 years and above &amp;ldquo;The Curious Incident of the Dog in the Night-Time&amp;rdquo; is a captivating and thought-provoking novel that tells the story of Christopher Boone, a 15-year-old boy with Asperger&amp;rsquo;s Syndrome. The book takes the reader on a journey through Christopher&amp;rsquo;s unique perspective as he navigates the complexities of everyday life and solves the mystery of a murdered dog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flour Babies</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/flour_babies_isbn_9780316283199/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/flour_babies_isbn_9780316283199/</guid>
      <description>Flour Babies Title: Flour Babies Author: Anne Fine Flour Babies is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Anne Fine, which was first published in 1992. The story revolves around a group of elementary school students who are given flour sacks as their &amp;lsquo;babies&amp;rsquo; to take care of, as part of a school project. The project aims to teach the students about the responsibilities and challenges of parenthood. The book is suitable for children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Summer Book</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_summer_book_isbn_140042725/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_summer_book_isbn_140042725/</guid>
      <description>The Summer Book Title: The Summer Book Review: The Summer Book is a charming and delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that captures the essence of a summer spent on a beautiful island. Written by Tove Jansson, the book follows the adventures of a young girl named Sophia and her grandmother as they explore the island, its flora, and fauna, and learn valuable life lessons along the way. Target Age Group: The Summer Book is perfect for children between the ages of 6 and 12.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Friend Flicka</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/my_friend_flicka_isbn_9780812420777/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/my_friend_flicka_isbn_9780812420777/</guid>
      <description>My Friend Flicka Title: My Friend Flicka Author: Mary O&amp;rsquo;Hara Review: My Friend Flicka is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young boy named Ken McLaughlin and his adventures with his horse, Flicka. The book is written by Mary O&amp;rsquo;Hara and is suitable for children between the ages of 8 and 12. The story is set on a ranch in Wyoming and follows Ken as he learns the importance of responsibility, patience, and perseverance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Lion</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_lion_by_joseph_kessel_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_lion_by_joseph_kessel_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Lion by Joseph Kessel Title: The Lion Author: Joseph Kessel Review: The Lion is a beautifully written children&amp;rsquo;s book by Joseph Kessel, which takes the readers on a captivating journey through the African wilderness. The story revolves around a young lion named Luk, who learns valuable life lessons as he navigates the challenges of growing up in the wild. Target Age Group: The Lion is a perfect read for children between the ages of 6 and 10 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Stowaway of the Ulysses</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_stowaway_of_the_ulysses_by_ana_maria_matute_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_stowaway_of_the_ulysses_by_ana_maria_matute_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Stowaway of the Ulysses by Ana Maria Matute Title: The Stowaway of the Ulysses Author: Ana Maria Matute Review: The Stowaway of the Ulysses is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young boy named David who embarks on a thrilling adventure aboard the ship Ulysses. The book is suitable for children aged 8-12 years old, as it contains elements of excitement, friendship, and self-discovery that will appeal to this age group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Something&#39;s Fishy, Hazel Green!</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/somethings_fishy_hazel_green_by_odo_hirsch_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/somethings_fishy_hazel_green_by_odo_hirsch_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Something&amp;rsquo;s Fishy, Hazel Green! by Odo Hirsch Title: Something&amp;rsquo;s Fishy, Hazel Green! Author: Odo Hirsch Review: &amp;ldquo;Something&amp;rsquo;s Fishy, Hazel Green!&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Odo Hirsch, which takes readers on a captivating journey through the eyes of its protagonist, Hazel Green. The story follows Hazel as she sets out to uncover the mystery behind a peculiar smell that has been plaguing her school. The book is primarily targeted towards children between the ages of 7 to 10 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Katy Did</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/what_katy_did_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/what_katy_did_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>What Katy Did Title: What Katy Did Author: Susan Coolidge Target Age Group: 8-12 years old &amp;ldquo;What Katy Did&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Susan Coolidge, originally published in 1872. The story revolves around the life of a young girl named Katy Carr and her family. The book has been cherished by generations of readers and continues to be a favorite among children today. The story is set in the 19th century and follows Katy, a lively and adventurous girl who loves to play with her siblings and friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Mole Always Turns Up on Its Own</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/a_mole_always_turns_up_on_its_own_by_hanna_johansen_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/a_mole_always_turns_up_on_its_own_by_hanna_johansen_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>A Mole Always Turns Up on Its Own by Hanna Johansen Title: A Mole Always Turns Up on Its Own Author: Hanna Johansen Review: &amp;ldquo;A Mole Always Turns Up on Its Own&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Hanna Johansen, which is perfect for children aged 4-8 years old. The story follows the journey of a mole who gets separated from its family and must find its way back home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manolito Quattrocchi</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/manolito_quattrocchi_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/manolito_quattrocchi_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Manolito Quattrocchi Title: Manolito Quattrocchi Author: Jorge Bucay Manolito Quattrocchi is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Jorge Bucay, which tells the story of a young boy named Manolito who embarks on a journey of self-discovery and learns valuable life lessons along the way. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old and is a perfect read for young readers who are beginning to explore the complexities of life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Wolves of Willoughby Chase</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_wolves_of_willoughby_chase_isbn_1435266544/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_wolves_of_willoughby_chase_isbn_1435266544/</guid>
      <description>The Wolves of Willoughby Chase Title: The Wolves of Willoughby Chase Author: Joan Aiken Recommended Age Group: 8-12 years old The Wolves of Willoughby Chase is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s novel written by Joan Aiken, first published in 1962. The story is set in an alternate 19th-century England and follows the adventures of two young cousins, Bonnie and Sylvia, as they navigate the challenges of living in a mysterious and sometimes dangerous manor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nesthakchen</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/nesthakchen_by_else_ury_isbn_3850011038/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/nesthakchen_by_else_ury_isbn_3850011038/</guid>
      <description>Nesthakchen by Else Ury Title: Nesthakchen Author: Else Ury Review: Nesthakchen is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Else Ury, which tells the story of a young girl named Anneliese who discovers a magical nest hidden in her garden. The nest is home to a family of talking birds who teach Anneliese valuable life lessons about friendship, courage, and the importance of cherishing the beauty of nature. The book is beautifully illustrated, and the vivid descriptions of the nest and its inhabitants make it easy for young readers to visualize the story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Platero and I</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/platero_and_i_isbn_9780292733282/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/platero_and_i_isbn_9780292733282/</guid>
      <description>Platero and I Title: Platero and I Author: Juan Ramón Jiménez Recommended Age Group: 8-12 years old Platero and I is a beautifully written and illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book that captures the essence of a young boy&amp;rsquo;s adventures with his loyal donkey, Platero, in a small Andalusian village. The book is filled with heartwarming stories that touch upon various life lessons, making it an excellent choice for children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Circus Is Coming</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_circus_is_coming_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_circus_is_coming_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Circus Is Coming Title: The Circus Is Coming Author: Phyllis Reynolds Naylor Review: The Circus Is Coming is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Phyllis Reynolds Naylor. This engaging story follows the adventures of a young boy named Nick as he eagerly awaits the arrival of the circus in his town. Target Age Group: The book is perfect for children between the ages of 6 and 10 years old. It is an excellent choice for early readers who are just starting to explore the world of chapter books.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are We There Yet?</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/are_we_there_yet_by_alison_lester_isbn_670880671/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/are_we_there_yet_by_alison_lester_isbn_670880671/</guid>
      <description>Are We There Yet? by Alison Lester Title: Are We There Yet? Author: Alison Lester Review: Are We There Yet? is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Alison Lester, which takes young readers on an exciting journey across Australia. The story follows Grace and her family as they embark on a road trip from their home in Melbourne to visit relatives in far-off Western Australia. The book is filled with vibrant illustrations and engaging storytelling, making it a perfect choice for children between the ages of 4 and 8.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contable Sniffler</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/contable_sniffler_by_asko_sirkia_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/contable_sniffler_by_asko_sirkia_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Contable Sniffler by Asko Sirkia Title: &amp;ldquo;Countable Sniffler&amp;rdquo; by Asko Sirkia Review: &amp;ldquo;Countable Sniffler&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes young readers on an exciting adventure with its lovable protagonist, Sniffler. Author Asko Sirkia has skillfully crafted a story that not only entertains but also teaches valuable life lessons. The book is targeted towards children aged 5 to 8 years old, making it a perfect addition to any elementary school library or home bookshelf.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Der Struwwelpeter</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/der_struwwelpeter_by_heinrich_hoffman_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/der_struwwelpeter_by_heinrich_hoffman_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Der Struwwelpeter by Heinrich Hoffman Title: Der Struwwelpeter Author: Heinrich Hoffman Der Struwwelpeter is a classic children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Heinrich Hoffman in 1845. The book consists of ten short stories, each with a moral lesson and an accompanying illustration. The stories are aimed at children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old, making it an excellent choice for parents and teachers looking for engaging and educational content. The book&amp;rsquo;s title character, Struwwelpeter, is a boy with unkempt hair and untrimmed fingernails.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Henry and Amy</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/henry_and_amy_by_stephen_michael_king_isbn_802786871/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/henry_and_amy_by_stephen_michael_king_isbn_802786871/</guid>
      <description>Henry and Amy by Stephen Michael King Title: Henry and Amy Author: Stephen Michael King Target Age Group: 4-8 years old Henry and Amy is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book written and illustrated by the talented Stephen Michael King. The story revolves around the friendship between a young boy named Henry and a magical, flying pig named Amy. Together, they embark on a series of adventures, learning valuable life lessons along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Will Not Ever Never Eat a Tomato</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/i_will_not_ever_never_eat_a_tomato_by_lauren_child_isbn_9780763611880/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/i_will_not_ever_never_eat_a_tomato_by_lauren_child_isbn_9780763611880/</guid>
      <description>I Will Not Ever Never Eat a Tomato by Lauren Child Title: I Will Not Ever Never Eat a Tomato Author: Lauren Child Review: &amp;ldquo;I Will Not Ever Never Eat a Tomato&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Lauren Child, targeting young readers between the ages of 4 to 8 years old. The story revolves around a young girl named Lola, who is very particular about her food choices and refuses to eat anything that is not her favorite.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Llama Llama Red Pajama</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/llama_llama_red_pajama_isbn_606400931/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/llama_llama_red_pajama_isbn_606400931/</guid>
      <description>Llama Llama Red Pajama Title: Llama Llama Red Pajama Author: Anna Dewdney Review: Llama Llama Red Pajama is a charming and delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Anna Dewdney. The story follows a young llama named Baby Llama who becomes anxious and worried when his mother, Mama Llama, goes out for the evening. As Baby Llama struggles with separation anxiety, he learns valuable lessons about patience, trust, and the importance of a loving and supportive family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Sea Monster</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_sea_monster_by_christopher_wormell_isbn_9780224070256/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_sea_monster_by_christopher_wormell_isbn_9780224070256/</guid>
      <description>The Sea Monster by Christopher Wormell Title: The Sea Monster Author: Christopher Wormell Age Group: 5-8 years old The Sea Monster is a beautifully illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book by Christopher Wormell that tells the story of a young boy named Jack who goes on a thrilling adventure at sea. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 5 and 8 years old, and it teaches valuable life lessons through its engaging narrative and stunning artwork.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zen Shorts</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/zen_shorts_isbn_9780545040877/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/zen_shorts_isbn_9780545040877/</guid>
      <description>Zen Shorts Title: Zen Shorts Author: Jon J. Muth Target Age Group: 5-10 years old &amp;ldquo;Zen Shorts&amp;rdquo; is a beautifully illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book that captures the essence of mindfulness and the importance of finding inner peace. Author Jon J. Muth has skillfully crafted a story that is both engaging and educational for young readers. The book follows the story of three siblings, Michael, Karl, and Addy, who meet a wise and mysterious panda named Stillwater.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Chair for My Mother</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/a_chair_for_my_mother_isbn_9780874993356/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/a_chair_for_my_mother_isbn_9780874993356/</guid>
      <description>A Chair for My Mother Title: A Chair for My Mother Author: Vera B. Williams Recommended Age Group: 4-8 years old &amp;ldquo;A Chair for My Mother&amp;rdquo; is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Vera B. Williams, which beautifully captures the spirit of love, family, and perseverance. The story follows a young girl named Rosa, who lives with her mother and grandmother in a small apartment. After their previous home was destroyed by a fire, the family saved coins in a jar to buy a comfortable chair for Rosa&amp;rsquo;s hardworking mother.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drac and the Gremlin</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/drac_and_the_gremlin_by_allan_bailie_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/drac_and_the_gremlin_by_allan_bailie_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Drac and the Gremlin by Allan Bailie Title: Drac and the Gremlin Author: Allan Bailie Review: Drac and the Gremlin is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the adventures of Drac, a young dragon, and his friend, the Gremlin. The story is set in a magical world where dragons and other mythical creatures coexist. The book is beautifully illustrated, with vibrant colors and detailed images that will capture the imagination of young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mr Majeika</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/mr_majeika_by_humphrey_carpenter_isbn_141323086/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/mr_majeika_by_humphrey_carpenter_isbn_141323086/</guid>
      <description>Mr Majeika by Humphrey Carpenter Title: Mr Majeika Author: Humphrey Carpenter &amp;ldquo;Mr Majeika&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Humphrey Carpenter, which tells the story of a young girl named Hilary and her encounters with the magical Mr Majeika. The book is suitable for children aged 7 to 10 years old, and it covers various life lessons that are essential for their growth and development. The story revolves around Hilary, who is having a hard time fitting in at her new school.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not So Fast Songololo</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/not_so_fast_songololo_by_niki_daly_isbn_9780711218895/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/not_so_fast_songololo_by_niki_daly_isbn_9780711218895/</guid>
      <description>Not So Fast Songololo by Niki Daly Title: Not So Fast Songololo Author: Niki Daly Review: Not So Fast Songololo is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young boy named Songololo who learns the importance of patience and hard work. The book is beautifully illustrated with vibrant colors and engaging images that capture the attention of young readers. The story is relatable for children, as it teaches them about the value of perseverance and the rewards that come with putting in effort.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stellaluna</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/stellaluna_by_janell_cannon_isbn_1859028667/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/stellaluna_by_janell_cannon_isbn_1859028667/</guid>
      <description>Stellaluna by Janell Cannon Title: Stellaluna Author: Janell Cannon Review: Stellaluna is a beautifully illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Janell Cannon. The story follows a young fruit bat named Stellaluna who becomes separated from her mother and is adopted by a family of birds. As Stellaluna grows up, she learns about the differences between bats and birds, ultimately discovering her true identity and reuniting with her mother. The book is targeted towards children aged 4 to 8 years old, as it teaches valuable life lessons in a simple and engaging manner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tar Beach</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/tar_beach_isbn_590463810/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/tar_beach_isbn_590463810/</guid>
      <description>Tar Beach Title: Tar Beach Author: Faith Ringgold Target Age Group: 5-10 years old Tar Beach is a captivating children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Faith Ringgold, which takes readers on a magical journey through the eyes of a young girl named Cassie. The story is set in the 1930s and is based on the author&amp;rsquo;s own experiences growing up in Harlem. The book is beautifully illustrated with Faith Ringgold&amp;rsquo;s quilt-like artwork, which adds to the charm and uniqueness of the story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Enormous Crocodile</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_enormous_crocodile_isbn_9789750719257/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_enormous_crocodile_isbn_9789750719257/</guid>
      <description>The Enormous Crocodile Title: The Enormous Crocodile Author: Roald Dahl Illustrator: Quentin Blake Recommended Age Group: 4-8 years old The Enormous Crocodile is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the renowned author Roald Dahl and beautifully illustrated by Quentin Blake. This charming story is perfect for children aged 4-8 years old, as it features colorful illustrations and a simple yet engaging plot. The story revolves around a greedy and devious crocodile who has a voracious appetite for children.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Prince of Motordu</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_prince_of_motordu_by_pef_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_prince_of_motordu_by_pef_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Prince of Motordu by Pef Title: The Prince of Motordu Author: Pef The Prince of Motordu is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the adventures of a young prince who loves to explore and tinker with things. The story is filled with vibrant illustrations that capture the imagination of young readers and keep them engaged throughout the book. The target age group for this book is 6-10 years old. The story is simple enough for young readers to understand and enjoy, while also being engaging enough to keep the attention of older children.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amelia Bedelia</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/amelia_bedelia_by_peggy_parish_isbn_153642658x/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/amelia_bedelia_by_peggy_parish_isbn_153642658x/</guid>
      <description>Amelia Bedelia by Peggy Parish Title: Amelia Bedelia Author: Peggy Parish Review: Amelia Bedelia is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Peggy Parish, which has captured the hearts of young readers for generations. The story follows the adventures of Amelia Bedelia, a charming and well-intentioned character who tends to take things literally. Target Age Group: The book is suitable for children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old. The simple language and amusing illustrations make it an enjoyable read for this age group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are You My Mother?</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/are_you_my_mother_isbn_1718185/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/are_you_my_mother_isbn_1718185/</guid>
      <description>Are You My Mother? Title: Are You My Mother? Author: P.D. Eastman Genre: Children&amp;rsquo;s Picture Book Recommended Age Group: 3-7 years old Are You My Mother? is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s picture book written by P.D. Eastman. This charming story follows a baby bird who hatches while his mother is away, and goes on a journey to find her. The book is filled with colorful illustrations and simple language, making it perfect for young readers and listeners alike.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blueberries for Sal</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/blueberries_for_sal_by_robert_mccloskey_isbn_9780812422085/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/blueberries_for_sal_by_robert_mccloskey_isbn_9780812422085/</guid>
      <description>Blueberries for Sal by Robert McCloskey Title: Blueberries for Sal Author: Robert McCloskey Review: Blueberries for Sal is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written and illustrated by Robert McCloskey. First published in 1948, this timeless classic has continued to charm readers of all ages with its heartwarming story and beautiful illustrations. The book tells the story of a young girl named Sal and her mother, who go blueberry picking on a beautiful summer day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Caps for Sale</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/caps_for_sale_isbn_9780590630726/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/caps_for_sale_isbn_9780590630726/</guid>
      <description>Caps for Sale Title: Caps for Sale Author: Esphyr Slobodkina Review: Caps for Sale is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a cap salesman who encounters a mischievous group of monkeys while trying to sell his caps. The story is set in a simple and colorful world, which makes it appealing to young readers. The book is targeted towards children aged 4 to 8 years old. It teaches valuable life lessons, such as the importance of hard work, patience, and problem-solving.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frog and Toad Are Friends</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/frog_and_toad_are_friends_by_arnold_lobel_isbn_9780867342123/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/frog_and_toad_are_friends_by_arnold_lobel_isbn_9780867342123/</guid>
      <description>Frog and Toad Are Friends by Arnold Lobel Title: Frog and Toad Are Friends Author: Arnold Lobel Review: &amp;ldquo;Frog and Toad Are Friends&amp;rdquo; is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Arnold Lobel, which beautifully illustrates the power of friendship and the importance of understanding and accepting each other&amp;rsquo;s differences. The book is perfect for children between the ages of 4 and 8, as it contains simple yet profound life lessons that are easy to grasp and relate to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joseph&#39;s Yard</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/josephs_yard_by_charles_keeping_isbn_9780192721723/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/josephs_yard_by_charles_keeping_isbn_9780192721723/</guid>
      <description>Joseph&amp;rsquo;s Yard by Charles Keeping Title: Joseph&amp;rsquo;s Yard Author: Charles Keeping &amp;ldquo;Joseph&amp;rsquo;s Yard&amp;rdquo; is a beautifully illustrated children&amp;rsquo;s book by the talented author and illustrator, Charles Keeping. This story is a delightful read for children aged 4 to 8 years old, and it effectively conveys essential life lessons through its captivating narrative and stunning visuals. The story revolves around Joseph, a hardworking man who spends his days tending to his garden.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leo the Late Bloomer</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/leo_the_late_bloomer_by_robert_kraus_isbn_694009806/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/leo_the_late_bloomer_by_robert_kraus_isbn_694009806/</guid>
      <description>Leo the Late Bloomer by Robert Kraus Title: Leo the Late Bloomer Author: Robert Kraus Review: Leo the Late Bloomer is a heartwarming and inspiring children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young lion named Leo, who struggles with feeling left behind as he watches his friends excel in various skills and abilities. The book, written by Robert Kraus, beautifully illustrates the importance of patience, self-acceptance, and embracing one&amp;rsquo;s unique journey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Morning in Maine</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/one_morning_in_maine_isbn_9780808536338/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/one_morning_in_maine_isbn_9780808536338/</guid>
      <description>One Morning in Maine Title: One Morning in Maine Author: Robert McCloskey One Morning in Maine is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written and illustrated by Robert McCloskey. The story follows the adventures of a young girl named Sal and her little sister, Jane, as they spend a day exploring the coast of Maine with their mother. The book is filled with beautiful illustrations that capture the essence of the Maine coastline and the charm of a small fishing village.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sylvester and the Magic Pebble</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/sylvester_and_the_magic_pebble_isbn_043973522x/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/sylvester_and_the_magic_pebble_isbn_043973522x/</guid>
      <description>Sylvester and the Magic Pebble Title: Sylvester and the Magic Pebble Author: William Steig Recommended Age Group: 4-8 years old &amp;ldquo;Sylvester and the Magic Pebble&amp;rdquo; is a heartwarming and enchanting children&amp;rsquo;s book written by William Steig. The story follows Sylvester, a young donkey who finds a magic pebble that grants wishes. When a series of unfortunate events occur, Sylvester and his family learn valuable life lessons about love, patience, and the importance of family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crocodile Beat</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/crocodile_beat_by_gail_jorgensen_isbn_689718810/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/crocodile_beat_by_gail_jorgensen_isbn_689718810/</guid>
      <description>Crocodile Beat by Gail Jorgensen Title: Crocodile Beat Author: Gail Jorgensen Crocodile Beat is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Gail Jorgensen, which takes the reader on an adventurous journey into the world of a young crocodile named Croc. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 4 to 8 years old and is filled with vibrant illustrations that capture the imagination of young readers. The story follows Croc as he learns to play the drums and eventually forms a band with his animal friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frog in Winter</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/frog_in_winter_by_max_velthuijs_isbn_9781842704479/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/frog_in_winter_by_max_velthuijs_isbn_9781842704479/</guid>
      <description>Frog in Winter by Max Velthuijs Title: Frog in Winter Author: Max Velthuijs Frog in Winter is a charming and delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book by Max Velthuijs, which tells the story of a frog who experiences the beauty and challenges of winter for the first time. The book is suitable for children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old, and it teaches valuable life lessons about friendship, overcoming fears, and embracing new experiences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lost and Found</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/lost_and_found_by_oliver_jeffers_isbn_7240376/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/lost_and_found_by_oliver_jeffers_isbn_7240376/</guid>
      <description>Lost and Found by Oliver Jeffers Title: Lost and Found Author: Oliver Jeffers Review: Lost and Found, written and illustrated by Oliver Jeffers, is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young boy who finds a lost penguin at his doorstep. The boy embarks on a journey to return the penguin to its home in the South Pole. This beautifully illustrated book is suitable for children aged 4-8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Madlenka</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/madlenka_by_peter_sis_isbn_9780439233132/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/madlenka_by_peter_sis_isbn_9780439233132/</guid>
      <description>Madlenka by Peter Sis Title: Madlenka Author: Peter Sis Madlenka is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the adventures of a young girl named Madlenka, who lives in a charming city apartment building. The story takes the reader on a journey through Madlenka&amp;rsquo;s day, as she interacts with her neighbors and friends, each with their own unique story to tell. The book is beautifully illustrated by the author, Peter Sis, who uses vibrant colors and intricate details to bring the city and its inhabitants to life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marc Just Couldn&#39;t Sleep</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/marc_just_couldnt_sleep_by_gabriela_keselman_isbn_9781929132911/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/marc_just_couldnt_sleep_by_gabriela_keselman_isbn_9781929132911/</guid>
      <description>Marc Just Couldn&amp;rsquo;t Sleep by Gabriela Keselman Title: Marc Just Couldn&amp;rsquo;t Sleep Author: Gabriela Keselman Review: Marc Just Couldn&amp;rsquo;t Sleep is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book that tells the story of a young boy named Marc who struggles to fall asleep at night. Through vivid illustrations and engaging storytelling, author Gabriela Keselman takes readers on a journey with Marc as he tries various methods to overcome his sleeplessness. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 4 and 8, making it an ideal bedtime story for parents to read with their young ones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Old Bear</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/old_bear_isbn_99413353/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/old_bear_isbn_99413353/</guid>
      <description>Old Bear Title: Old Bear Author: Kevin Henkes Review: Old Bear is a heartwarming children&amp;rsquo;s book written and illustrated by Kevin Henkes. The story revolves around a young girl named Emily, who is given a stuffed bear as a gift by her grandmother. The bear, named Old Bear, is well-loved by Emily and becomes her constant companion. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 4 to 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Owl Moon</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/owl_moon_isbn_9780590420440/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/owl_moon_isbn_9780590420440/</guid>
      <description>Owl Moon Title: Owl Moon Author: Jane Yolen Illustrator: John Schoenherr Recommended Age Group: 4-8 years old &amp;ldquo;Owl Moon&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Jane Yolen and illustrated by John Schoenherr. This story is a perfect blend of adventure, family bonding, and the beauty of nature. The book is recommended for children aged 4-8 years old and is a perfect read-aloud story for bedtime or anytime. The story follows a young girl and her father as they venture into the snowy woods in search of an owl.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pumpkin Soup</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/pumpkin_soup_by_helen_cooper_isbn_374460310/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/pumpkin_soup_by_helen_cooper_isbn_374460310/</guid>
      <description>Pumpkin Soup by Helen Cooper Title: Pumpkin Soup Author: Helen Cooper &amp;ldquo;Pumpkin Soup&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Helen Cooper, which tells the story of three friends - a cat, a squirrel, and a duck - who live in a cozy cottage and work together to make delicious pumpkin soup. The book is filled with beautiful illustrations and captivating storytelling, making it a perfect read for young children. Target Age Group: The book is suitable for children between the ages of 3 and 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slinky Malinki</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/slinky_malinki_by_lynley_dodd_isbn_9780907349747/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/slinky_malinki_by_lynley_dodd_isbn_9780907349747/</guid>
      <description>Slinky Malinki by Lynley Dodd Title: Slinky Malinki Author: Lynley Dodd Review: Slinky Malinki is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Lynley Dodd, which follows the adventures of a mischievous cat named Slinky Malinki. The story is engaging and fun, making it a perfect read for children between the ages of 3 to 7 years old. The book&amp;rsquo;s illustrations are vibrant and captivating, which adds to the overall charm of the story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Adventures of Maya the Bee</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_adventures_of_maya_the_bee_by_waldemar_bonsels_isbn_1627937587/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_adventures_of_maya_the_bee_by_waldemar_bonsels_isbn_1627937587/</guid>
      <description>The Adventures of Maya the Bee by Waldemar Bonsels Title: The Adventures of Maya the Bee Author: Waldemar Bonsels Review: The Adventures of Maya the Bee, written by Waldemar Bonsels, is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the journey of Maya, a young bee who embarks on an adventure to explore the world outside her hive. The story is filled with colorful characters, exciting adventures, and valuable life lessons that make it an enjoyable read for children aged 6 to 10 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where&#39;s My Teddy</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/wheres_my_teddy_by_jez_alborough_isbn_1564020487/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/wheres_my_teddy_by_jez_alborough_isbn_1564020487/</guid>
      <description>Where&amp;rsquo;s My Teddy by Jez Alborough Title: Where&amp;rsquo;s My Teddy Author: Jez Alborough Review: Where&amp;rsquo;s My Teddy is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written and illustrated by Jez Alborough. The story revolves around a young boy named Eddie who loses his teddy bear, Freddy, and embarks on a journey to find him. Along the way, Eddie encounters various animals who help him in his quest, each teaching him valuable life lessons. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 3 and 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Widemouthed Frog</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/widemouthed_frog_by_francine_vidal_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/widemouthed_frog_by_francine_vidal_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Widemouthed Frog by Francine Vidal Title: Widemouthed Frog Author: Francine Vidal Review: &amp;ldquo;Widemouthed Frog&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Francine Vidal that tells the story of a wide-mouthed frog who sets out on a journey to find a new home. The book is beautifully illustrated and is perfect for children aged 4-8 years old. The story is filled with colorful and engaging illustrations that capture the attention of young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alfie Gets in First</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/alfie_gets_in_first_by_shirley_hughes_isbn_688008496/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/alfie_gets_in_first_by_shirley_hughes_isbn_688008496/</guid>
      <description>Alfie Gets in First by Shirley Hughes Title: Alfie Gets in First Author: Shirley Hughes Review: Alfie Gets in First is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the talented Shirley Hughes. The story revolves around a young boy named Alfie, who is eager to show his independence and curiosity. Alfie&amp;rsquo;s adventures in the book teach young readers valuable life lessons while also entertaining them with its charming illustrations and engaging storyline.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Avocado Baby</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/avocado_baby_by_john_burningham_isbn_690042434/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/avocado_baby_by_john_burningham_isbn_690042434/</guid>
      <description>Avocado Baby by John Burningham Title: Avocado Baby Author: John Burningham Review: Avocado Baby is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book by the talented author and illustrator John Burningham. The story follows the journey of a young couple who, after trying various methods to have a baby, finally succeed in growing one from an avocado seed. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old. It is filled with colorful and engaging illustrations that capture the imagination of young readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brown Bear, Brown Bear, What Do You See?</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/brown_bear_brown_bear_what_do_you_see_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/brown_bear_brown_bear_what_do_you_see_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Brown Bear, Brown Bear, What Do You See? Title: Brown Bear, Brown Bear, What Do You See? Author: Bill Martin Jr. Illustrator: Eric Carle Review: Brown Bear, Brown Bear, What Do You See? is a delightful and engaging children&amp;rsquo;s book that captivates young readers with its vibrant illustrations and simple, rhythmic text. The book is ideal for children aged 2 to 5 years old, as it helps them develop their visual and auditory skills while introducing them to various animals and colors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clifford the Big Red Dog</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/clifford_the_big_red_dog_isbn_9780439409506/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/clifford_the_big_red_dog_isbn_9780439409506/</guid>
      <description>Clifford the Big Red Dog Title: Clifford the Big Red Dog Author: Norman Bridwell Clifford the Big Red Dog is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Norman Bridwell. This book is a perfect addition to any child&amp;rsquo;s library, as it targets children aged 4 to 8 years old. The story follows the adventures of Clifford, a lovable and oversized red dog, and his owner, Emily Elizabeth. The book is filled with colorful illustrations that capture the attention of young readers and help them understand the story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Freight Train</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/freight_train_isbn_9789573212409/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/freight_train_isbn_9789573212409/</guid>
      <description>Freight Train Title: Freight Train Author: Donald Crews Freight Train is a charming and vibrant children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes young readers on a journey through the world of trains. With its simple yet engaging story and colorful illustrations, this book is perfect for children aged 2 to 5 years old. The story follows a freight train as it travels through different landscapes, passing by cities, mountains, and tunnels. The book teaches children about colors, shapes, and the concept of a train&amp;rsquo;s journey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Go, Dog. Go!</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/go_dog._go_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/go_dog._go_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Go, Dog. Go! Title: Go, Dog. Go! Author: P.D. Eastman Review: Go, Dog. Go! is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the adventures of a group of dogs as they travel to a big dog party. The book is filled with colorful illustrations and simple, engaging text that makes it perfect for young readers. Target Age Group: The book is suitable for children between the ages of 3 and 7 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Green Eggs and Ham</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/green_eggs_and_ham_isbn_1717952/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/green_eggs_and_ham_isbn_1717952/</guid>
      <description>Green Eggs and Ham Title: Green Eggs and Ham Author: Dr. Seuss Review: Green Eggs and Ham is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the renowned author Dr. Seuss. This book is a classic and has been enjoyed by children for generations. The story follows the adventures of Sam-I-Am, who tries to convince an unnamed character to try green eggs and ham. The unnamed character is initially hesitant, but eventually gives in and ends up enjoying the dish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little I Am I</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/little_i_am_i_by_mira_lobe_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/little_i_am_i_by_mira_lobe_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Little I Am I by Mira Lobe Title: Little I Am I Author: Mira Lobe Review: Little I Am I is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Mira Lobe, which is perfect for young readers between the ages of 4 and 8. The book follows the story of a little girl who is trying to find her place in the world and learn about the importance of self-worth. The illustrations in the book are vibrant and eye-catching, which helps to keep the young readers engaged.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lyle, Lyle Crocodile</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/lyle_lyle_crocodile_by_bernard_waber_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/lyle_lyle_crocodile_by_bernard_waber_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>Lyle, Lyle Crocodile by Bernard Waber Title: Lyle, Lyle Crocodile Author: Bernard Waber Review: Lyle, Lyle Crocodile is a charming and delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Bernard Waber. The story revolves around a friendly crocodile named Lyle, who lives in a house on East 88th Street in New York City with the Primm family. Lyle loves to sing and perform, and he becomes a beloved member of the community. The book is aimed at children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mr Archimedes&#39; Bath</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/mr_archimedes_bath_by_pamela_allen_isbn_688419194/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/mr_archimedes_bath_by_pamela_allen_isbn_688419194/</guid>
      <description>Mr Archimedes&amp;rsquo; Bath by Pamela Allen Title: Mr Archimedes&amp;rsquo; Bath Author: Pamela Allen &amp;ldquo;Mr Archimedes&amp;rsquo; Bath&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the talented author, Pamela Allen. The story follows the adventures of a dog named Mr. Archimedes, who loves taking baths in the bathtub. One day, he discovers that the water level in the bathtub is rising, and he embarks on a journey to find out why. This book is an excellent choice for children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pancakes for Findus</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/pancakes_for_findus_by_sven_nordqvist_isbn_1912480441/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/pancakes_for_findus_by_sven_nordqvist_isbn_1912480441/</guid>
      <description>Pancakes for Findus by Sven Nordqvist Title: Pancakes for Findus Author: Sven Nordqvist &amp;ldquo;Pancakes for Findus&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Sven Nordqvist, which tells the story of an old man named Farmer Pettson and his curious cat, Findus. The book is a part of a series that revolves around the adventures of Pettson and Findus, and this particular story focuses on the duo&amp;rsquo;s attempt to make pancakes together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peace at Last</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/peace_at_last_isbn_9780230015487/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/peace_at_last_isbn_9780230015487/</guid>
      <description>Peace at Last Title: Peace at Last Author: Jill Murphy Target Age Group: 4-8 years old Review: &amp;ldquo;Peace at Last&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Jill Murphy, which takes young readers on a heartwarming adventure with the endearing Mr. Bear and his family. The story follows Mr. Bear as he tries to find a quiet place to sleep after being constantly disturbed by the noises made by his family members.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Little House</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_little_house_isbn_1536423041/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_little_house_isbn_1536423041/</guid>
      <description>The Little House Title: The Little House Author: Virginia Lee Burton Review: The Little House is a charming children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Virginia Lee Burton, which tells the story of a little house that has been built in the countryside. The story follows the house as it witnesses the changes around it, from the peaceful countryside to the bustling city that eventually surrounds it. The book beautifully captures the essence of time and the impact of progress on our surroundings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Story of Babar</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_story_of_babar_by_jean_de_brunhoff_isbn_590757482/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_story_of_babar_by_jean_de_brunhoff_isbn_590757482/</guid>
      <description>The Story of Babar by Jean De Brunhoff Title: The Story of Babar Author: Jean De Brunhoff Review: The Story of Babar, written and illustrated by Jean De Brunhoff, is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that has captured the hearts of readers for generations. Originally published in 1931, this timeless classic tells the story of a young elephant named Babar who embarks on a series of adventures after losing his mother to hunters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Story of the Root Children</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_story_of_the_root_children_by_sibylie_von_olfers_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_story_of_the_root_children_by_sibylie_von_olfers_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>The Story of the Root Children by Sibylie Von Olfers Title: The Story of the Root Children Author: Sibylie Von Olfers Review: The Story of the Root Children is a beautifully illustrated and enchanting children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes readers on a magical journey through the seasons. Written by Sibylie Von Olfers, this book is perfect for children aged 4-8 years old. The story follows the adventures of the Root Children, who work diligently to help Mother Earth prepare for each new season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Are the Triplets</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/we_are_the_triplets_by_roser_capdevila_isbn_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/we_are_the_triplets_by_roser_capdevila_isbn_0/</guid>
      <description>We Are the Triplets by Roser Capdevila Title: We Are the Triplets Author: Roser Capdevila Review: We Are the Triplets is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the adventures of three young siblings who, despite being triplets, have their own unique personalities and interests. The story is told through colorful illustrations and simple, engaging text that will capture the attention of young readers. Target Age Group: This book is suitable for children between the ages of 4 and 8 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bathwater&#39;s Hot</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/bathwaters_hot_by_shirley_hughes_isbn_744526450/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/bathwaters_hot_by_shirley_hughes_isbn_744526450/</guid>
      <description>Bathwater&amp;rsquo;s Hot by Shirley Hughes Title: Bathwater&amp;rsquo;s Hot Author: Shirley Hughes Review: Bathwater&amp;rsquo;s Hot is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by the talented author and illustrator, Shirley Hughes. The story follows a young girl named Lucy as she navigates her day-to-day life with her family and friends. The book is perfect for children aged 4-8 years old, as it teaches valuable life lessons through simple, relatable situations. One of the key themes in Bathwater&amp;rsquo;s Hot is the importance of family and the joy of spending time together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dear Zoo</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/dear_zoo_isbn_9780590078689/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/dear_zoo_isbn_9780590078689/</guid>
      <description>Dear Zoo Title: Dear Zoo Author: Rod Campbell Illustrator: Rod Campbell Publisher: Little Simon (Simon &amp;amp; Schuster) Target Age Group: 2-5 years old Dear Zoo is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that follows the story of a young child who writes to the zoo asking for a pet. The zoo sends various animals, but each time, the child returns them because they are not suitable for the home. The story concludes with the perfect pet being delivered, and the child is overjoyed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Each Peach Pear Plum</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/each_peach_pear_plum_isbn_140509194/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/each_peach_pear_plum_isbn_140509194/</guid>
      <description>Each Peach Pear Plum Title: Each Peach Pear Plum Author: Janet and Allan Ahlberg Review: Each Peach Pear Plum is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book that takes young readers on a journey through a world of fairy tales, all within the pages of a single story. The book is filled with vibrant illustrations and simple, engaging text that will capture the attention of children aged 3-7 years old. The story follows a series of characters from classic fairy tales, such as Little Red Riding Hood, Cinderella, and Jack and Jill, as they interact with one another in unexpected ways.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make Way for Ducklings</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/make_way_for_ducklings_isbn_874996589/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/make_way_for_ducklings_isbn_874996589/</guid>
      <description>Make Way for Ducklings Title: Make Way for Ducklings Author: Robert McCloskey Target Age Group: 4-8 years old &amp;ldquo;Make Way for Ducklings&amp;rdquo; is a timeless classic written by Robert McCloskey, which has been capturing the hearts of young readers since its publication in 1941. The story revolves around a family of ducks who are searching for a safe place to raise their ducklings in Boston&amp;rsquo;s Public Garden. The book is beautifully illustrated, with detailed drawings that bring the characters to life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Owl Babies</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/owl_babies_by_martin_waddell_isbn_1854303449/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/owl_babies_by_martin_waddell_isbn_1854303449/</guid>
      <description>Owl Babies by Martin Waddell Title: Owl Babies Author: Martin Waddell Owl Babies is a heartwarming and engaging children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Martin Waddell. The story follows the adventures of three young owlets who wake up one night to find their mother missing from their nest. The three siblings, Sarah, Percy, and Bill, are filled with worry and concern as they wait for their mother&amp;rsquo;s return. The book is beautifully illustrated by Patrick Benson, with soft and warm images that perfectly capture the emotions of the young owlets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pat the Bunny</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/pat_the_bunny_isbn_9784062740036/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/pat_the_bunny_isbn_9784062740036/</guid>
      <description>Pat the Bunny Title: Pat the Bunny Author: Dorothy Kunhardt Age Group: Infants and Toddlers (0-3 years old) Pat the Bunny is a classic children&amp;rsquo;s book that has been cherished by generations of young readers. Written by Dorothy Kunhardt and first published in 1940, this timeless story has become a staple in many households. The book is specifically designed for infants and toddlers, making it an excellent choice for parents looking to introduce their little ones to the world of reading.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rosie&#39;s Walk</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/rosies_walk_by_pat_hutchins_isbn_370324463/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/rosies_walk_by_pat_hutchins_isbn_370324463/</guid>
      <description>Rosie&amp;rsquo;s Walk by Pat Hutchins Title: Rosie&amp;rsquo;s Walk Author: Pat Hutchins Review: Rosie&amp;rsquo;s Walk is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written and illustrated by Pat Hutchins. The story follows Rosie, a hen, as she takes a walk around the farm, unaware of the danger that lurks behind her. The illustrations are vibrant and engaging, with the simple yet effective art style that perfectly captures the essence of the story. Target Age Group: The book is best suited for children between the ages of 3 and 8.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Little Engine That Could</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_little_engine_that_could_by_watty_piper_isbn_448189631/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_little_engine_that_could_by_watty_piper_isbn_448189631/</guid>
      <description>The Little Engine That Could by Watty Piper Title: The Little Engine That Could Author: Watty Piper The Little Engine That Could is a classic children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Watty Piper. This heartwarming story has been a favorite among children and parents alike for generations. The book is beautifully illustrated and has a simple, yet powerful message that resonates with readers of all ages. The story revolves around a little blue engine that is faced with the daunting task of pulling a long train over a steep mountain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Very Hungry Caterpillar</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/the_very_hungry_caterpillar_isbn_9788417074609/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/the_very_hungry_caterpillar_isbn_9788417074609/</guid>
      <description>The Very Hungry Caterpillar Title: The Very Hungry Caterpillar Author: Eric Carle The Very Hungry Caterpillar is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written by Eric Carle. This book is a timeless classic that has been enjoyed by children all over the world since its publication in 1969. The story follows the journey of a caterpillar as it transforms into a beautiful butterfly. The book is targeted towards children between the ages of 2 and 5 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where&#39;s Spot?</title>
      <link>https://www.monsty.co/wheres_spot_isbn_399243739/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.monsty.co/wheres_spot_isbn_399243739/</guid>
      <description>Where&amp;rsquo;s Spot? Title: Where&amp;rsquo;s Spot? Author: Eric Hill Age Group: 2-5 years old &amp;ldquo;Where&amp;rsquo;s Spot?&amp;rdquo; is a delightful children&amp;rsquo;s book written and illustrated by Eric Hill. The story follows the adventures of a lovable dog named Spot as he explores his world and makes new friends. The book is targeted towards children aged 2-5 years old, and it teaches valuable life lessons through its engaging and colorful illustrations. The book&amp;rsquo;s primary focus is on the importance of friendship, as Spot encounters various animals throughout the story.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
